Chapter 1270: [Black Star's Era]!

In an office of Black Star Palace, Han Xiao leaned back in his chair, staring at the clock as he silently awaited the prompt that signaled the new version beginning. Time slowly ticked by second after second.

In this past year, the three Universal Civilizations and the association's relationship had dropped to a freezing point. The dynasty had not contacted him for a whole year now.

The three Universal Civilizations had issued an announcement a year ago that they had started studying the Sanctum Revival method. There was no follow-up news, and no one knew what stage they had reached. It seemed like their results were not too impressive.

On the side of the Holy Accord, they were still collecting the keys in secret. While they did not possess the intelligence channels of the three Universal Civilizations, causing the materials to be harder to collect, the problem was not big. It would just cost them more money and time. Now that the Holy Accord had more of the recipes of how to create keys, there were more opportunities for them, but a mere year was not enough to collect another key.

On the other hand, the military of the three Universal Civilizations had mobilized recently, seemingly getting ready to set off. This caught the attention of Han Xiao and the other members of the association, causing the atmosphere in the universe to become more tense.

The players' return at this time could thus be considered timely.

Han Xiao rubbed the back of his palm as his eyes flashed.

"The time when the players come online will be my opportunity to quickly reach level 360. With the current deadlock in the situation, if I manage to break through my personal power level, it might serve as a turning point, becoming the entry ticket to breaking this entire game."

The stalemate was exactly what he had predicted and what he wanted. Were it not for the Sanctum Revivals and the massive increase in strength of the association, perhaps the Calamity of the Supers would have long broken out like in his previous life. Right now, he was only suppressing it.

While the situation was akin to a gunpowder keg, which would result in a greater explosion the more he suppressed it, nothing was absolute. In his opinion, there were only a few opportunities to break the game. If he succeeded, he would really eliminate the Calamity of the Supers and prevent it from evolving into a large-scale war.

His current methods were all to stall time for the Holy Accord. Han Xiao was equally clear that there would be a battle between both sides, and the association would naturally have more casualties. This was his opportunity. As long as the unlimited counts of the Sanctum Revival were revealed by that time, most of their problems would be solved. The Sanctum Revival key was a necessity to break this game.

On this basis, he could use a higher level of personal power to frighten the three Universal Civilizations and also attract Beyond Grade A members. That would be killing two birds with one stone.

Just as he was analyzing his options, the long silent interface finally had some movement. There was a notification of a new update just like what the players would receive.

Version 5.0 Activated!

Fetching data… Fetching data complete!

Player Forum Opened.

Welcome to 'Galaxy' Version 5.0—Black Star's Era!

"Hmm?" Han Xiao was stunned.

Why was the version not 'Calamity of the Supers'‽

And it even used his name!

In the previous four versions, while he was a little butterfly flapping its wings and causing an impact, compared to the general trend of the universe, it was miniscule, still moving along with the changes in time.

But this time was different. He had single-handedly created a tornado with a flap of his wings, causing himself to become the pioneer of the changing times. Thus, even the name of this version had changed…

This also showed how important his position was in the universe at the moment, as well as his pivotal role in this storm.

"Even my name has been included into the version update. This is superb."

Han Xiao's expression twitched, before he revealed a perverted smile.

What was prestige and face? This was!

If the players saw this… heh, this was equivalent to a super compound fertilizer that would help him farm his leeks!

"It's been fifty years. I really miss my cute little… moneybags."

Han Xiao raised his brows, calling out the surveillance of the great hall and observing the situation.

At this moment, countless white lights flashed in the lobby of Black Star Palace's great hall, and the large number of players that had been away for fifty years finally returned online.

The originally cold and empty great hall was suddenly packed to the brim, full of liveliness. Countless players were excitedly whooping and shouting.

"Wahaha, this master is back! Countless stars, prepare to tremble under my feet, for my huge cannon's hunger and thirst can no longer be suppressed!"

"Dammit, it's already the fifth version, so why is there still a bug that prevents us from stripping? Lousy!"

"Hehe, I can immediately tell that you're not a pioneer. To this day, you're still hung up over the fact that clothes cannot be taken off. You're behind the times brother! Do you know the meaning of 'clothes on the body but naked in the mind'? This older brother's realm is one that you cannot hope to fathom!"

"How long has passed since the last version? I don't see any changes in the base. It seems like we weren't gone for too long."

The crowd chattered and gossiped, opening their interfaces. Immediately came the shocked gasps.

"Hurry and take a look at the version's name! I'm shooketh!"

"F*ck, the name of Version 5.0 is actually Black Star's Era?"

"What the hell has he done during the update!"

The countless army players opened their eyes wide.

No one expected that their faction leader would actually turn into the main topic of this version!

Based on the impressions of the players, the version name indicated what the Main Storyline would be. In the previous few versions, it was either a disaster or a changing of the time, but to think that they would actually put a character as the Main Storyline!

What prestige!

Many of the players began to tremble with excitement, their hearts filled with strong curiosity—just what exactly did their Army Commander do during their absence‽

The bunch of professional players that just came online were equally shocked.

Frenzied Sword immediately opened up the calendar. What he saw made him suck in a deep breath.

"The version update actually took a whole fifty years this time!"

Everyone immediately turned to look at the date, full of surprise and shock.

"Wow, really fifty years!"

"I remember when we went offline, it was in the Year 734. Right now, it's 782!"

"The span is too huge, more than double the previous updates."

"I don't even know if my wife Sylvia is still alive…"

"Do you want to eat sh*t? She's obviously my wife!"

"Quickly, go on the internet and check, see what the situation is right now."

The players immediately took out their communicators to search, wanting to check what exactly happened during the time they were away.

Following their searches, the news that the Flickering War had ended decades ago appeared on their pages, leading to more surprised gasps.

When they went offline, the Flickering War had still been raging, so they naturally thought that they would get to continue fighting the moment they returned online. To think that during the version update, the battle had already ended.

Reading on, the expressions of the players got even more confused. Some of them even catcalled.

The fall of Gaud, Sorokin escaping in fear of being sentenced for his crimes, Aurora entering the Beyond Grade A realm, the Sanctum Revivals leading to the Primordial Ones being resurrected, and the standoff between the Beyond Grade A Association and the three Universal Civilizations… A series of major events was shown before the eyes of the many players. Just looking at the description, many of the players could very well imagine the stormy situation that happened then.

"This… the change is too great!"

"Aurora has really entered the Beyond Grade A realm… Damn, who's this blonde sister? I've fallen in love with her!"

"This is amazing. Germinal is really the strongest representing organization in the whole universe. One sect, three Beyond Grade As—who else is that impressive?"

"The Germinal spirit will never wither! Hooyah!"

"This is indeed worthy of a span of fifty years. The original structure of the universe has been completely subverted."

"Black Star is too fierce. No wonder this version is named after him."

Everyone was shocked. They felt as though they had woken up from a long sleep only to find out that everything around them had changed.

Seeing the actions of Black Star during the update, many of the players understood why the name of Version 5.0 was called 'Black Star's Era'.

Their Army Commander had become the 'Leader of the Martial Way'. With his unparalleled courage and charisma, he led the Beyond Grade A class against the explored universe overlords. He was undoubtedly a leader of this era!

The title 'Black Star's Era' was totally worthy of the name!

"So fierce, Old Blackie is indeed an extraordinary existence."

"Army Commander is awesome! (voice cracks)"

"Next time, we shouldn't call him Black Star. We'll just address him as Black Deity."

"I'm not sure why, but I feel as though I'm watching my own son having grown up…"

The players had lots of mixed feelings.

The figure of Black Star had been with them through several versions, and now, he had even become the Main Storyline of the version, leading to a new era. His identity was unique in this universe. In their eyes, Black Star was already confirmed as the ultimate protagonist!

Many of the old hardcore players had personally watched Black Star rise from an insignificant person, stepping into the glorified altar. Their hearts had a sense of gratification, as though they were witnessing the continuation of a legend.

Bun-Hit-Dog was so excited, his entire body trembled. He immediately pinched his assistant, Little Wheat, who was beside him as he babbled, "Quickly! Material! A lot of material! At least twenty episodes of videos can be released using this. Quickly record them all!"

Little Wheat hurriedly nodded and began to record.

Meanwhile, Frenzied Sword and the professional players controlled their emotions, quickly checking the attributes panel.

"It seems like the upper limit this time has been opened to level 180."

"Speaking of which, most Calamity Grades usually enter the realm around level 160 and 170. While we're weaker than them at the same level, level 180 should be enough for us to hit the Calamity Grade, right?"

"It's possible. Maybe in this version, the strength of the players will be pulled apart. Those who can enter the Calamity Grade will definitely be able to slap and beat up a whole bunch of Grade Bs."

Everyone discussed their levels fervently before they remembered something.

"That's right. I remember that our main storyline for the Flickering War was not settled. Now that the war has ended, I wonder what has happened to the situation."

In the previous version, the Main Storyline in the Flickering War for the Black Star Army was something that Han Xiao had created, and it had long been settled. What the other organizations' players got was the true Main Storyline, which could only be settled after the war.

Hearing this, many of the players entered the forums, and with a glance, they almost laughed themselves to death.

They saw that the forums for the Flickering World were extremely lively, and many of them were crying blood and tears, especially those from the Limitless Financial Group.

[Fan Shuishui: Where's my faction? Where's my huge faction‽]

[Atlas: Madafaka, why has the entire Limitless Financial Group disappeared‽]

[Adventures of Tintin: Flickering World, ah Flickering World. The largest galactic consortium, the Limitless Financial Group, went bankrupt; the boss Sorokin owed up to 3.5 billion in debt for food, drinks, and gambling, and he took his mistress with him to go on the run! We toiled for half a year and didn't even get a single paycheck. B*stard Sorokin, you're not human!]

On the forums, there were a large portion of players who had lost their factions and were wailing. This was as good as them not having any contribution for the entire of Version 4.0.

Players who were in a smaller faction always lived on tenterhooks the moment they logged back in after a version update, fearing that their faction would be gone and all their effort wasted.

Originally, those players who had joined larger factions were not worried about this problem, but the Limitless Financial Group was no small faction, and it had actually disappeared, causing the players to feel immense regret.

If they had known this, they would have followed the other group of defectors to jump ship during the national war!

"Too unlucky."

"That's why choosing a faction is of utmost importance, just like picking stocks. One must be cautious!"

"It's lucky our Black Star Army is resilient enough."

Watching the scene, the army players could not help but laugh.

Even a behemoth like the Limitless Financial Group could crash. While the Black Star Army was strong, they had provoked the three Universal Civilizations, and thus, their futures were not too bright either.

Their Army Commander might be fierce, the association strong, and the Sanctum Revival miraculous, but their opponents were the three Universal Civilizations. Now that their original cooperative relationship had evolved to become enemies, many people did not have much confidence in battling them. If something went wrong, they might lose their faction like the Limitless Financial Group players.

"The battle between the Beyond Grade A Association and the three Universal Civilizations should be the Main Storyline of this version. We're inherently on the side of the association, but can we really win?"

"That's right. If the association loses, won't the army disband? Won't it be our loss then?"

Some people chatted in small voices, their stand wavering. These were all new players who had joined only in Version 4.0.

As for the veterans, while they were worried about the safety of the army, their stand was firm.

Most of the old players had long treated the army as their own faction, working hard to make it grow to where it was today. Even if the enemy was strong, they would not wish to switch to another faction. Anyway, they were not afraid of death, so it was still better to work for their own faction!

The army had shaped the sense of belonging for their players for many years, and the results showed. While players valued benefits, they sometimes went the opposite way instead. While benefits were important to them, the real core logic that determined a player's actions could be summarized in one sentence.

I do what makes me happy!

Ding!

At this moment, the interface of every army player rang at the same time.

You have triggered the S Ranked Main Storyline: Calamity of the Supers—Black Star Army!

Chapter 1272: Progress and Accident

The news of the return of the Immortals spread like wildfire. In this current situation, this matter had received much more attention, with many organizations secretly in awe.

There were tens of millions of Immortal Grade B Supers, and no one could ignore this strength, especially if a few million of them belonged to the Black Star Army. This made many of the large organizations, including the three Universal Civilizations, more vigilant. They were worried that the Black Star Army would take major action after the return of their powerful armed forces.

However, these organizations soon heaved a sigh of relief as they saw the Immortals just going about their daily tasks, without any huge changes in their schedules.

It was just that every time after they disappeared, the strength of these Immortals would grow. This was a law that had been discovered. Many of the top organizations had confirmed this through the intelligence that the Immortals strength was still growing, which led them to feel concerned.

While they were only at the Grade B realm, their strength was already terrifying. Every organization knew that if the Immortals continued to grow, it would inevitably impact the existing universe's structure and produce unknown effects, which was not good.

Furthermore, the current galactic society was now also aware of the Sanctum Revivals, and thus, they unconsciously linked it to the immortal nature of the players.

On the internet, public anger, which had begun to cool down, once again flared up. The galactic residents discussed recent events, giving rise to much speculation. There were rumors that the reason Black Star had mastered the Sanctum Revival was precisely because he discovered some clues from the Immortals.

The speculation was reasonable, and got the widest acceptance, making countless people feel that they had stumbled across the secret of Black Star.

For a period of time, almost all organizations in the universe started to offer more generous conditions for the Immortals, enthusiastic to win them over so as to research the Sanctum Revivals through them.

However, with the lessons learned through the collapse of the Limitless Financial Group, as well as the version name being called Black Star's Era, most players rejected the olive branches that the small and medium sized organizations offered and instead transferred over to the Black Star Army. The army once again ushered in a period of members skyrocketing.

As the saying went, better late than never. Because of certain factors, many players had already missed out several versions with the Black Star Army. Now that the new version had just opened, it was a good opportunity for them to start afresh, and many of them did not wish to throw away this opportunity.

The movements of the players attracted the attention of the entire universe, and countless organizations paid attention to this covetously yet fearfully.

…

In the territory of the Black Star Army, on the rocky, mountain-like surface, two figures were fighting each other at an extreme speed, leaving a series of afterimages. Each of their collisions resulted in a ring of compressed air exploding.

This was a secret training ground hidden on a barren planet.

Bang bang bang!

The two slammed into each other, much like an earth dragon rampaging amid the ground, kicking up choking sand and dust. Their Pugilist auras shot everywhere, exploding rocks and mountains alike.

Suddenly, the figure wearing heavy training armor seemed to have discovered a flaw in the opponent, raising his elbow before condensing his Pugilist flames at the point of contact. This skewed the opponent's defensive posture, and taking advantage of this short opportunity, a sharp leg whip swept across like a tomahawk, creating a sonic boom from the speed alone as it closed the distance to the opponent's chest in the blink of an eye.

Bang!

A silver figure was thrown out like a cannonball, smashing through three mountains before embedding deeply in the fourth. There was a loud bang as the rocks surrounding it crumbled, leaving behind a deep pit filled with smoke and dust.

"…Good fight."

The silver figure shook himself, and the hill was blasted to pieces, turning into a rain of rocks.

He suspended himself in midair, his body akin to flowing mercury. The depression made in his chest was quickly recovering. This person was Silver Shadow.

His opponent did not pursue the attack, taking off his helmet to reveal an honest face. It was none other than Karlot.

Silver Shadow flew in front of Karlot and nodded. "Your progress is getting faster. It has been little more than a year, yet the current you can probably beat three of the you from a year ago. Within the Calamity Grade, your abilities are pretty good."

"Am I that good?" Karlot scratched his head. He was a little embarrassed as he was used to being the worst performing.

"Your Pugilist potential is something I've rarely seen in my life. Given time, I'm sure your achievements will be higher than mine," Silver Shadow said emotionally.

He had suppressed his strength to the Calamity Grade to battle with Karlot, but the latter's performance completely surprised him, giving him immense pressure.

Initially, when Black Star had asked him to come teach Karlot, Silver Shadow was a little unwilling, but after a year of guidance, all negative thoughts had flown out of the window.

Karlot's abilities soared upward at an incredible speed. If he was only an ordinary Calamity Grade in the past, right now, he was near the boss level, and this change only happened within a year!

Silver Shadow could feel a sort of Beyond Grade A potential coming from Karlot, so instead of rejecting his teaching, he instead became even more dedicated, almost unreservedly imparting his Pugilist experiences to Karlot. If Karlot became a Beyond Grade A, it would be a good thing for him too.

Black Star had a wide range of connections and had no shortage of friends who were experts in the Pugilist system. However, he actually gave such a good opportunity to Silver Shadow. Thus, Silver Shadow could not help but feel grateful to Han Xiao, thinking that Black Star was supporting him.

However, Silver Shadow devoted himself to teaching Karlot not just entirely out of goodwill of cultivating a younger generation. He was also extremely compatible with Karlot in terms of personality, and they got along very well.

"It's because you have taught me well." Karlot smiled in an honest manner.

"It's not entirely my credit. You have to thank Black Star as well. His vision is truly too precise, and if he had not taught me how to guide you, I probably would not have a clue." Silver Shadow shook his head.

Because Han Xiao had seen through Karlot's growth mechanism in the interface, he had asked Silver Shadow to conduct targeted training, specifically explaining each Pugilist concept before training at high intensities. The result was that they achieved double the results with half the effort, creating this remarkable achievement of allowing Karlot to improve by leaps and bounds.

According to the original growth trajectory, Karlot was a late bloomer, but the main reason was that he was not clear about his own characteristics, so he could only slowly explore and accumulate, wasting a lot of time. If there was a targeted exercise for him at the very beginning, perhaps Karlot's rise to power would have been much faster.

If they were to compare, Karlot was similar to the famed Hero Guo [1. Guo Jing, also known as Hero Guo, is a fictional character from Jin Yong's novel "Legend of the Condor Heroes"], hiding outstanding talent under his simple and honest appearance. Both of them also did not meet the right teacher at the beginning, wasting too much time. If they had practiced the correct method from the beginning, their combat strength would have long soared and solidified.

Because the interface could list one's advantages and disadvantages, in terms of training, there was no one in the universe more suited for guidance than Han Xiao.

Not only Karlot, but the hundreds of Beyond Grade A seeds who joined the Black Star Army also obtained some guidance, making tremendous progress in their cultivation. All of them had begun to treat Han Xiao as some sort of spiritual mentor.

At this moment, the very person being mentioned appeared beside Karlot and Silver Shadow in a remote projection.

"Your Excellency Black Star."

Silver Shadow and Karlot immediately saluted him.

"How's the training coming along?" Han Xiao smiled.

"He improved once again, and he can even break through my defense now." Silver Shadow let out an appreciative smile.

"Dang, not bad. Keep working, you'll soon step into the Beyond Grade A realm. At that time, I'll find even more teachers for you to keep growing." Han Xiao laughed cheerfully.

He had completely grasped the correct training method Karlot needed. The crucial factor behind [Everlasting Martial Path] was to accumulate Pugilist insight, and a shortcut was to have him interact with many Beyond Grade A pugilists to quickly improve his Pugilist insight. This would allow him to complete the transformation of his talent, allowing him to take the fast track to improving himself.

The moment Karlot reached the Beyond Grade A realm, Han Xiao planned to use his own personal connections to have Beyond Grade A Pugilists guide Karlot and teach him experiences and insights. With Karlot's simple and honest attitude, Han Xiao was sure that his investment would not lose out but rather allow him to earn plenty in return.

After exchanging a few more words, Han Xiao wrapped up the conversation and left.

Karlot exhaled, feeling very heartened inside himself.

In this past year, no matter how busy Black Star was, he would call every ten days or so to inquire about his training progress. He even made a training plan specifically for him and invited Silver Shadow, a Beyond Grade A, to be his teacher. All this had shown the importance Black Star placed in him.

As the saying went, there was no harm without comparison. Thinking back to how the dynasty had treated him, even if Karlot was not a small-minded person, he could not help but feel that both parties were simply not comparable.

The kindness shown to him was firmly engraved in his heart. Even if one removed his idolatry for Black Star, his sense of belonging toward Black Star had already broken through the roof.

Since you treat me like a state scholar, I'll be sure to repay this country with my life!

…

In Black Star Palace's office, Han Xiao shut down the remote projection, smiling brightly.

"Karlot was really worth training. Just a year and his growth is already so high. If we follow this trend, he might even surpass Lothaire and reach the Beyond Grade A realm first."

He could not be more satisfied with Karlot. This guy was indeed the poster boy of the future Pugilist system.

Lothaire was still stuck outside the door of the Beyond Grade A realm. This final step was the most difficult, and it was unknown how long he would take.

On the other hand, Evans had been cultivating diligently for several decades. Because the players were not online, he could not absorb any new abilities. He had only been polishing his core abilities and upgrading his realm. He had finally realized his potential, succeeding in entering the Calamity Grade as well.

Han Xiao was full of expectations for this new 'EsGod'. Since the players had returned, they could finally add some new abilities to Evans.

In addition to these potential stocks, the army had expanded its advanced combatants by many times, hosting a large number of Beyond Grade A seeds, including many talented people worth training.

Oh, that's right, there's still that balding baby Sylvia.

A pity, that with her potential, the most she can reach will probably be the Beyond Grade A realm.

Han Xiao felt that she should actually just remain as the Chief Administrative Official…

Shaking his head, Han Xiao took out the communicator and scanned it.

Right now, the universe is reacting to the players' return, worrying that if they continue to grow, they'll become more lawless, shaking the order of the Galactic Society. It is actually true to think so. The fuse has already been lit.

The ancients used this phrase in the past: a pugilist could use his strength for evil. This trait was perfectly demonstrated by the players; as their strength grew, they became harder to control. This would allow one to understand why the Calamity of the Supers was named thus, which was accurate if looking from the players' perspective.

"The three Universal Civilizations will be moving soon. I keep feeling that something is about to happen."

Han Xiao rubbed his forehead as he frowned.

At this moment, a black flame suddenly appeared in front of his eyes, rapidly expanding into a projection of Oathkeeper's soul.

Han Xiao raised his brows. "Why are you not saying hi? Did you come to me because you've collected another set of keys?"

"Not yet." Oathkeeper's tone was solemn. "Black Star, I have two pieces of bad news for you."

"Oh? Say them."

"There's a traitor that has appeared among the group of avengers, who wishes to sell out the Holy Accord in return for the assistance of an advanced civilization's help to seek revenge."

Han Xiao's expression sank. "How did this happen? Has the news been leaked?"

"Pangon is currently in pursuit of the traitor, and we've managed to intercept the intelligence temporarily."

Han Xiao furrowed his brows. "Then the other bad news?"

"Someone used magic to spy on the Holy Accord. We've traced the source and discovered that it came from the secondary dimensions. Most likely, we've been discovered by some existence hidden in the secondary dimensions, but we're still unclear as to who it is," Oathkeeper said in a heavy tone.

Hearing this, Han Xiao calmly stood up, putting on his cloak.

"Give me the coordinates. I'll go take a look."

Chapter 1273: Traitor

Grains of black sand swirled along with the raging tempest, covering the sky in darkness. This high-speed sandstorm was akin to a grinder that could smash apart steel. It was prevalent on the surface of this barren planet all year round, causing this planet to be unable to give birth to any life.

All of a sudden, blue brilliance flashed in the sandstorm, and a figure appeared out of thin air, falling to the ground.

This person wore a broken mechanical suit and was covered in blood, as if he was seriously injured. He struggled to stand up, raising his hand to eject a thin energy shield to ward off the surrounding high-speed sandstorm.

The next instant, a few rays of light flashed behind him, and Pangon as well as a few other Beyond Grade As quickly surrounded him.

Pangon coldly stared at the person, his tone full of murderous intent.

"Kotlin, you betrayed us!"

This Primordial One named Kotlin gasped for breath as he looked around the people surrounding him. He sadly smiled.

Everyone present was at the Beyond Grade A realm, so the spatial fluctuations and folds left by the teleportation and transitions were all clues for them to track him, leading to his inability to get rid of them. His communicator network was locked by the Mechanics around Pangon, so there was already no way for him to escape.

Pangon's expression was stone cold, as he raised his fist and shouted, "I've said this before. Our principle of action is to not drag Black Star and Holy Accord down in our affairs. For you to try to exchange intelligence on them to the Super Star Cluster Alliance in exchange for assistance has already broken the original agreement. I can only get rid of you!"

He felt heartache yet grateful. Kotlin was a member of the Avengers, so he was saddened that his companion had deviated to another path, but he was also grateful that he managed to discover this before he and the Super Star Cluster Alliance formed deep bonds.

Kotlin exhaled before solemnly speaking. "Pangon, can't you see it. With our meagre manpower, even if we develop ourselves silently for hundreds of years, we basically cannot complete the revenge plan. It is whimsical to hope so without external help. I can't do it just by following you; it's a waste of time!"

Pangon was silent for a moment before resolutely replying, "Even if hope is slim, I will not use this method of betraying Oathkeeper and Black Star. They've carried out the mission of the Holy Accord, reviving us and giving us a second life. You're ungrateful to do so!"

"We're all founders of the Holy Accord, and without our efforts in the early years, how could they be able to grasp the Sanctum Revival method now? I indeed owe Oathkeeper, but for Black Star… heh, he's just an opportunist. How dare he put on a front as though he's our savior? His position now was obtained through us!" Kotlin's eyes flashed, and his attitude remained stubborn.

Another Beyond Grade A by the side coldly said, "Black Star is merely planning for the future of the entire class. While we're not participating in it, we should not try to backstab him or get in his way. You've crossed the line."

Kotlin did not seem to approve as he raged immediately. "What does the bullsh*t class struggle have to do with me‽ I only had one goal from the beginning, and that is to avenge my compatriots! For that, I could give up everything, including my life. This time, I didn't even think about getting back alive! Since there's only one chance for us to undergo the Sanctum Revival, to me, the Holy Accord and Black Star are now useless!

"If they did not affect me, I could have given them face and helped them keep their secret, but Black Star is obviously trying to find ways to coexist peacefully with the three Universal Civilizations, my enemy! In the future, he might even show his loyalty and destroy us! If he dares block my way, he can only scram!"

Hearing this, Pangon and the rest frowned.

The goals of each of the founding Primordial Ones in the Holy Accord were different. Not everyone did this to escape the war, and people such as Pangon and Kotlin wished to leave a lifeline to protect their civilizations one day after the war as assurance.

Pangon shook his head. He felt that there was no point wasting his breath on Kotlin anymore. The guy had been completely corrupted by his hatred, unable to accept any other advice. He just wished to take revenge at all costs.

He did not wish to waste his time by arguing over Kotlin's personal beliefs. He changed the topic and coldly asked, "What benefits did the Super Star Cluster Alliance promise you?"

"We haven't negotiated." Kotlin did not hide anything either.

The secrets such as the way to open the Sanctums as well as the formula for creating the keys were firmly held by Oathkeeper and Black Star, and they had never been disclosed to the other Revivors. Kotlin could only trade a shallow layer of intelligence, such as the composition of the Holy Accord and the private deals between Black Star and the Holy Accord. However, just that was already very valuable.

Before negotiating conditions that fit both parties, Kotlin would naturally remain a stranger to them. It was not the first time he had dealt with such organizations, so he would not reveal his bargaining chips, otherwise he would lose his negotiation value.

Pangon mutely nodded before the Pugilist flames on his body re-ignited. He coldly said, "Alright, there's nothing more to say. I'll send you off personally."

"I never intended to wait for death. If you wish to kill me, then come and try!"

Kotlin burned his life without reserving any, frenziedly exciting his fatigued cells.

The next instant, several silhouettes blurred and smashed into each other.

Boom!

Fierce shock waves swept across the surface, causing the planet to shatter.

In the secondary dimension world, Han Xiao shuttled forward at high speed, jumping through secondary dimensions repeatedly as he headed deep in.

After receiving the news from Oathkeeper, Han Xiao had taken the coordinates and gone straight in to track the peeping Tom.

Over the years, Han Xiao had constructed many new machines, and this mechanical suit he was currently wearing was a model that specifically allowed him to move through the secondary dimensions at high speeds.

As for the traitor on Pangon's side, Han Xiao had no control over him for the time being. Pangon and the others could not take a Throne along as well, so he could not go there even if he wanted to. He could only leave it to Pangon to settle… While this person was a little reckless, his combat strength could not be faulted.

Moreover, none of the revivors knew any key information such as the method to open the Sanctums. Even if intelligence was leaked, the outside world would at most know of the existence of the Holy Accord and his connection with them. Such problems could be controlled, and there might even be advantages among the disadvantages.

The Holy Accord in his past should have met with a similar matter, but the offender was not anyone who was currently a Revivor. In the Calamity of the Supers version during his previous life, Kotlin acted normally, and it seemed that no information about the Holy Accord had been leaked.

"This could be the butterfly effect caused by me. In the past, the Sanctums were not exposed, nor was there an association, so he must've made a different choice."

At this moment, a black flame materialized beside him, which took on the shape of Oathkeeper. As he followed Han Xiao, he spoke.

"Black Star, the problem on Pangon's side has been resolved. The traitor has been killed."

"Quite efficient." Han Xiao nodded. "Did you manage to find out the reason?"

"Oh, Kotlin spoke like this…"

Oathkeeper recounted the incident to him.

Hearing this, Han Xiao silently nodded.

"No wonder…"

This was indeed related to him. In his previous life, the Holy Accord had always kept to the shadows, not participating in these political storms. The Revivors had all maintained a neutral stance in the past, but they had all been converted by Han Xiao to join the Beyond Grade A war. Thus, Kotlin's mentality was altered.

However, this was a rare situation. Basically, the Revivors would not risk leaking any intelligence, as they knew that once the plan of Black Star and the Holy Accord was known, they would be hunted down and might even cost Black Star his life, wasting his 'precious second life'.

People like Kotlin who were ungrateful and did not care about their lives were few. This binding of class interest and the safety of one's life was enough to suppress most of them.

In actual fact, Law and Fay had privately suggested in the past that Oathkeeper use the Soul Flame as a way to seal their mouths. While it might not be a strong restraining factor, it could be used to sense when a Revivor was leaking intelligence. However, this suggestion was rejected by Oathkeeper.

Han Xiao also did not agree with this proposal. It would be easy if things could be that simple… The Holy Accord was able to suppress the second batch of Revivors, mainly because they relied on the support of the Primordial Ones in the first batch. Their identities were people who had originally founded the organization, so if this suggestion was carried out, the nature of the Holy Accord would change, and the Revivors would run away.

Han Xiao shook his head to clear his thoughts. "Traitors are hard to avoid; we just have to be more careful."

"Kotlin was not like this… Sigh, hatred can really change a person completely. The next time we activate a Sanctum, let's not count him in."

"That's only natural." Han Xiao nodded.

The two of them were the only people who knew the true mechanism of the Sanctum Revival function. After this incident, they had removed Kotlin's name from the list, and they would no longer consider reviving him in the future.

This b*stard thought that the revival only worked once, so he felt that the Holy Accord and Black Star were of no use to him, deciding to kick them to the curb since they had outlived their usefulness. As such, Han Xiao decided to grant him his wish, so Kotlin's Sanctum Revival was limited to that once. He would never know what he had missed out on!

At this moment, the built-in secondary dimension coordinate tracker on the mechanical suit pinged.

Han Xiao followed its instructions and jumped through a few more secondary dimensions, after which he broke into the chaotic space stream, moving until he abruptly stopped outside a secondary dimension.

The outer wall of the secondary dimension in front of him was inscribed with countless magic array circuits, which protected the place tightly. This was obviously an artificial transformation, and the coordinates that were given to him also indicated this place.

"… It looks like a dimensional Mage Pagoda at first glance."

Han Xiao carefully scrutinized his surroundings.

Because he possessed the coordinates provided by Oathkeeper, he had arrived very quickly. The Holy Accord had long deployed countless countermeasures against prying eyes. Once someone tried to snoop on them, they would be tracked. The magic and technology involved in this was akin to how one's IP address could be tracked.

Han Xiao flew over and placed a hand on the magic protective shield on the outer wall of the secondary dimension, feeling the strong repulsion. This indicated that the strength of the shield was extremely tough.

"A barrier of this level would only be arranged by a Beyond Grade A, and not just a normal Beyond Grade A…"

Han Xiao secretly nodded to himself, his eyes gleaming.

This meant that it was likely secluded experts within the secondary dimension had known of his presence but did not take the initiative to greet him.

Tsk, were they pretending to be tortoises? Thinking it was safe so long as they remained within their turtle shell?

"It seems like I need to utilize some brute force."

Han Xiao did not plan to use any force, but seeing the other party's attitude, he could not help but raise his palm, a lump of psionic energy gathering.

At this moment, Han Xiao acutely felt the magic barrier of the secondary dimension fluctuate, opening a gap.

Buzz!

The next moment, a figure flew out of the gap, arriving near him. This person wore a platinum and gold mage robe, with a pointy mage hat, and had a long flowing white beard. His appearance was very similar to a famous violent, dual-wielding battle mage.

A mental message surged into Han Xiao's mind. "How do you do, guest from afar?"

Looking over, Han Xiao raised his brows as a look of surprise flashed across his face.

This was simply because he recognized the 'stranger' that he had met for the first time.

Turns out to be this guy… Isn't he the Beyond Grade A in seclusion who fought with the World Tree Army in the secondary dimension during the World Tree War in my previous life?

Chapter 1274: Negotiations

'Mystery Mage' Joey Terrain, a secluded expert who lived in the secondary dimension world, was a person from the same era as the foul-mouthed 'Elf King' Dylan.

There was, however, no such person within the galactic history. He had avoided the universe for a long time without leaving any record. The first time he appeared before the universe in Han Xiao's previous life was during the World Tree invasion.

The Mage class was similar to the Mechanic class in that they grew stronger the more they accumulated and learned. For most, their age was directly correlated to their strength. Having stayed in the secondary dimension world for so many years, Joey had slowly accumulated his knowledge like how water droplets slowly accumulate in a bucket to the point that he had reached the pinnacle Beyond Grade A realm. However, due to a lack of talent, potential, and other factors involved, his level was likely lower than the pillars of each Universal Civilization. He would barely qualify to rank as a top-tier combatant in the universe. If one did not count the Revivors, however, he would definitely occupy a spot as one of the strongest Beyond Grade As in the world.

Han Xiao had a deep impression of him. During the World Tree invasion, the secondary dimension world was reduced to a battlefield, and all the secret organizations and hermits turned into objects of conquest, being bombed out of their hiding places. Unable to remain secluded, they banded together to resist collectively.

Joey was one of them. It was said that because the secondary dimension had received severe damage, he was forced to bring his base with him, employing guerrilla warfare tactics against the World Tree Armies. He was eventually killed and absorbed by the World Tree.

Various knowledge flashed through his mind. Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, sizing up Joey before casually speaking.

"Joey Terrain… I was wondering who it was, but it turned out to be you."

Joey was about to introduce himself, but upon hearing his name being called out, he received a huge shock, surprise showing on his face.

"How did you find out my name‽"

He was a little befuddled in his heart. What sort of situation is this? I've hidden myself for so many years. No one in the main universe should be aware of my name. How did this guy recognize me?

Han Xiao laughed. "I guessed it. Isn't it magical?"

Joey choked at his words, suddenly feeling a wave of depression.

He felt that Black Star's character was a little different from the rumors. Secretly suppressing his depressed feelings, he coughed and said, "Well, whether you guessed it or not, you seem to already know who I am… I'm curious, why has the famous Black Star in the main universe come over to visit my homeland?"

"Oh, so it turns out that you recognize me. I thought you had completely secluded yourself and did not pay any attention to the changes in the main universe." Han Xiao smacked his lips.

"… I just keep an eye on the news every now and then." Joey became more suspicious in his heart, having that nagging feeling that Black Star had a deep understanding of him. However, he had never dealt with the other party before, which made him feel weird.

"Is that so?" Han Xiao did not agree nor disagree with him. "However, not long ago, you spied on my friend's base. It seems like your focus is quite wide, not just about news."

"So, it turns out that you came here for this matter."

Joey came to a realization, his inner bells ringing in warning.

He had only just discovered Black Star in the secondary dimension and wondered why he had come over. He initially only wanted to wait in silence and guess his intentions, but the moment he saw Han Xiao raising his hand to break his magic enchantment, Joey could only come out to meet him.

He did not expect that the random object that caught his curiosity would be related to Black Star. Now, the master had come knocking, likely to seek trouble.

Since the other person came all the way here, they must have had some form of evidence. There was no use trying to hide.

Joey's expression changed.

Seeing this, Han Xiao smiled and said, "As the saying goes, 'a visitor from afar is a guest'. Are you not going to invite me into your secondary dimension to discuss this?"

Joey nodded when he heard those words. He made a gap in the barrier before gesturing Han Xiao in.

"Of course, please follow me."

He led the way as Han Xiao flew into the secondary dimension. The world in front of him suddenly transformed, a peaceful world filled with lush nature coming into view. The huge city guarded a white tower that reached up into the clouds.

Passing by from a high altitude, Han Xiao overlooked the scene on the streets as the residents, who were the size of ants, bustled around. The city atmosphere was harmonious and lively.

The duo landed on the top platform of the tower. Joey lightly snapped his fingers, and two sets of high-end tables and chairs as well as a trolley filled with snacks and tea appeared out of thin air.

Han Xiao smiled by the side and muttered to himself, "Magic is really convenient."

Joey glanced at him, not knowing what to make of his statement, before inviting him to sit. "… Please sit. Try my specialties."

Both of them sat opposite each other.

Han Xiao took a sip of tea, and a strong fragrance swept across him. The tea was mellow yet rich, with a faint milky fragrance and an endless lingering aftertaste.

"Pretty good." Han Xiao placed his teacup down before turning to gaze at the city below, smiling as he spoke. "This secondary dimension is not bad at all. It's been a long time since I've seen such a peaceful place."

"This is the place where I've secluded myself. Everything you see here has been built up by me bit by bit…"

When it came to this topic, Joey's tone got a little warmer, as though he liked to hear others praise his achievements.

Han Xiao listened for a bit, smiling. "It's good to live in seclusion here. You won't feel lonely as well. It seems like you've transformed this into a Mage Pagoda as well. Does this place have a name?"

"Yes, it's called…" Joey suddenly paused for a bit before finishing. "The Kingdom of God".

Hearing this, Han Xiao secretly smirked.

This old man thinks that I don't know this place is actually called the Land of Four Gods and did not say its actual name, afraid that I would guess there are three other Beyond Grade As hidden here.

The three of them hid themselves presumably as trump cards, just in case I create trouble. Then they can catch me off guard.

Han Xiao did not immediately expose the other party, instead changing his tone and replying playfully, "However, I saw that many of the residents here are actually the various galactic races in the main universe. You abducted a lot of people from the main universe to accompany you, right?"

Joey remained unmoved, sipping on his tea as he casually replied, "It's not abduction. The universe is such a dangerous place. I only helped a few of them obtain some stability in their lives. Here, they can enjoy the peace that I created for them without fear. What's wrong with that?"

"Sounds pretty good to me. This might be the life that many people dream of, but… heh." Han Xiao only raised his brows but did not finish his sentence.

Dominating the lives of the ordinary was a matter of course for many of the Beyond Grade As. Regardless of whether the masses were willing to accept the arranged life or not, they had no choice either way. This mentality had long been ingrained among the Supers and could not be separated from power and authority.

Han Xiao did not have much to say about it but instead shook his head secretly in disapproval of Joey's practice.

The Land of Four Gods seemed to be an independent paradise, but Han Xiao knew that under the iron hooves of the World Tree, this fragile peace could not even withstand a single blow from them and would forever be on the run. It was not so easy to remain detached from all worldly affairs.

Han Xiao rapped on the table as he leaned forward, getting into the main topic. "Alright, I've already drank your tea, so let's talk business. The target that you used your spying magic not long before was actually my friend. I would like to have an answer for that."

"What do you intend to do?" Joey inwardly tensed up.

Han Xiao waved his hands in dismissal. "There's nothing about it. I just want to know your motive and objective, as well as how you did it."

"You came in such a hurry. Could it be that the object of my spying is that important to you?" Joey frowned, secretly wondering why Black Star would make such a big move.

Han Xiao blinked as he sized up Joey's expression before laughing.

From these words, he probably understood the details behind Joey. The old man likely did not know the full story behind the Holy Accord, but it was unknown how he managed to find the base of the Holy Accord to spy on. He probably did not have a strong motivation.

Because this guy had secluded himself for too long, he had become easy to read.

"Do you think I have a lot of free time?" Han Xiao turned the question back.

Joey seemed taken aback by this question, "No, with your position and authority, I suppose you must be very busy."

"Then since I'm personally here, do you still need to ask about my attitude toward this?" Han Xiao shook his head, his smile vanishing. "Answer me, I don't wish to repeat myself."

Joey's expression twitched. He was shocked by Han Xiao's brief release of his strength and felt a little unhappy.

It was just that as someone who had hidden himself away, his personality was more pliable, so he suppressed the unhappiness in his heart, replying truthfully.

Han Xiao observed his expression, tone, even actions as he listened to his explanation.

According to Joey, this was a coincidence. He said that he did not know the details of this organization, and the reason for spying was because he discovered the Holy Accord capturing many Primal Esper Entities through his 'messenger', making him curious. He thus marked the very 'concept' of the Holy Accord, such that if there ever came a day where their fate string changed or became entangled with his, then he could observe them. This was a spell he had created during his seclusion.

Not too long ago, he had suddenly had a faint hunch, so he had followed his intuition to observe the situation of this mysterious organization. However, the 'messenger' he sent out was blocked, and he saw nothing.

"You said it was a coincidence?" Han Xiao could not prove otherwise.

Although this sounded unreliable, he could not dismiss it as a lie. The secondary dimension was bizarre, with hidden dragons and crouching tigers. The Holy Accord had organized their secret activities for so many years; it was natural that a slight trace of their activities would be discovered. It was not strange for them to be seen by the experts by accident, but not everyone would be able to find out the details of the organization.

The high-level Mages usually had their own set of secret skills. After spending so many years in seclusion, Joey had also developed his own unique set of spells. According to the intelligence from his previous life, his research mainly concerned the environment in which he was located. His spells were extremely suitable for combat in the secondary dimension. On the contrary, it was unsuitable for combat in the main universe, where his strength would fluctuate.

Han Xiao believed around sixty to seventy percent of what he had said. Not only was he observing the actions of the other party, but he was also basing it on his behavior in his past life. This person was not a guy who liked to snoop around, nor did he work for other organizations. He seemed reliable.

It was precisely because of this that while Han Xiao did not know how much Joey had learned about the Holy Accord, he still stated outright that he was connected to the Holy Accord. This was because the moment he recognized Joey, he changed his initial strategy, planning to pull this man aboard.

Furthermore, Joey also recognized him quickly and was even being compliant. Han Xiao could roughly guess that the other side also wished to side with him in order to enjoy the Sanctum Revival.

All sorts of thoughts flashed through his mind, and since Joey had finished speaking, Han Xiao took the chance to sip on his tea before smiling lightly as he spoke.

"Ok, I'm now clear about this matter. It seems like it was just a coincidence."

"It's good that you're willing to believe in me…"

Joey breathed out a sigh of relief. The reason he tried his best to comply was because he wished to resolve the misunderstanding, not wishing to clash with Black Star.

At this time, Han Xiao's words took a change, and he meaningfully said, "However, this isn't my true objective of coming today. Let's talk about something else… You should be interested in the Sanctum Revivals, right?"

Joey was a little surprised. He did not expect Han Xiao to actually change to this topic. After a brief moment of hesitation, he nodded.

"That's right. I am very interested."

Han Xiao laughed. "If you wish for it, I can also include you."

Joey was dumbstruck.

He originally intended to look for a chance to contact Han Xiao in the future and try to obtain an opportunity to have a Sanctum Revival, but he did not expect it to be so effortless, which made him feel a little lost.

This is the first time we've met, but you're already giving me a chance to revive? Has Black Star always been so generous?

Seeing Joey's expression, Han Xiao immediately knew what he was thinking. He helplessly sighed before saying, "Of course, this chance does not come for free. Right now, the relationship between the association and the three Universal Civilizations is pretty strained, with conflict ready to erupt at any time. I need to enhance the strength of the association, so as long as you join the association and stand on our side, you will have your share in the Sanctum Revival."

Hearing this, Joey hesitated before whispering, "But I have long decided to live in seclusion. Matters of the main universe are not something I wish to interfere in… Can I join in name after the association has reconciled with the three Universal Civilizations?"

"You don't wish to invest anything, but you expect returns. Don't you think this sort of dream is too good to be true?" Han Xiao rolled his eyes as he replied.

For him to even say such nonsensical words, this person really had been in seclusion for too long.

Joey was a little troubled. "Can you change the terms?"

Han Xiao raised his brows in reply. "I don't think you are in any position to bargain. Besides, what do you have that I actually need?"

Joey was speechless.

Han Xiao suddenly stood up and patted his clothes.

"Your hesitation mainly stems from the fact that you do not trust me, so you think that my chances of failure are high. I believe we need to spar for you to understand. How is it? Shall we exchange a few moves?"

"This seems a little too rushed…" Joey had an expression of surprise, but he did not refuse. "That's good as well. I'm curious about your endurance. Let's have a spar outside here."

Black Star had an outstanding reputation, and since Joey had secluded himself for so many years, he also wished to see where he stood against Han Xiao. Making friends through battles had always been standard procedure for the Beyond Grade As.

However, Han Xiao shook his head.

"You're mistaken. I wasn't asking for spar with you one-on-one but with all of you."

As he spoke, he turned away, speaking in another direction.

"The three of you, I believe you have eavesdropped enough. Please come out."

As his voice sounded, three figures appeared a few seconds later. As they landed on the tower, they shared helpless glances.

These were the other three Beyond Grade As of the Land of Four Gods. They thought that Black Star did not discover them, but it turned out that he had known about it a long time ago.

Thinking of this, the trio could not help but feel embarrassed. Hearing how Black Star wished to take four of them at once, they got even unhappier.

"Are you sure you wish to go against all four of us?" Joey frowned, feeling that he was being underestimated.

"That's right, otherwise I believe it will end too soon. There'll be no excitement."

Han Xiao chuckled softly.

He had already prepared himself to fight against all four together. Whoever had the strongest fist would have the most rights, so only when these four were convinced could he then facilitate the negotiations.

"You're too arrogant."

Joey's tone was cold. He might have had a good temper, but he was also somewhat prideful. Being looked down on, his anger also soared.

Seeing their unsatisfied expressions, Han Xiao also wiped his smile off his face, his eyes transmitting electric arcs. His aura gradually rose, and golden Mechanical Force crackled around his body.

A voice laden with energy blasted out from his mouth.

"It is you guys who've stayed hidden for too long. You've already regressed. I don't mind helping you clearly identify whose era it is now!"

Chapter 1275: I'm the True Mechanic Emperor

There was an endless expanse of white, without any matter present. It just resembled a white, blank space.

Suddenly, a blue vortex appeared out of thin air. Han Xiao and the rest flew out of this portal.

Joey sent out a spiritual message. "This is a prototype of a secondary dimension that I've created. Generally, we all spar with each other here to improve ourselves. You have no problem with this, right, Black Star?"

"Sure."

Han Xiao surveyed his surroundings before nodding in assent.

After reaching a consensus to spar, they decided to change the location due to the fear of destroying their own base. Joey opened a portal, leading everyone to his usual training site.

Advanced mages could utilize magic such as fantasy realization to artificially create secondary dimensions. This white world was merely an imperfect prototype, very simple to manufacture.

"While you might wish to fight against all four of us, we will not take advantage of you. At most, all of us will go one after another until one side admits defeat."

Joey snorted as he dropped this sentence. He then rapidly withdrew, his comrades each flying to a corner.

Han Xiao merely smiled without talking, opening up his interface for a glance.

As expected, a notification popped up, telling him that a special mission had been activated. The format was similar to that of the Beyond Grade A Mission Requirements, which was to last for a certain amount of time in battle. The rewards were divided into different levels, with the highest rating allowing him to randomly draw an ability from any of the four, as well as to gain a talent named [Secondary Dimension Adaptor].

This talent would allow him to obtain bonuses based on the environment when fighting in the secondary dimensions, increasing his combat power slightly. It was just a general-purpose talent, but it was better than nothing.

"Heh, would be nice if I could receive such a surprise every time."

Han Xiao smirked.

At this moment, Joey, who had opened up a good distance, finally stopped. He made a few hand seals, levitating before a series of magic circles, which turned into light gates. Countless monsters then surged out, with all sorts of varieties present within the various secondary dimensions.

"You want to compete with me in the Army Style?"

Han Xiao nodded.

The opponent had definitely heard of his reputation, so he would not allow him to close in easily. Thus, they wanted to use the Human Wave Tactic to go against his own Human Wave Tactic.

Joey was not a specialized Summoner, but having lived in the secondary dimension for such a long time, it was unknown how many strange secondary dimension creatures he had already seen, let alone the contracts he had signed. He could summon quite a lot of them, and most of them were very powerful.

Han Xiao guessed the other's thoughts at a glance. He wished to use his solid foundation to fight against him, since he assumed that Han Xiao was lacking in accumulation, having only entered the Beyond Grade A realm relatively recently.

"Fine, I'll play with you."

Han Xiao did not mind. He pulled up his secondary dimension barracks, and the endless mechanical army poured out. Compared to the scattered formations of Joey's monsters, the mechanical army queued up neatly, forming different formations. There was a unique sense of beauty within.

At the same time, he summoned his Divine Mechanical Throne, floating high up in the central area guarded by the machinery, like the commander of an army.

The mechanical army and the summoned monsters grew in volume, the battle line stretching out endlessly to form a confrontation.

While the array of summoned monsters frequently roared and screamed, the mechanical army was on the extreme end, totally silent.

Seeing that both sides had already deployed their troops, Han Xiao waved his hand as he commanded, "Do it."

As soon as he spoke, the mechanical army moved as one.

The heavy machinery vanguards at the forefront immediately raised their shields, advancing neatly forward. As for the long ranged mechanical units at the back, they discharged all their firepower at once. The dense number of psionic energy beams seemed to combine into a curtain of light, directly targeting the summoned monsters. Han Xiao watched as the ranged regiment directly decimated the enemy's lineup, spraying huge pieces of monster carcasses everywhere. In addition, the elite vanguard troops were engaging in three-dimensional combat, acting as independent guerrillas as they sought for opportunities to attack the weakness in the enemy's formation.

At the same time, large swathes of golden lightning chains were emitted from the Divine Mechanical Throne, instantly connecting the various mechanical units, forming a spider web-like shape. The large number of mechanical soldiers dyed with the golden lightning received the buffs of the Mechanical Force, their performance increasing sharply by the naked eyes, as though they had entered a state of excitement.

Joey was unwilling to show weakness. With a wave of his hand, beams of magical lights spilled onto the summoned creatures, which also brought about a state akin to a blessing. The summoned creatures behaved like a flash flood, rushing toward the mechanical army!

While there existed a variety of summons, their formations were not scattered with the blessing from Joey's spells. The different types of summoned creatures formed a formation with complementary abilities and tactical coordination, instead of rushing out as a swarm.

The two waves approached each other quickly, before slamming viciously at each other, akin to a comet smashing against Earth!

Boom!

Chaos broke out in an instant, and the scene blazed up. The teeth of both troops were intertwined with each other, as machinery collided with flesh and blood. They fought tragically, killing each other repeatedly!

However, the moment they collided, the mechanical army gained the upper hand, constantly squeezing the monsters back under their advancement.

"What a powerful mechanical army!"

Joey gulped in shock before hurriedly casting a temporary buff spell to stabilize his frontline troops. He also cast a recovery spell to heal their injuries.

It was a pity that all his efforts came to naught.

The Han Xiao right now was terribly strong, with his additions of God's Trait Transformations, Machinery Faith, Proof of Leadership, and Mechanical Divinity. This gave him overwhelming Mechanical Force strength, which even the Mechanic Emperor could hardly match.

Moreover, his decades of research into Jayz's technological treasures had allowed his Mechanical army to be updated and strengthened many times over. Not only were there many new models of combat machinery, all the machines had their performance raised by several tiers.

Han Xiao's current combat power was probably at the very forefront of the universe. There was no need for him to burst his potential, and he could crush almost anyone in an upright manner.

As for Joey's summoned creatures, they were in no way a match for Han Xiao's mechanical army!

The battlefield quickly turned into a one-sided advantage, where the machinery attacked and retreated as they wished. Their formation remained tight knit as they travelled back and forth, constantly shattering the formations of the summoned monsters, slowly whittling them.

At the rear, Han Xiao remained firmly seated on his Divine Mechanical Throne, adjusting the type of Mechanical Force buffs. He had too much machinery now, and his Mechanical Force was not enough to cover all his troops, so he had to constantly adjust the focus of his buffs manually, using it as a means to control the overall situation and the battlefield.

At the same time, Han Xiao also opened a specific battle formation buff, which was a commanding skill commonly used by the Army Style. There were various combat methods, formations, and tactics existing in the form of different talents and skills, and this was a special command-type skill that provided an overall boost for the army. It would boost all attributes by at most ten percent, which was akin to adding wings to a tiger.

Very quickly, the summoned monster army experienced serious casualties, and Joey felt his heart ache. He raised his hand, drawing mana from the Mage Pagoda floating in the air, before slapping his palm against a portion of the machinery.

Buzz!

A huge golden magic circle akin like a lotus flower spread out, and the area in the mechanical army's location suddenly collapsed. The chaotic space streams raged, but it was only restricted to this circular area.

The mechanical soldiers in the area seemed to have been erased by an eraser, disappearing into thin air in an instant. The soldiers that subsequently entered this area also disappeared into thin air.

Gazing over, Han Xiao's eyes narrowed.

"Instant exile spells are actually being used to serve as traps. This is interesting…"

The disappeared machines were not destroyed but rather exiled by Joey's spells into the chaotic space stream of the secondary dimension world. All of them were split up, so there was no knowing where they would end up. This effect was similar to the Dimensional Exile Bullet that the Holy Accord had, but its effect was better.

This was one of the reasons Joey was so suited to fighting in the secondary dimensions. He had a lot of self-made spells that could only take effect in this place and could not be used in the main universe.

Joey stretched out a few more palms, exiling a few more areas of machinery. At this moment, his senses suddenly rang in warning, and he did not hesitate to activate a short-range teleportation spell, leaving his spot.

Swoosh!

The next moment, a highly concentrated ray blasted over, penetrating the layers of magical barriers he had set up to hit his afterimage.

Flashing to the side, Joey turned to look at the origin of the beam. He discovered that Han Xiao had unknowingly donned a mechanical suit that was dyed black in color. He raised his fingers to point over at him, the fingertips of the mechanical suit still flashing with light.

"You really dodged it fast. I still thought of trying out the actual combat capabilities of this anti-Mage gamma splitting ray."

Han Xiao's tone was a little regretful.

The style of a normal mechanic was to prepare countermeasures against any sort of enemy. In the past few years, Han Xiao had developed a lot of new weapons against the five major classes, changing out his entire equipment set.

This anti-Mage gamma splitting ray was based on a highly concentrated gamma ray cluster imitating a gamma ray burst, supplemented by magic suppression energy through the reverse transformation of Psionic energy. It was hypothesized that when hitting those of the Mage classes, it would then impose a 'magic activity inhibition' state for several hours, greatly weakening the opponent's spells and magics.

Han Xiao shook his head before standing up from his throne and disappearing.

Joey's heart sounded with warning bells, and he immediately sent out a backhand filled with magical power behind him, barely blocking the fist of Han Xiao which jumped out from his Void Hyperdrive.

Boom!

As the hand and fist connected, a shockwave of blue and purple suddenly burst out!

Joey was about to borrow the force to increase the distance between them but discovered to his dismay that his palm was glued to Han Xiao's fist. He saw that Han Xiao's mechanical suit suddenly lit up with fluorescent blue phantom energy patterns, which pulsed like it was breathing.

Joey's expression changed drastically at this moment, as he found out that the mana in his body was to flow into his opponent outside of his will, through their connected hands.

The Psionic energy agglomeration decay module was invented by Han Xiao. By stimulating the process of production and transformation of psionic energy, he was able to create an energy that could engulf all other energies. As long as the judgement requirements were met, it could assimilate and absorb the opponent's energy, turning it into fuel for his energy furnace.

To put it simply, this was akin to the Star Absorbing Great Art[1]!

Joey immediately made a decision, activating an enchantment and producing spatial turbulence, swallowing himself in it and getting rid of his controlled state as he disappeared without a trace.

"Oh, he really has many ways to escape."

Han Xiao's brows furrowed, and he turned his head to survey his surroundings. He saw a blast of chaotic space stream surge out from the extreme end of the battlefield, spitting Joey out. The chaotic space stream that seemed uncontrollable had actually been transformed into his own vehicle.

"Close shave… I lost around five percent of my total mana in just that brief contact." Joey was secretly surprised when he looked into his own status.

This time, the blue lines on Han Xiao's mechanical suit dimmed as he shook his head with a smile.

"It's better for all of you to come at me at once. You alone won't give me any pressure."

Hearing this, Joey's expression sank. The other three by the side did not have good expressions either.

In just that short exchange, Joey had personally experienced Han Xiao's strength. He felt that he had no shortcomings, like an impassable mountain. He could not think of any way to defeat Black Star with just his own abilities.

Since Joey was the strongest out of the four of them, the other three of his comrades were secretly shocked to see his embarrassing performance. Even without going against Black Star, they knew that they would get the same result, or worse.

There was no point sending themselves up for the slaughter one by one!

Cognizant of this, the other three started to be tempted by Han Xiao's suggestion.

Originally, they did not do so because they had to maintain their dignity as Beyond Grade As, but now that they would just be beaten up if they went one by one, it would be better to besiege Black Star and avoid making a fool of themselves.

As for their round robin arrangement at the start… that was what Joey said; it had nothing to do with the thoughts of the other three.

One of them coughed a little before solemnly saying, "Since you so strongly demand it, we cannot refuse your invitation. Let's spar together then!"

Glancing at him, Han Xiao secretly gave a thumbs up.

What a shameless sentence, this has my style all over it. Thumbs up to you!

The three of them no longer watched by the side, joining the battle one after another to showcase their magic.

Seeing this, Joey blushed as he recalled his thoughts before fighting.

However, he knew in his heart that just relying on himself would be a lost cause, so he chose not to reject his comrades' help. He would rather pretend and not say anything, cooperating with them in battle.

The five fought fiercely, clashing and tumbling around, causing the wall of the secondary dimension to tremble constantly. This dimension was not made to withstand the aftermath of their battle and soon became full of holes.

…

This battle lasted for several hours, and they had already cycled through three battlefields, with the fourth secondary dimension they were fighting in on the verge of breaking apart.

There was a huge floating island here, and at this moment, the entire island was stained red with blood, with broken corpses lying everywhere.

On the uneven ground, Joey was leaning on his staff, panting heavily and covered with cuts and bruises.

With horror in his eyes, he tremblingly raised his hand to signal to Han Xiao, hurriedly saying, "I, no, we have lost. Don't come over anymore!"

Not far off, Han Xiao stopped moving, his voice laced with regret. "Just like this? I still have quite a few devices I haven't tested out…"

It had taken him a long time to find such good opponents to spar, so he did not wish to make this battle a quick one. He took out all the equipment he had made in the past few decades to test out, torturing Joey and the others to the point he almost left them with psychological trauma.

This time, because he mainly focused on testing out his equipment, Han Xiao was not too serious in fighting and did not activate any of his aces. Even so, Joey and his gang could not cause him any trouble. The situation was always under his control, a one-sided victory.

He had a slightly clearer understanding of his own strength… If anyone were to fight head-on with him, without a dozen Beyond Grade As with an Energy Rank at 70,000 or above clashing with him, there would basically be no danger to him!

Han Xiao sighed in relief.

"This is not even counted as my warmup. I've given you guys a chance, but you did not use it well."

Hearing this, the four of them were speechless.

If these words were spoken before the fight, they would have been unhappy, but now, they recognized the strength gap between the two sides. Knowing that Black Star could deal with all of them himself, the arrogance in their hearts dissipated.

The Beyond Grade As were realistic. If they could not beat someone, there was nothing they could do but endure it.

However, while Joey and the rest were being tortured by Han Xiao, they also saw the accumulation that Han Xiao showed. They finally understood why Black Star dared to fight against the three Universal Civilizations.

Black Star's mechanical army was simply incredible, his accumulations too terrifying. His mechanical army was practically endless!

The title of 'Mechanic Emperor' obviously belongs to you instead!

[1] This is a reference to the wuxia novel 'The Smiling, Proud Wanderer' Back

Chapter 1276: Achieving Nirvana

"Right now, you guys should be assured of my strength, right?"

Han Xiao snapped his fingers, and the mechanical suit folded and contracted, merging into his body.

Joey took a breath, suppressing his frustration of being beaten up, before seriously speaking.

"… You're indeed the strongest Beyond Grade A I've ever seen, but what you need to do is far from what can be achieved with an individual's power. It may be okay for you to protect yourself, but others don't have your ability. It's too difficult to unite the entire Beyond Grade A class and become a force on par with the three Universal Civilizations!"

"At the core, you're just unwilling to even bear the slightest risk." Han Xiao pursed his lips.

Joey spoke in a low voice. "I witnessed the entire Tragedy of the Pinnacles. The three Universal Civilizations are not doing anything now not because they're really afraid of you. Don't be fooled by the current stalemate. The current strength of the Beyond Grade A Association is not enough to compete against the three Universal Civilizations on the same level, and they're just looking for low-cost solutions to their problems. If they do not care about the consequences, the three Universal Civilizations truly have the power to destroy the current explored universe, turning it into a barren land."

Han Xiao lightly shook his head. "Spare me your alarmist talk. Unless the three Universal Civilizations go crazy, this sort of situation will never occur. Thus, your assumption is meaningless. Who would ask to be euthanized after getting a slight cold or flu? The most suitable option for us right now is to fight for peace."

"The three Universal Civilizations allow Beyond Grade As to exist, but they do not want us to unite…" Joey hesitated before tentatively saying, "Since you've mastered this precious Sanctum Revival technique, why do you have to use it to carry out such a dangerous business? With your strength, you can be completely independent, treating the Sanctum Revival as a form of business. You can cooperate with the three Universal Civilizations and the various Beyond Grade As. In any case, the Sanctum Revival is only limited to one time, so everyone can be satisfied!"

Han Xiao stared at him for a while before speaking calmly. "Everyone has their own goals and ambitions."

He did not think it surprising that Joey would have this mentality. Most of the hermits preferred to be alone, but they still wished to enjoy the benefits of the Sanctum Revival, without the risk of any danger.

"Is there really no way around this?" Joey appeared a little disappointed. After hiding for so many years, he did not wish to expose himself to the eyes of the advanced civilizations.

Han Xiao waved his hands without answering. His intention was obvious.

Joey paused for a while but did not give up, trying to persuade Han Xiao further.

"Black Star, if the three Universal Civilizations really manage to obtain the Sanctum Revival technology, then that will be the day they take action. The three Universal Civilizations will definitely try to monopolize this technology and will attempt to neutralize this advantage of the association. The three Universal Civilizations just have to get rid of you and then revive you before anyone else does in order to not be challenged any more… I feel that you should stop walking down this path."

Han Xiao frowned and spoke in a slightly offended tone.

"Do I need you to remind me of such things? You might think that it would be safer to join the three Universal Civilizations after they have mastered the technology, but think about it. The three Universal Civilizations' target of revival will not be as loose as ours. They will not think much of Beyond Grade As after gaining this huge weapon, so Beyond Grade As will only become a tool for them to unify, and if they are unwilling to become tools, then they will not be able to enjoy the benefit that is the Sanctum Revival.

"Why else do you think the association is resisting? Only when we exist can the Beyond Grade As still achieve the maximum freedom. If you don't choose to bet and contribute your strength now, how long will you wait? To have to constantly look forward and backward, afraid of this and that, don't be naïve. There's no surefire method to win. If you have a need for the Sanctum Revival, then you have to give something up. If you're not interested, then stop wasting my time and continue your own escape from reality. Obediently stay out of the way until the end of your life."

Joey's expression was twisted, his emotions tangled, as he dully replied, "I did not mean that. Could you give us some time to consider instead…"

Hearing this, Han Xiao no longer made any noise but took out a few secure communicators, throwing them toward the four. "This can allow you to connect to me directly. If you make up your mind, inform me. Right now, the situation is still stable, so you have a lot of time to consider. I hope to get a satisfactory answer. If you only choose to continuously shy away from the changes of the times, in the end, you can only passively accept the final results. If you don't fight and pay for yourself, who else can you count on?"

Finished, Han Xiao waved his hand, recovering his army into the secondary dimensional army box before disappearing in place with a single teleport. He had no intention of returning to the Land of Four Gods as a guest.

Seeing this, Joey and his party could not help but stare at each other. After a long while, one of them said, "Is Black Star fed up with us?"

"Seems that way… Joey, you seem to have annoyed him."

"He wouldn't be offended, right?"

The four of them were concerned about their gains and losses.

Their feelings were very complicated. On one hand, they wished to avoid all risks, tagging behind Black Star to ask until they were confident that it was completely safe, but they were also worried that this sort of questioning would make him unhappy.

This was especially so since they had just seen the opponent's combat power. They subconsciously shrank back at the mere thought.

Joey gripped the communicator and helplessly said, "Black Star is right. My request might be too much… Let's discuss it ourselves first. We shall not disturb him."

…

His vision blurred, and Han Xiao was teleported back to his office in Black Star Palace. He took off his mechanical suit, sighing.

"My trip was worthwhile… I just don't know if they will agree."

Stroking his chin, Han Xiao felt curious.

He had a lot of experience in interacting with Beyond Grade As. With such people who had no ambition or motivation, rather than settling things amicably, it was better to show off his strength and influence.

These people had stayed away from the world for too long a period and had no ambition. They were soft tempered, and trying to persuade them with nice ways would take double the work to achieve half the effort. On the contrary, a person with strong authority would instill a psychological tendency to make up their minds and settle on a decision in them.

He knew Joey well, that this person was the type that would only regret when things were too late. He was an indecisive person, so it would be basically impossible to convince the other party to join the association on the spot. Even if the discussion went well, the other party would hesitate and ask many questions. Instead, it would be better for him to develop a tough attitude, rule over their tendencies and let them worry about their own personal gains and losses themselves.

After all, the association was full of talents, and there was no urgent need for the four of them to join. He was not begging them; it was rather the other way around.

Han Xiao himself did not fancy the strength of the four but their identities.

"If they are willing to join, then this will indirectly send a signal to all the recluses in the secondary dimensions. Perhaps they will lead us to find more secluded hermits, increasing the momentum of the association."

In his opinion, succeeding in this was a good thing, but it would not be much of a pity if he failed.

Han Xiao didn't take this matter to heart, turning his head and opening his interface to turn in his mission.

_____________________

You have received 65 billion experience.

You have received the talent 'Secondary Dimension Adaptor'!

Secondary Dimension Adaptor: When battling in the secondary dimension world, you will gain bonuses of 3 – 6% in Attack, Resistance, Ability Strengthening, and all Attributes. This effect also applies to mechanical soldiers, summons, and subsidiaries.

_____________________

"The effect is not bad. Three percent is better than nothing."

Han Xiao nodded, just focusing on the lower limit of the stat boost.

A prompt also appeared, asking him to select a subject to extract an ability from.

Recalling his combat information, of the four of them, there were two Mages, a Psychic, and a Pugilist. Their Molding Talents likely fitted with their own Classes, so it was impossible to obtain. He simply chose Joey as his target to obtain an Intellect talent.

_____________________

You have received the reward: Randomly draw an ability from Joey Terrain (Talent/Ability).

Remark: Joey Terrain is a Mage, not suitable for your Class, so the extracted skills will be appropriately adjusted.

Randomizing… complete!

Please select one from the five options below as the reward.

Melee Mastery - Talent: +1 Melee skills Level, +25% Melee attack power, +25% Melee attack frequency, +20% Melee parry rate. (As a qualified combat mage, it is reasonable to be good at melee)

Aura Wave—General Version - Ability: The commonly seen Super skill, by compressing one's energy in the body then releasing it as a shock wave. The lethality is low, but it will give various negative statuses depending on one's Energy Attribute. If one's Class is a Pugilist, it will automatically be replaced by the Pugilist's Shockwave Blast skill. Cooldown: 24s. Consumes 120 Energy.

Multiple Staff Strikes - Ability: When using a stick-based weapon (such as a Staff), you are able to unleash a continuous attack in an instant, gaining an extra 6 – 12% attack power bonus. The number of attacks depends on your DEX attribute, with a maximum of 12 times. Cooldown: 44s. Consumes 80 Energy and 270 Stamina.

Crisis Intuition - Talent: When you're about to be attacked, you will receive a strong alert.

The Ancient Ones - Talent: A long life brings about precious spiritual wealth. +20% INT, +10% MYS, +2 all skill Levels.

_____________________

"This…"

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. He did not know what to choose.

[The Ancient Ones], why is it always you?

This talent keeps popping out. Just how much does it love me?

Do you really want me to become an 'ancient one'‽

Han Xiao glanced at the other options but only felt that they were too offensive. He almost wanted to curse out at the fact that a mage could possess the talent [Melee Mastery], totally not respecting the fact that they were a paper Class!

The five options were a jumbled mess, and there was no need to hesitate in his choice.

_____________________

You have chosen the talent [The Ancient Ones]!

_____________________

A wave of coolness spread through his mind, and Han Xiao felt revitalized. He could feel that his thought processes had become a lot quicker, as though he had been through a comfortable massage.

Compared to the four hermits, this talent was his biggest gain in this trip. Finally, he managed to obtain a positive fate with [The Ancient Ones] talent, which he had missed out on many times.

This time, he no longer needed the Old Man Manison's Character Summon Card to reach the power of his explosive state.

Moreover, the Character Summon Card would still be useful. This would be similar to having double Perfect Mechanical Sense, having multiple The Ancient Ones stacked…

"Yo, I've gained quite a bit."

Han Xiao had an expression of happiness as he switched off his interface and sent a message to Oathkeeper, telling him the problem was solved.

Kotlin and Joey both gave him a slight surprise, but there was no danger in the end. Everything was handled smoothly without anything being revealed.

However, this also caused him to have a sense of urgency.

"The longer I wait, the easier it is for such accidents to happen. I need to speed up the efficiency of harvesting experience…"

Han Xiao took a look at the movements of the army players before opening the book titled 'Cultivation of Leeks'…

"Right now, the scale of players is too big. There are no big movements in the army, and the daily missions are also limited. It will not be easy for players to gain experience… It seems that the best method would be to scatter some 'fertilizer' to create more jobs for the players, accelerating their acquisition of experience. At the same time, I probably have to improve the internal welfare system of the army to better harvest their labor output…"

Chapter 1277: Continuous Benefits, Leek Harvesting Skill

In a certain part of the Flickering World, a spaceship with the Black Star Army emblem was slowly moving.

In the cabin, a group of players were busy with their own affairs. Some were playing cards, some browsing the forums, others browsing the army shop. The IDs above their heads showcased that they were all from the Rivervale Guild. Frenzied Sword and Maple Moon were among them. This spaceship held the core members of the guild as they were going toward a mission location.

At this moment, in a corner of the spaceship, Frenzied Sword was lecturing the team members.

"After coming online, we have not been training diligently. We've yet to get back to our peak state. While we're currently travelling, we should not waste time and engage in entertainment before we arrive at our destination. Let's all go through a dungeon copy and practice our tactical coordination."

As he spoke, Frenzied Sword pulled out a few Nightmare-level Dungeon Crystals from his inventory.

Seeing this, everyone could not help but sigh.

"Captain, how long has it been since the previous Pro League? We have yet to get a good rest, and you already want us to start practicing like that now? It's still early before the next league!" Maple Moon complained.

Frenzied Sword patiently explained, "With King Admiral from Dynasty and Sleepy Winter from Long Sky retiring, their teams will have new players and thus need to break in the coordination. Their strength will likely weaken, so our competitiveness will be even more obvious. This is a great chance for us to win the championship once again. We'll need to work harder."

"… I feel like you're becoming like Hao Tian, only knowing how to grill us daily." Maple Moon pursed her lips.

By the side, Bun-Hit-Dog snickered. "After all, he is the captain. Rivervale has lived up to its expectations to achieve good results, and credit is inseparable from his own serious responsibility. I still remember that in the first Pro League, Rivervale was a disgrace, but luckily, the superiors of Rivervale put Frenzied Sword as the cornerstone, allowing him to reform the team. Facts have proved that your club invested in the right people, with Rivervale now having the reputation of a top-five club in China."

Frenzied Sword felt comfortable hearing himself get praised. He raised his thumb up. "Nice words. I'll agree to an exclusive interview."

"Alright, I have some goods now. This trip was not waste." Bun-Hit-Dog laughed.

This group was still joking around when the President of Rivervale club, 'Moon of Thousand Rivers', walked in, approaching Frenzied Sword.

"Frenzied Sword, another NPC organization contacted me. They wish to poach us from the army."

"Again? Who is it this time?" Frenzied Sword was curious.

"It's people from the Federation of Light." Moon of Thousand Rivers was a little helpless.

Recently, they had received many such private solicitations. There were all kinds of organizations involved and they all were offering generous conditions, with the hope that their club would pull out their roots and leave the army. It was not just Rivervale; all the affiliated guilds to the Black Star Army were experiencing such things.

"The Federation of Light wants to rope us in? Since when did our ranking become so huge…" Federation of Light murmured. "Don't worry about it, we're not planning to switch factions anyways."

He was a hardcore supporter of the army, so even if the three Universal Civilizations wished to poach him, he was not interested in jumping ships. As far as he knew, most of the guilds in the army shared the same attitude, not liking such poaching tactics.

"Recently, all the major galactic organizations have been trying to poach players from the army. This intensity is greater than in previous versions. During this period, I've analyzed the current situation, and it is estimated that the war between the galactic civilizations and the association is inevitable. Thus, we 'Immortals' are the most suitable to be used for attacking, becoming the sweet pastry that all sides want to fight for. Otherwise, why would organizations on the level of the three Universal Civilizations specially send people to win us over?" Maple Moon thoughtfully said. While she had become a professional player, she still retained the same interest in analyzing the storyline.

At this moment, everyone's communicators rang with the notification tone reserved for the army's internal message.

"What's this new announcement from the army?"

Taking out their communicators, Frenzied Sword and the rest opened the intranet. An internal document titled 'Recent System Reform of the Army' came into their sights.

Everyone quickly browsed through it, and their expressions changed to joy.

According to the announcement, the army had expanded the type of available positions for the Immortals, opening up more middle-tier positions and long-term official positions such as in logistics, instructors, captains, intelligence officers, and more.

To put it simply, they just opened up more channels for the players to be promoted. Originally, the players were only assigned mercenary and combatant roles, but now they could become part of the middle-tier officers in various departments, gaining power and leading a group of subordinates or commanding a group as their player identities. This appealed toward the players that loved to role play.

At the same time, such a position also represented formally entering the organization, which allowed them to receive a fixed salary from the army. This was also in line with the preferences of the Chinese players.

The requirements for promotion were to have a sufficiently high level of Faction Authority, which depended on one's accumulation Contribution Points, as well as a purchase of a digital qualification certification named 'Army Officer Registration Application Form'. The purchase required only a few Enas and experience points, and they would then await the review of the various personnel in each department.

In addition, the army also released at the request of their members a new insurance service, named 'Army's Specialized Protection Scheme'. This gave them faction store discounts, free medical treatments, equipment repairs, enhancements, and free logistical services. Depending on their protection level, they could obtain various welfare guarantees such as loan qualifications, lower interest rates, lower renting costs, and so on.

Those members with a higher authority would be able to purchase more advance protections, but this was not a one-time cost. They required the player to renew it at regular intervals. However, the benefit of discounts was enough to stimulate the players to purchase this Specialized Protection. Not to mention the special services, one just had to look at it to know that they would make a killing!

This was especially so for the price of Dungeon Crystals, which had been reduced the most. They were currently the main source of experience for the players. It was akin to an inexhaustible vein of 'experience ore mineral', and the players were akin to the miners.

Adding on to this, the army also stated that they would increase the range of missions that Immortals could accept, as well as setting up special missions with rich rewards. The players would need to spend experience points and a certain amount of money as a 'mission deposit'. The money would be returned upon completion but not the experience.

However, players would not care about this paltry amount of experience when they were being given missions. With the huge size of the army, the daily amount of disposable experience earned would be astronomical. With his experience quota being allocated to players through quests, Han Xiao then harvested that experience from the players, maintaining this positive cycle.

Han Xiao also put in the announcement that the Evolution Cube was now eligible to be used, requiring players to spend money and experience to purchase usages.

Because the players would only be able to reach level 160 in this version, the extra Race Evolution chance offered by the Evolution Cube would be useful, and the demand would not be too low.

Han Xiao was not just aiming at earning experience; he also planned to utilize the side effects of the Evolution Cube to curb the players' speed of levelling so that the Calamity Grade players would appear at a later date.

During the side effect duration, many of them would feel that upgrading themselves would be a loss, so they would spend their experience elsewhere, so this could kill two birds with one stone, delaying plus conveniently letting him harvest them more.

After reading the announcement, Frenzied Sword and the others were stunned by this series of favorable policy changes.

"The army is probably sending out a response to the poaching of other organizations."

"Indeed, the factions must fight before we will get enough to eat."

"That's great. Blackie values us like always."

Frenzied Sword and company were overjoyed.

Most of the players had a close relationship with the army, akin to husband and wife. They did not wish to leave and did not expect any reaction from the army, but the latter actually responded with a series of benefits in response to the poaching, which made them feel wanted and happy.

The last part of the announcement was about a military exercise that would be held among the Immortals. The reward for this mission would be extremely rich, but quotas were limited, and the mission could only be undertaken by experience points.

This would be the only large-scale collective operation of the army in the near future. While this was only an exercise, the reward for this mission was extremely rich. Naturally, Frenzied Sword and the others did not hesitate to pay their experience to register.

In just five minutes, the hundreds of thousands of openings were cleanly robbed, which showed just how popular the army was.

The welfare announcement of the Black Star Army caused stomach ulcers in the players of other organizations. Their eyes were green with envy, and there were many complaints on the forums.

Han Xiao could guess the players' reaction to these benefits even without paying attention. He had long mastered the G spot for the players, and this kind of harvesting means could be done with his eyes closed.

According to his estimates, this wave of harvesting should allow him to make up the amount needed to reach level 360 a few months in advance.

…

"Your Excellency President, our plan to win over the Immortals has had little effect. Few of the immortals from the Black Star Army are willing to change factions."

"… What a bunch of troublesome guys."

Hearing the report in the President's Office, Louis frowned.

In order to study the Sanctum Revival phenomenon, the major galactic organizations were vigorously trying to attract Immortals to their cause. However, the movement of the Immortals showed that there was a higher tendency for them to gather around the Black Star Army than around them, which could not be explained.

They thought that using the name of the three Universal Civilizations as well as the large benefits would attract a lot of Immortals, but it turned out that there were not many people who bought into this.

He naturally did not know of the existence of the version name 'Black Star's Era', so he would not know how much this name had helped Han Xiao.

Louis frowned and pondered for a bit before replying in a deep voice.

"This could be the influence of the Scattered Stars Return event… It has been a year, but the effect of it has actually not dissipated. Just in this year, the number of Supers that have gone under the wings of the Beyond Grade As are too many…"

He could not help sighing, feeling that it was a pity.

If not for the Super Star Cluster Alliance, the interception and killing of hundreds of Beyond Grade A seeds would have been successful. If the Scattered Stars Return event did not occur, their method of killing the chickens to warn the monkeys would have been effective. The negativity as a result of the assassinations would have made Supers more likely to compromise with the three Universal Civilizations… but this could only remain a fantasy.

The Chief Elder paused on his crutches before slowly saying, "This situation needs to be dealt with further. After a year of preparation, it is almost time for sanctions to be issued. The Beyond Grade A organizations will no longer be so comfortable. If we're always trying to be scrupulous and openly creating contradictions, they will only continue developing."

Louis nodded as well. "I really have to curb their momentum of development… I'll talk to the church and the dynasty. I want to see how the Beyond Grade A Association can continue to grow when they are blocked by the entire galactic society!"

Chapter 1278: Sanctions

The Black Star Army held a six-day military exercise exclusively for the Immortals within the territory, with the participation of millions of army players confronting each other.

The original intention was to hold a large-scale collection action for players as a reason to issue large-scale experience rewards, but given the sensitive situation, the military exercises of the army were interpreted differently by the outside world.

On the quantum network, many of the galactic residents believed that the army's military exercise was an indirect demonstration to the three Universal Civilizations. Many of them believed that the Black Star Army was warming up, preparing for major action in the near future.

However, even if rumors raged, the Beyond Grade A Association remained silent, allowing the universe to continue their guessing.

After around half a month, just as the public opinion started to die down, an unexpected event happened suddenly, with almost no warning. The three Universal Civilizations jointly released a top level decree for the entire universe, of which the content was to activate sanctions against the Beyond Grade A Association!

The Beyond Grade A Association and the three Universal Civilizations had been fighting in secret for more than a year. While many of the galactic residents were simply watching the show, in public, neither side had ever openly challenged the other.

But right now, the three Universal Civilizations actually tore apart this facade, which was beyond the expectations of most people, yet at the same time reasonable.

Countless organizations' heads saw the contents of the decree, and their pupils needled. They were startled by the harsh sanction, and everyone thought the same thing in their mind.

How vicious!

The three Universal Civilizations finally utilized their political and economic influence that had permeated throughout the universe, beginning a blockade against them.

…

In the Army Commander's private workshop, Han Xiao was concentrating on studying a Gold Grade blueprint, working hard toward achieving the pinnacle of his God's Trait Transformation—Void.

Suddenly, Phillip popped up, his little face full of anxiety. He hurriedly shouted, "Master, hum… something big has happened! The three Universal Civilizations have issued joint sanctions against us!"

Hearing this, Han Xiao's eyes flashed, and he put down the document. With two fingers, he squeezed on Phillip's head and brought him to eye level.

"The day has still arrived… Speak, what sorts of terms did the three Universal Civilizations issue?"

"Look at this, it's so scary, hum!"

Phillip waved his little hand, and a virtual screen unfurled like a scroll. It revealed a densely packed document bearing the joint seals and signatures of the three Universal Civilizations at the bottom, proving that this was a valid decree that had been certified by the three Universal Civilizations. There was also a special note stating that the decree was effective at the date of signing.

Han Xiao read from start to end, and the beginning was a statement from the three Universal Civilizations, explaining their reasons for issuing this decree.

"In order to minimize the danger of an individual's strength to the galactic civilization, the Ultimate Knowledges of each Super system have always been jointly controlled by the three Universal Civilizations, and other organizations cannot spread it at will. This is the requirement of the sixth section of the 'Galactic Superpower Management Act: Knowledge Dissemination Agreement'. The Beyond Grade A Association (hereinafter referred to as the 'Association') has not obtained our permission but has been privately disseminating the Ultimate Knowledge of various Classes for many years. We have repeatedly asked the Association to rectify this, but they have ignored our requests many times. A year ago, our side issued a final notice to the Association, yet it was ignored. Thus, we have decided to impose sanctions in view of their negative behavior."

"Humph, they indeed resorted to such an excuse. I thought the three Universal Civilizations might have something new up their sleeves."

Han Xiao did not find this a surprise at all. He lightly snorted before reading onward.

In the document, the three Universal Civilizations righteously accused the association of violating the rules, extensively citing the regulations they flouted. Then they emphasized that the nature of the association was non-governmental, and thus, it was not affected by the Peace Treaty or other galactic civilization protection agreement.

This was followed by the three Universal Civilizations declaring that the Beyond Grade A Association would now be included in the list of 'Unreliable Civil Organizations' as well as the list of 'Malicious Armed Organizations'.

These two lists were specially set up for some organizations with a doubtful business nature. While they were not as serious as wanted warrants, as long as one was included in the list, all their rights in the Galactic Society would be greatly affected, similar to having low credit ratings or being a deadbeat.

As for the Beyond Grade A Association, their sanctions encompassed a wide range of areas including politics, economy, and the scale of their armed forces.

In terms of politics and governance, most Beyond Grade As usually took care of their own parent civilization, and this decree required that the Beyond Grade A organizations were to stay out of the politics of their own civilization. Otherwise, the rights of the related civilizations would be downgraded. They stated a list of key planets under review, including Planet Aquamarine.

Those Beyond Grade A organizations that were part of a civilization were all subject to some restrictions. It was claimed that the Beyond Grade A had some sort of 'unreliable cooperative relationship' with them. Psyker's Star Pupil Civilization was an example.

In the area of economics, the terms were much more complicated and cumbersome, occupying half of the content and encompassing all areas.

The first was a notice to the various regional civilizations, requesting them to cooperate with their orders and stop any form of cooperation with the Beyond Grade A organizations. They also would not provide public services such as stargate transportation to the Beyond Grade A organizations and would not open any trading channels to the Beyond Grade A organizations. Any existing resources of the Beyond Grade A organizations left in the civilization would at the same time undergo multiple checks, otherwise they would be personally questioned.

In the private sector, any consortium or enterprise that maintained business dealings with the Beyond Grade A Associations would have their Credibility Points downgraded in the Galactic Civilization Bank. Consortiums that had not corrected themselves would then be included in the list of untrustworthy enterprises. Only when their relationship was terminated would they be subjected to a review, restoring their credit, and they might even obtain certain subsidies. The three Universal Civilizations would protect the companies from threat of force by the Beyond Grade A Association, and they would also provide any judicial assistance in the violation of commercial contracts. There would be no need to pay compensation to the Beyond Grade A organizations.

The Credibility Points for all Beyond Grade A Organizations would be lowered, every fund transfer reviewed and supervised.

Other than these main points, there were also many miscellaneous provisions. The three Universal Civilizations had also attacked their allies this time, but since many of them did not follow them blindly, this was also something they had predicted.

At the end of the document, the three Universal Civilizations stated that the above terms were only for members of the Beyond Grade A Association and did not involve the neutral Beyond Grade As. As long as they withdrew from the association and were re-examined, normal treatment would be restored. As for the ordinary Supers, if they were willing to switch to the three Universal Civilizations or local civilizations, they would not only restore their credit but also enjoy more benefits and subsidies.

Throughout the decree, Han Xiao only had one thought.

How domineering!

Han Xiao shook his head.

Tsk, the three Universal Civilizations are really ruthless.

These clauses simply used their power to entrap the galactic society and block the association, so as to curb their development. It had little impact on the Beyond Grade As but was lethal to their organizations.

If one were to sum up the practices of the three Universal Civilizations, it would be understood as… 'Football certifications, evidence, sponsors, and organizers of the match all belong to me. What are you going to use to fight against me‽'

I made this hypothesis many years ago, and alas, it still came true.

Han Xiao had long been mentally prepared for this. It was not surprising for them to come out with this measure, and since the three Universal Civilizations dared formulate such a clause, they were naturally confident in implementing it.

Even the Super Star Cluster Alliance did not face such ruthless measures. After all, they were also part of the Peace Treaty, and hence, they were afforded some form of civilization guarantee. The three Universal Civilizations would only be seeking trouble if they dared to violate those regulations. However, the Beyond Grade A Association was a non-governmental organization, not authoritative and thus not protected by any civilization guarantee agreements.

Since the development of Galactic Society, the three Universal Civilizations had long held hegemony in the financial, political, technological, and military sectors. Their influence radiated in all fields and was deeply tied to all civilizations at all levels. Seeking advantages and avoiding disadvantages was an inevitable tendency for most civilizations, so Han Xiao could foresee that there would be many civilizations acting in response to this decree.

As for the civil organizations and the general public, those who dared to oppose the rulers of the universe were a minority. After all, the majority only wanted a decent job. If they tried anything funny and became marginalized in society, that would be too depressing.

"The three Universal Civilizations hesitated for a year but finally decided to bring this conflict to the surface. I don't know if the players themselves have influenced it… but starting from this decree, the three Universal Civilizations have finally torn off all pretenses with us."

The three Universal Civilizations dropping these sanctions were within his expectation, but even if he had predicted it, there was no good way to resolve them. However, in recent years, he had been committed to improving the independence of his consortium and had secretly made a lot of preparations in order to deal with this risk.

Beep beep!

Right at this moment, his communicator rang.

Han Xiao opened it and saw that it was Bennett calling.

Just as the communication was formed, Bennett immediately asked, "Black Star, have you seen the sanctions imposed by the three Universal Civilizations?"

"Yes." Han Xiao nodded.

He then sized Bennett up.

After replenishing his vitality, Bennett's life span had been extended by a lot. Even decades later, he was still alive, his bones still strong.

Every year, Han Xiao thought that this fellow was going to die, but Bennett would always jump out and shout, "I'm not dead yet!"

Following this trend, it seems like Nero would become a hundred-year-old prince.

"What do you intend to do?" Bennett was full of worry.

"Take it as it comes." Han Xiao waved his hands and raised his brows. "Rather than me, it's Planet Aquamarine that also falls within the scope. What are you going to do?"

Bennett gritted his teeth, solemnly saying, "After a while, our Planet Aquamarine will pull out from the Shattered Star Ring Civilization Conference, signaling that we are unwilling to accept such an arrangement!"

"You wish to accompany me to walk this treacherous path?" Han Xiao laughed.

Bennett had an expression of seriousness. "While Planet Aquamarine is still very weak, we also have our own dignity. We will not deny the great men in the history of our civilization because of such unreasonable demands!"

Han Xiao felt a little touched and warmly replied, "Hearing this, I feel your sincerity. Planet Aquamarine's short-term development might be severely set back, but with my protection, you will not be in any danger. What you lose now will be earned back in the future."

"It's enough with your guarantee. I know I can believe you." Bennett nodded, disengaging the communication.

Han Xiao exhaled, thought for a while, and turned to contact Kasuyi.

Very quickly, Kasuyi's projection appeared on the screen with a solemn expression.

"Black Star, I've read the news. Do you have a plan?"

Stroking his chin, Han Xiao slowly said, "The three Universal Civilizations are doing this, so we have no need to be polite. Hold an emergency meeting. I have two things to announce."

"Which two things?"

"Firstly, from now on, the association will not accept any form of help from the three Universal Civilizations. Secondly, we will also stop subsidizing the associations' direct Beyond Grade A members, freezing their membership at the same time. This will temporarily deprive them of the right to participate in our regular meetings. We will tell the universe that unless the three Universal Civilizations revoke the sanctions, this situation will continue."

Kasuyi frowned. "This will not hurt or itch the three Universal Civilizations at all. At most, it will display our unwillingness to retreat."

"That's enough. If it was so easy to resolve the sanctions, the three Universal Civilizations would have been ruling for so many years for nothing." Han Xiao was nonchalant. "The cooperation with the civilization officials has always been an important point for many of the Beyond Grade As, and now that this channel has been cut off, what's left will be obtaining resources from the Galactic Black Market. The three Universal Civilizations will definitely focus on this field, and friction will be inevitable."

Han Xiao paused.

"Also, we might need to contact the Super Star Cluster Alliance now…"

There was no such thing as permanent enemies, only permanent benefits. He did not wish to help the Super Star Cluster rebel, but a simple deal was worth considering.

His goal was only to control the intensity of the Calamity of the Supers, stabilizing the situation, but he also knew that it was impossible for things to constantly be peaceful. The three Universal Civilizations would not give up, and the checks and balances would always go on. Even if he sought stability, he had to first show off his teeth and claws.

Chapter 1279: Meetings and Backups

In a few days, the sanctions of the three Universal Civilizations directly caused the public opinion of the entire galactic society to explode, be it ordinary people, Supers, civilizations, or non-governmental organizations!

The Beyond Grade A Association had partners in practically all fields, so these sanctions were too far-reaching, involving almost all aspects of Galactic Society. It was no exaggeration to say that this would affect the entire workings of the universe!

Because the three Universal Civilizations had already ruled for many years as defenders of order, it was inevitable that they would gradually become rotten and conservative. Many people's fear of the three Universal Civilizations stemmed more from their dominance and great power, but they had gradually forgotten their ferocity. This decree had now re-awakened the dusty memories of the many civilizations in history, and they remembered the bloody history of the three Universal Civilizations.

In the eyes of many civilizations, the three Universal Civilizations seemed to be wiping away the rust on their bodies, slowly regaining the cruelty they displayed eons ago. Many were secretly worried, not knowing how much of their edge the three Universal Civilizations would recover.

Public opinion was the rifest on the quantum network, and many of the Supers were in an uproar. They expressed extreme resentment toward this decree and felt that the excuse for sanctions used by the three Universal Civilizations was simple cr*p.

In their view, the association had not done anything heinous. The motive of the three Universal Civilizations was simply their need for control. This caused many of the Supers to feel extremely disgusted, thinking that it was a violation of freedom for the Supers.

For a period of time, the association's voice among the Supers rose once again, and countless Supers went to support the association, thinking that this was unfair.

However, it would be unrealistic to say that the methods of the three Universal Civilizations were ineffective. The slogans of support shouted by the Supers were merely that, since no one wished to put themself in danger. Thus, those Supers who initially wished to join the association slowly retreated…

One could still use the internet to make themselves look and feel good, but their bodies were still the most honest.

It was just that this method had no effect on the players. Instead, it aroused widespread dissatisfaction. This was not limited to the players who were in the Beyond Grade A faction, but even players from the neutral faction and the three Universal Civilizations' faction were annoyed.

To the players, while sanctions could be forced on others, the same should not apply to them. The three Universal Civilizations tried to force them to conform to their ideals, which sparked a rebellious mentality for some of the players.

So what if it's the three Universal Civilizations? Why don't they take a look at what the name of this version is? Do you think we're all afraid of you?

The players were originally a part of the Super community, and thus, they were innately closer to the association. These sanctions also indirectly strengthened the determination of some players to join the association, speeding up the rate at which players from various organizations switched over to the association…

Anyway, since we're not afraid of death, just try it!

At this time, while public opinion was raging, the Beyond Grade A Association held an emergency meeting under the call of Han Xiao.

…

In the association's meeting hall, no one was late, and many Beyond Grade A projections sat there with solemn expressions.

Some did not attend, and some of the seats at the round table that should have been filled were vacant.

At this moment, however, everyone's gaze was trained on Han Xiao at the main position.

Han Xiao surveyed the audience, both of his hands steepled in front of his nose as he spoke.

"The reason for me convening this meeting is clear, I believe. The three Universal Civilizations have imposed sanctions on us, so we must also reciprocate and counterattack."

As he spoke, he gestured at the empty seats in the room.

"Everyone can see that the direct members of the three Universal Civilizations did not come to this meeting. I have temporarily terminated their membership rights, and we are no longer obliged to provide any form of help, including but not limited to Beyond Grade A military, technical support, and more. If you have any objections, please stand up now."

Just as he finished speaking, the room echoed with a resounding, "Approve!"

The key behind these two commands was to obtain the consent of the Beyond Grade A allies. After all, while the allies were not direct members, not everyone was on bad terms with the three Universal Civilizations.

However, this time, the three Universal Civilizations did not differentiate, throwing everyone, even their allies, under the bus. This made the majority of the allies unhappy.

Only a few of the allies hesitated due to different concerns, but before the situation turned for the better, they could not leave the association since they were already riding atop the tiger. If they did not accompany the association in advancing and retreating, they would not be able to mix in with the rest of the Beyond Grade A circle in the future. In addition, the attitude the three Universal Civilizations had toward the Beyond Grade As was not worthy of their high hopes.

In the eyes of everyone present, the second life afforded by the Sanctum Revival was naturally more important than anything external.

The majority of strength held by a Beyond Grade A organization was judged by the strength of their leaders. So long as they were still helming the place, even if their organizations were hit by various problems, they would always make a comeback. They were people who relied on their abilities to feed themselves and thus did not panic.

Almost everyone knew that the goal of them uniting was in the interest of benefitting their entire caste. The three Universal Civilizations had already exposed all their cards, so if they did not unite to resist now, there would not be any more chances in the future. Temporary gains and losses were not important at the present. Only those with extreme short-sightedness would view such things with importance, thinking about how they could save themselves.

The association was playing the role that was originally envisaged, becoming the link for the unity of the Beyond Grade As. Even if someone had different thoughts and opinions, they could only stand with the association at this point in time.

"Since everyone agrees, these two orders will remain active until the three Universal Civilizations revoke the sanctions." Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

To be honest, he had long wanted to exclude the direct descendants of the three Universal Civilizations but never had a good chance. Now they had just sent an excuse to his doorstep.

Milizaus stroked his beard before solemnly saying, "No matter what, the sanctions will pose a problem for us. Black Star, what are your plans?"

Han Xiao tapped the table. "Channels, territory, manpower, funds… These are all entry points for the three Universal Civilizations to restrain us. Withstanding the pressure will be our next focus. It is imperative for us to shrink our business and streamline the scale of our operations. Among them, the most affected would be the channels, as the sanctions practically deprive us of resources. Thus, the Galactic Black Market will be an important area for us… Secret Master, we'll have to rely on you."

Secret Master nodded.

As the administrators behind the Galactic Black Market were all Beyond Grade As, in the future, the black market would serve as the logistical core of the association. A new round of expansion and integration would inevitably occur in the black market, which would be beneficial to Secret Master and the other administrators.

Han Xiao paused momentarily before he continued. "Furthermore, not everyone in the universe will impose sanctions on us. These forces will also be the targets of our cooperation."

"Like the Super Star Clusters?" someone probed.

Han Xiao flashed the person a glance, smiling. "If the bargaining chips are right, the Super Star Cluster will also be an option."

Hearing this, some of the Super Star Cluster Beyond Grade As that were disguised as neutral parties brightened.

At this time, Kasuyi interjected. "The Super Star Clusters… It's ok if they make trouble, but are you willing to cooperate with them?"

"That will depend on whether both sides can come out with a bargaining chip that they are satisfied with. Moreover, from another viewpoint, the Super Star Cluster also needs us to confront the three Universal Civilizations. While both of us are not to the point that we are mutually tied down, we each have something that the other can give," Han Xiao said.

At this moment, Manison lightly snorted. "Initially, I cooperated with the Super Star Cluster Alliance, but the reaction from the three Universal Civilizations was not small at all. If we arrive at a deal with them, the three Universal Civilizations will definitely be riled up, and it will not be a simple matter to clear up."

Han Xiao turned to him, raising his brows. "You scared?"

"Humph, what do I have to be scared of?" Manison snorted in disdain. "I'm just reminding you of the consequences."

Han Xiao waved his hands. "It doesn't matter. Since the three Universal Civilizations have decided to publicly impose sanctions, they must have also predicted that we will contact the Super Star Cluster Alliance. But they did not care, proving that they're psychologically prepared, maybe even having the mentality to capture all of us in one go… Even so, we still have to contact the Super Star Cluster Alliance to let the three Universal Civilizations know that we're not easy to handle."

"I thought you would always remain loyal to the three Universal Civilizations." Manison spoke coldly, apparently still having the Intelligent Plague incident at the back of his mind.

"I only aim to maintain order. I've never had any sort of loyalty toward the three Universal Civilizations. If I can maintain order in the universe, it doesn't matter who I support." Han Xiao rebutted.

Manison blandly replied, "That sounds nice to hear, but aren't you just taking my old path? It seems like I'm still right after all."

Han Xiao did not think much of it, smiling. "You endangered the entire Galactic Society with your actions. I only made the rulers fear our power. The two are different in nature. I'm much better than you."

"Humph, excuses, excuses." Manison avoided his gaze, no longer daring to speak.

Since things had already developed to this point, the fake Virtual Mutiny Virus he had developed over the years was practically of no use, so Manison felt that this was a pity.

However, in his opinion, it was still good as secret insurance. If the association could not withstand the pressure of the three Universal Civilizations, he would not mind using this assassin to help the association, turning it into the situation he originally envisioned.

Han Xiao did not bother with Manison either, carefully explaining the next steps of the plan. Right now, the association needed everyone to be united, not involved in their own private disputes. His current authority and words were already enough to make everyone obey.

At the very end, Han Xiao paused before instructing, "If we want to resolve this situation, we must either let the three Universal Civilizations revoke the sanctions on their own, or we open up a new form of development. We can progress in both routes simultaneously… but acting is one thing. We also have to maintain a balance, not implicating too many innocents. The purpose of our counterattack is to make the three Universal Civilizations feel pressure in facing us directly. The three Universal Civilizations are pressuring us so as to force us to make a wrong move, allowing them to prove that we pose a huge threat to the Galactic Civilizations."

Everyone nodded in return. They also understood this logic, as such mind games in war were common. However, if they broke the baseline, then they would become the unreasonable ones.

This meeting lasted almost a whole day, and many of the members divided the labor among themselves. While the association was originally a loose alliance, it now felt more like an organization.

After the meeting ended, the projections disappeared one by one, leaving only Han Xiao and Kasuyi in the room.

Kasuyi's expression relaxed as he smiled. "When are you planning to show your hand against the three Universal Civilizations? They seem thoroughly convinced that there's only a limited number of revival opportunities in the Sanctums, or else they would be more radical."

He was more confident than anyone else about this battle, as he held the secret of the unlimited times for Sanctum Revival. He had no fear of the sanctions from the three Universal Civilizations.

At the same time, Kasuyi felt that Han Xiao made the right choice by concealing this secret. Otherwise, the three Universal Civilizations would probably not adopt such a radical method. In his opinion, this was luring the three Universal Civilizations to make the wrong decisions.

"No worry, we'll just wait for the opportunity." Han Xiao waved his hand.

"Anyway, you know what to do, so I'll leave it to you." Kasuyi nodded before cancelling his projection.

Han Xiao shook his head, his eyes flashing.

"I estimate that the Super Star Cluster Alliance Beyond Grade As dressed as neutrals will have already conveyed my words to the Super Star Cluster Alliance…"

…

The leaders of the Super Star Cluster Alliance gathered together, listening to the report.

"Are you sure? Black Star said he wants to reach out?"

Many of the leaders were overjoyed.

"The association is now in a tight situation and urgently requires new channels. It also has to fight back against the three Universal Civilizations. Cooperating with us is naturally a good choice," the leader of the Star Arc Civilization said, his eyes beaming.

While Black Star had some conflicts with them and they disliked each other, if they could obtain help from the Beyond Grade A Association through Black Star, that little grudge could not be considered much.

The stronger the Super Star Cluster Alliance became, the more uncomfortable the three Universal Civilizations would feel. The Super Star Cluster Alliance were most willing to have a new variable appear in this universe.

As for the offenses stated by the three Universal Civilizations when violating the sanctions, the Super Star Cluster Alliance did not give two hoots. Both of them were in conflict, so even without this extra reason, the three Universal Civilizations would still suppress them at every opportunity.

However, the association only cooperated with them at this point, after falling out with their 'old bestie' the three Universal Civilizations, treating them like a backup plan…

Thinking of this, many of the Star Cluster leaders felt a little awkward.

But they did not wallow in their anxieties for long.

Forget it. As long as we get the good stuff, so what if we're spare tires?

We're happy to be so!

Chapter 1280: Withdrawal and Conditions

The meeting place for the Shattered Star Ring Civilization Conference consisted of an area where the dome looked like a portion of the starry sky, constantly shifting, while the great hall was filled with various civilizations in the Star Field. The meeting seemed to have been going on for quite a while.

"… Regarding the sanctions from the three Universal Civilizations, there is too much content. In response to this joint decree, I suggest that the Shattered Star Ring Civilization Council supervise the implementation of the decree in the Star Field, ensuring the complete termination of all civilizations to the Beyond Grade A Association…"

A representative of a Star Cluster civilization sitting on a chair read out the proposal before throwing the question out and saying in a deep voice, "This is the current situation. Does anyone have an opinion?"

The moment he finished speaking, the scene turned silent, and the expressions of the many representatives present were complicated.

The power of the Black Star Army in the Shattered Star Ring was too large. This Star Field could practically be considered as their backyard. More than eighty percent of the civilizations there had different areas of cooperation with them, and they had always cooperated happily in a win-win situation. The sanctions were a trouble for them.

However, they were even more afraid of the three Universal Civilizations. In terms of interests, they were more intertwined with the three Universal Civilizations.

It was not just that, but the strongest seven civilizations of the Shattered Star Ring had already chosen their positions, expressing support for the three Universal Civilizations. No one knew what sort of agreement they had with the three Universal Civilizations, but even reluctant, all of them had no choice but to follow suit.

"… Agreed."

"Seconded."

Everyone was silent for a while before opening their mouths one after another. Many of them vaguely glanced toward the Planet Aquamarine civilization, their eyes complicated, with pitying, sighing, or gloating gazes.

The condition to access the Civilization Conference was to be a Star System level Civilization, but Planet Aquamarine was of a different breed. It ranked as a surface civilization, but its status was brought to it by Black Star. Just a Beyond Grade A was enough to propel them to the sky.

For a long time, many of the civilizations had envied and hated Planet Aquamarine. They could not cultivate a Beyond Grade A, but they actually had three of them. This was some bullsh*t luck!

With the promotion of Hila and Aurora, the status of Planet Aquamarine had risen rapidly in recent years. Even if the civilization was weak, they could afford to be rampant in the Civilization Council since all the civilizations in the Shattered Star Ring depended on the Black Star Army. They had taken good care of Planet Aquamarine, but without the protection of Black Star, Planet Aquamarine would be nothing in their eyes.

Since Black Star had fallen out of favor, many of the people in the room wished to see the Planet Aquamarine turn into a joke.

Very quickly, every civilization present either agreed or abstained from voting, leaving only the Star Pupil Civilization and Planet Aquamarine having not expressed their opinions.

At this moment, one of the Star Cluster level council members spoke up. "Representatives of Planet Aquamarine and Star Pupil Civilization, only you two are left."

The expression of the Star Pupil Civilization Represent was conflicted, his lips twisting around. After a few long seconds, he finally answered in a low voice.

"… We abstain."

Everyone could not help but glance at him, and a touch of surprise flashed across their faces. However, they understood the reason behind.

Only Planet Aquamarine was left, and everyone's gaze fell onto Bennett.

"Planet Aquamarine Civilization, what about you guys?" The Star Cluster representative pressed on.

Bennett took a deep breath before solemnly speaking as he stood up.

"We strongly oppose these unfair sanctions and will never accept the unprovoked accusations and slander… From now on, Planet Aquamarine Civilization will withdraw from the Shattered Star Ring Civilization Conference!"

His tone was sonorous and powerful, without hesitation.

Everyone suddenly went into an uproar, looking at the expressionless Bennett in surprise.

They had thought that Planet Aquamarine would adopt a more roundabout attitude but did not expect them to be so stubborn, immediately speaking about leaving the council.

The Representative of the Purple Crystal Civilization could not help but ask, "Are you certain?"

"Black Star is one of the greatest figures in the history of Planet Aquamarine. We will not allow any person or organization to maliciously slander him. Even the three Universal Civilizations should not arbitrarily discredit the great figures of other civilizations!" Bennett's tone was hard as steel.

Having said this, he directly lifted the remote projection, disappearing from the meeting. He expressed his attitude through actions.

Seeing this, many of the representatives exchanged glances, their expressions complicated.

They did not expect that Planet Aquamarine would be so resolute as to remain standing by Black Star's side, willing to bear the hatred of the three Universal Civilizations…

In fact, in their eyes, Planet Aquamarine had a much better way to deal with this matter. They believed that Black Star would understand, but to take such a tough attitude and openly challenge the three Universal Civilizations, they would likely become a model for the latter to use as a lesson to learn for others.

Many of the representatives shook their heads and sighed, involuntarily glancing at the Star Pupil Civilization representative.

In their eyes, what the Star Pupil Civilization did was undoubtedly the right thing…

But in their hearts, all of them were unsatisfied toward the three Universal Civilizations, and seeing how someone actually dared to stick their head out filled them with admiration.

Almost every civilization wished to oppose the hegemonic decree from the three Universal Civilizations in a clear-cut manner, but unfortunately… no one had such confidence.

The representative of the Star Pupil Civilization secretly clenched his fists in a place where no one could see, as an expression of shame flashed across his face.

…

In his office, Bennett opened his eyes as his vision returned to the room.

He only saw a group of executive officials waiting there, staring at him for orders.

Bennett lightly sighed before solemnly ordering.

"We have already withdrawn from the Shattered Star Ring Council. Announce our decision to the whole civilization."

"…Understood."

No one said anything more, receiving the orders and leaving the room in a file.

It did not take long for this incident to spread across the entire Planet Aquamarine through their official media and social channels.

Bennett stayed within his office the whole time. After reading the news, he took out his communicator and logged onto the quantum network to check the public's attitude on this matter.

Soon, messages came into his view.

"Well done! I've long gotten tired of seeing the three Universal Civilizations!"

"To dare discredit our greatest, what a bunch of garbage!"

"I sincerely support the decision of our federal government. The three Universal Civilizations are clearly bullying us. Did you think we were submissive people‽"

Seeing the messages filled with indignation and righteous fury from the citizens, Bennett's old face crinkled into a smile.

Let's hope that this was the right choice…

…

On the Star Pupil Civilization's mother planet, Psyker stood in front of the window, overlooking the bustling city. Flying vehicles passed as they emitted trails of flames in the neighborhood, and the glow was reflected across his seven pupils simultaneously, like countless flashing meteors.

At this moment, a few of the upper echelons walked into his office.

"Has everything been settled?" Psyker blandly asked, without turning his head back.

"Yes… we've made them express their attitude in the council," someone replied with a low voice. They seemed rather disappointed.

Psyker turned around and slowly said, "Get ready for my retirement ceremony as soon as possible."

Upon hearing this, the expressions of several of the upper echelons became heavier. They revealed a sense of helpless sorrow.

Seeing this, Psyker smiled. "You will soon take over my authority. Don't be so glum."

One of them could not help but grit his teeth and ask, "Do you have to do this? Can't we be like Planet Aquamarine and express our objections?"

Hearing this, Psyker fell silent. "… I'm not Black Star. He alone can make the three Universal Civilizations fear his presence. I don't have that ability."

Psyker was uncomfortable in his heart. He shook his head gently before looking out of the window again as he whispered, "If we wish for the civilization to avoid the attacks of the three Universal Civilizations, then I can only step down… In the end, we are all involuntary people trapped within the torrent of the times."

The three Universal Civilizations' sanctions specified that the Beyond Grade A could not interfere in civilization politics in any form, even if they had always been the leader of the civilization. Psyker attached importance to the Sanctum Revival, but he could not sit back and watch his civilization be sanctioned. Thus, he decided to surrender his power and step down.

As the saying went, when there were policies at the top, there would be countermeasures from the bottom. As long as the political connection between himself and his civilization was broken, the Star Pupil Civilization would not meet the standard to be sanctioned and would not be downgraded. After becoming a free man, he could also throw himself into the struggle of the Beyond Grade As without any baggage.

At the same time, Psyker was not completely letting go. Going rogue was just a temporary measure to avoid the limelight. If the association reached a balance with the three Universal Civilizations, he would still have the chance to regain power.

Furthermore, having led his civilization for so long, he wished to let go and take a break.

"I understand."

The rest of the upper echelons helplessly nodded.

At this moment, someone thought of something and said, "By the way, the Shattered Star Ring Council passed a bill, asking us to cooperate with the sanctions. What should we do?"

Psyker's eyes flashed, his tone playful, as he replied, "You guys decide. I'll just remind you not to take it so seriously. The civilizations of Shattered Star Ring are cooperating with each other, but no one will do their best… because all of them are smart, knowing that both the three Universal Civilizations and the Beyond Grade A Association cannot be offended. If we leave ourselves a way out, we will have better days ahead. Don't worry about that. The civilizations themselves know what to do."

…

In the Super Star Cluster Alliance remote conference room, the rest of the Star Cluster leaders gathered in a hall, everyone showing solemn expressions, displaying a majestic attitude.

Everyone was serious as though awaiting a distinguished guest. It was precisely Han Xiao.

A few days ago, after learning about the attitude of the association, the Super Star Cluster Alliance had issued a private invitation to Black Star to have a meeting with them and received a positive answer.

The leaders had made a show out of this meeting. On one hand, they wished to show their sincerity and cooperation to Black Star… Basically, they were willing to pretend and butter up to him.

Time ticked by, and Han Xiao's projection suddenly appeared.

Surveying around, Han Xiao greeted, "Hey, everyone's here?"

"Your Excellency Black Star."

Everyone nodded.

This should be the first time all the leaders of the Super Star Cluster Alliance were speaking with Black Star. No matter what emotions they had, everyone suppressed them to be cordial.

In fact, most of the grievances between the Super Star Cluster Civilization and Han Xiao were only limited to the friction during the Flickering War, which was no deep hatred.

Only the Three Kings of Modo secretly clenched their fists, trembling in anger.

Their grudges with Han Xiao were the greatest, since they were directly kicked out of the Flickering War. There was also one of their leaders whom they suspected to have died in an assassination from the Black Star Army. The other party's hands were covered in Modo blood.

If it were not for the overall situation, the Three Kings of Modo would have pounced on Han Xiao.

Han Xiao swept his gaze across the room, disregarding them as he slowly spoke. "I'm quite busy, and I believe everyone knows why, so let's make this long story short. I also roughly understand the purpose of you inviting me to meet. From your standpoint, you also hope that there'll be an organization that can resist against the three Universal Civilizations. Now that we have flipped the table with the three Universal Civilizations, the association needs new allies. As long as their price is right, cooperation between our two parties will not be a problem."

"Very good, this is also what we want." The leader of Star Arc Civilization coughed and expressed their agreement as the representative. "So, what do you want?"

"Channels, territories, resources, funds, intelligence networks…" Han Xiao listed the most urgent needs of the association, as well as hiding the rare materials needed for the Sanctum key openings within.

After discussion, the Star Arc Civilization's leader nodded. "These things can be provided, and the share meets your requirements. Long-term supply will also not be a problem. In order to show our sincerity, we will give them to you as soon as possible."

"Then your conditions?" Han Xiao calmly replied.

"First, we hope that the association will continue to confront the three Universal Civilizations and carry out more counterattacks." The leader stretched out a finger.

"Sure."

"Second, we hope to get assistance from the association's top people, such as combat strength, techniques, and the like."

"Okay."

"Third, we hope the association can provide its own channels and special products. Working closely with the Super Star Cluster Alliance will help both of us achieve a win-win situation."

"Okay."

"Lastly… we hope that you will use the Sanctum Revival to resurrect all of our dead Beyond Grade As, especially those who were sacrificed during the Tragedy of the Pinnacles!"

As his voice sounded, everyone became more eager, staring firmly at Han Xiao.

The last condition was their core requirement. If they could resurrect their direct ancestors, then in terms of advanced combatants, the Super Star Cluster Alliance would be able to stand up against the three Universal Civilizations.

Moreover, the Tragedy of the Pinnacles was an eternal thorn in their hides. If this could be remedied, then it would all be worth it!

Han Xiao did not find it surprising. He stared at everyone with a playful smile, but a cold gleam seemed to flash across his eyes like that of a reaper's scythe.

"The three Universal Civilizations gave the same conditions, and I rejected them. However, that was then, and this is now. I can consider this request… but the current price you are offering is far from enough."

Chapter 1281: Gains Without Risks

Hearing this, the eyes of the leaders present brightened.

When they put forward this condition, they were a little nervous in fact. They were worried that Black Star would reject everything at once, since the three Universal Civilizations would have made similar requests, and the sanctions meant that Black Star had rejected them, probably because he did not wish to strengthen his enemies.

In all fairness, if they were standing in Black Star's position, they would also firmly control the quota of the Sanctum Revivals and not easily resurrect the direct members of the other factions. Thus, they were not confident in their proposal.

But when they heard Han Xiao's answer, everyone was finally relieved. It did not matter if the price was too huge, as long as there was room for negotiation!

"These can be discussed. I don't know what sort of conditions you might have." The leader of the Star Arc Civilization probed.

Han Xiao stroked his chin, slowly saying, "Since a Beyond Grade A can only be revived once, this is a one-shot deal, so every revival will be worth a lot. Does everyone here agree?"

Everyone nodded.

Han Xiao secretly smirked, but his tone remained casual.

"Thus, don't expect me to resurrect all your direct descendants at once. I will only do it in batches, with a fixed number in each batch. As for the specific resurrections, it will depend on which civilization gives me the price I want. First come, first served… Of course, my needs at each stage will be different. It might be that, later, fewer things will impress me, so a larger amount of money will be needed."

The leaders all revealed choking expressions.

This was practically trying to rip them off!

They were all allies, but each civilization would definitely wish to resurrect their own direct descendants first. Black Star's move was undoubtedly a plot to make them outbid each other. This was the power of a monopolistic business.

However, the leaders present were mentally prepared for this. They knew that cutting off some flesh was unavoidable.

"What exactly do you want in general?"

Han Xiao casually pinched his fingers as he smiled. "High Grade Blueprints, unique technology, Universal Treasures, rare resources… it does not have to be all these, you can weigh the standard of the items yourself. After all, I don't know what items each of you hold. You can discuss it among yourself. I don't care, but don't try any tricks. In here, it doesn't mean that the highest bidder wins but rather that I have to be satisfied.

"Of course, I also welcome those who wish to operate in the dark and privately bid. I'm still a bit ethical and will not disclose your respective bids easily… In short, it depends on how much you are willing to fork out."

Hearing this, the Star Arc Civilization's leader exchanged a glance with everyone before nodding on behalf of them all.

"… Ok, we'll accept this condition."

"Then, I'm delighted to have reached a consensus with you all. I look forward to cooperating with all of you in the future."

Seeing Black Star cancel his projection, the taut nerves of the leaders began to relax, their expressions resigned.

"Black Star has quite the appetite."

"Humph, he's just taking advantage of us."

"What else can we do? Who made it that he would be the only one monopolizing the Sanctum Revival knowledge? We'll have to discuss what price to pay now."

Based on the situation, they could only play by Black Star's rules and not anything else. They had finally opened this channel between both parties, so if they did something stupid for the sake of reducing costs and ended up offending Black Star, causing them to lose their Sanctum Revival privileges, that would be a disaster.

Universal Treasures, unique technological blueprints… these things might cause them to feel the pinch, but they could still afford it.

They intended to discuss who would resurrect their descendants first and who later on, arranging the order. They were unwilling to blindly bid and hurt their relationships.

…

After Han Xiao cancelled the communication, his vision returned to his office. His eyes flashed.

"Heh, god knows how much good stuff I can obtain this time. While I scammed the Super Star Cluster Alliance quite a bit this time, they should have sufficient treasures to meet my demands."

Taking out a piece of fruit candy from his snack jar, Han Xiao fiddled it casually before throwing it into his mouth. The sweetness he tasted mirrored his emotions.

From the beginning, he had planned to cooperate with the organizations that had a need to resurrect others; it was the correct way to maximize the benefits of the Sanctum Revival. In the past, in order to maintain the mystery and to stabilize the situation, he did not engage in this business, but now, his situation had changed. He had to adapt to the changes and adjust his strategy.

The Sanctum Revival was a rare product, so Han Xiao was not worried that the Super Star Cluster Alliance would not agree to his demands. To him, this was a way to gain something without risking anything of his own. As long as he continued to pretend that the Sanctum Revival was only available once, he could drive the price up and trick them into giving him a lot of resources in exchange for the precious 'one-off' quota.

As for how and when to resurrect them, this was completely up to him. He just needed to say that the time was not yet right to turn away the dissatisfaction of the Super Star Clusters. These 'leeks' would have no choice but to only wait.

However, Han Xiao also did not intend to completely fleece them. He would resurrect a small portion of the Super Star Cluster descendants to give them a taste.

This move would not only allow the Super Star Cluster Alliance to taste the fruits of success, deepening their transaction cooperation, but it would also anger the three Universal Civilizations, causing both sides to go against each other. So long as the resurrected ones remained small, the situation would still be under the control of both the association and the Holy Accord.

After all, the Super Star Cluster was different from the three Universal Civilizations. Since there were more experts in the three Universal Civilizations, they naturally wanted to rule over everything, but once the advanced combatants of the Super Star Clusters returned, they would be able to pressure the three Universal Civilizations, which would indirectly benefit the association.

Thus, Han Xiao would only make this transaction with the Super Star Clusters and not with the three Universal Civilizations. Otherwise, this would only make the latter think that their sanction order had been effective, leading them to mistakenly think that they had succeeded in bending the association to their will.

However, if the war against the World Tree Civilization broke out, then Han Xiao would not mind resurrecting a lot of the old Beyond Grade As to deal with the invasion. The main thing was that he had to act on the spot and adjust his strategies flexibly.

Just as he was deep in thought, Phillip emerged from his table, holding a virtual screen several times larger than his body in both hands as he gruffly spoke.

"Master, master, many civilizations of the Shattered Star Ring have sent a communication request to you. Do you wish to answer, hum?"

Han Xiao came back to his senses, glancing at the caller ID on his screen before curling his lips.

"Heh, these people don't dare to offend the three Universal Civilizations, and at the same time, they don't dare to offend me either, so they ran over to apologize and explain… Let's listen to what sort of rainbow farts they can give off."

Han Xiao swept through the list before picking his old partner, the Purple Crystal Civilization.

When the representative of the Purple Crystal Civilization appeared, he did a customary bow before speaking. "Paying respects to Your Excellency Black Star…"

Han Xiao waved his hands in dismissal. "I'm a little busy. Just get to the point."

"Alright, this time, I'm here to represent the Purple Crystal Civilization to apologize to you…" He snuck a glance at Han Xiao's expression that was still calm before carefully following up. "Due to the sanctions imposed by the three Universal Civilizations, the Shattered Star Ring Civilization Conference has already passed the proposal, and we have no choice but to cooperate. The Purple Crystal Civilization Conference has been happily working with you for a long time, but with the severity of the situation now, I hope you can understand…"

"So, you wish to end all our partnerships?" Han Xiao raised his brow.

"Cough cough, please believe us when I say it's temporary. You also understand. Given the chance, we would love to continue working with the Black Star Army, but the attitude of the three Universal Civilizations is too tough now. We're just being safe. When the problem is solved, we'll immediately resume our business dealings and will also give you compensation…"

The representative of the Purple Crystal Civilization spoke sincerely, emphasizing their helplessness.

Han Xiao did not agree with him in his heart, but he did not refute him, only verbally expressing his understanding.

He then followed by answering the communications of all the others in the Shattered Star Ring one by one. Everyone basically had the same attitude, which was to apologize and express that they had to cooperate with the sanctions.

After hanging up the last communication call, Han Xiao sneered.

"Humph, a bunch of fools who steer the rudder based on the wind direction."

They cooperated with the army when they wished to have benefits, but now that they were under pressure, they kicked the army to the curb since they had outlived their usefulness.

Of course, the civilizations had to take care of themselves, and there was no point in them supporting the association either. Han Xiao understood this clearly, but it did not mean that he had to forgive them.

These civilizations blindly thought that the rule of the three Universal Civilizations over the Galactic Society was still stable, and thus, they would rather offend the Black Star Army a little than being marked by the three Universal Civilizations. For civilizations, between the Black Star Army and the three Universal Civilizations, it was easy to decide which to trade off.

Thus, Han Xiao could not be bothered to force the civilizations to choose his side, or else it would only turn nasty. It was better to keep this current state of getting along and make the other party feel as though they owed him something. While it might not be of any use, it was better than making more enemies.

He snorted as he chewed on his candy.

"Once the sanctions of the three Universal Civilizations lift, you'll be the ones who bleed… Heh, you think that the Galactic Society will remain stable so long as you are under the rule of the three Universal Civilizations? The moment a foreign enemy invades, you'll know how fragile this peace is, and by then, let's see if the three Universal Civilizations that you trust so much will have the energy to protect you."

After cursing a while longer, Han Xiao reined in his emotions, calling his secretary and letting him handle the handover procedures of the civilizations.

He then opened the organization territory distribution version of the star map, looking at it as he muttered.

"Expanding and controlling the Galactic Black Market in various places will be our next focus. The three Universal Civilizations will definitely not sit back and watch, however. It will likely turn into another secret war, which will cause quite a high death rate. Thus, the players will be the best to send in for the mission of obtaining the black markets. Not only is their strength good, but they are also not afraid of death. It is sufficient to take on this mission."

As he spoke out loud, Han Xiao marked down this idea on the star map, deciding to issue this order in a few days to send the players collectively to perform the mission.

"Furthermore, in terms of advanced combatants, we have to put more pressure on the three Universal Civilizations. I previously promised them that I would not casually resurrect any historical Beyond Grade As, but now that they've done this, I have to be 'courteous' and respond in kind. It's a pity that the keys to the Sanctums have not been fully gathered, so I cannot simply just resurrect a batch of new ones…"

Han Xiao's thoughts flew rapidly.

"The Holy Accord can come in handy, since there are still many of them hiding within the organization. It's better to pull a portion of the Beyond Grade As into the association, pretending to have done a new resurrection… Having a trump card is indeed convenient, and I don't know how the three Universal Civilizations will react…"

…

Meanwhile, the three Universal Civilizations' leaders met up in a joint meeting room to secretly discuss matters.

"The association has frozen the membership rights of our direct Beyond Grade As and also announced that they will not accept any tasks from us. These are all expected counters, but they're meaningless," the Pope said indifferently.

Louis nodded. "The association's next move is expected to be the integration of the black markets. This will be their main resource channel in the future, but we will have long set the ground and will not let them succeed so easily."

Marbruce then spoke in a deep voice. "This is not the main point. The key is to test if Black Star can indeed perform Sanctum Revivals at will."

"Well, with his character, he will inevitably take countermeasures, such as contacting the Super Star Cluster Alliance and cooperating with them. The Super Star Cluster Alliance will likely also propose resurrection as a bargaining chip, and it is hard to say whether Black Star will agree to that. But even if the deal is not reached, Black Star will also try to recover other historical Beyond Grade As to put pressure on us. Now, it's up to him whether he can do so."

"If he cannot do this…" The Pope's eyes gleamed. "Then whatever he's doing now is undoubtedly playing for time!"

The sanctions by the trio were not just to contain the expansion of the association but also to test Han Xiao's control over the Sanctums.

This was not a whimsical thought but rather a conclusion they reached as a result of much research in the Sanctum Revival Research Institute. They had confirmed that the Sanctums were immensely difficult to open and needed some sort of catalyst as well. Thus, the Sanctum Revival could not be casually done.

Based on this idea, the trio had introduced the current sanctions. If it was proven that Black Star could not resurrect people at will, this would be the best time to implement the cleansing plan. Otherwise, if they waited too long, it might allow for another wave of Sanctum Revivals.

However, even if Black Star resurrected newcomers, it might be an opportunity for them as it would cause Black Star to waste a valuable medium and cause the resurrection method to enter another cooldown.

Of course, they did not rule out the fact that Black Star had seen through them and deliberately kept his hand hidden. This was a danger to them.

This was undoubtedly risky behavior for them, which would not only make them pay a huge price but also go against their need to maintain order. Thus, they had yet to make up their minds, only wanting to probe Black Star.

At this moment, the Pope glanced at Louis, before asking, "By the way, how are your preparations for Manison's operation?"

Louis calmly nodded. "It's almost ready, thanks to your help. The things we promised you will be delivered back to you soon."

"That's good," the Pope replied blandly.

When the federation came knocking on their door for help, he had suggested returning the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter back to them.

Because they were unable to crack apart the Spacetime Amber even after so many years, the federation finally agreed to this request and chose to return the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter in its seal back to the original owner.

At the same time, the federation also had their own expectations. If the Arcane Church could manage to unblock or duplicate the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter by chance, then in the future Beyond Grade A cleansing operations, this would come in handy.

Chapter 1282: Entering the Black Market

On April 1st, Year 782 of the Galaxy Calendar, the three Universal Civilizations jointly issued a sanction order against the entire Beyond Grade A Association. On April 3rd, the Beyond Grade A Association responded, and both parties officially tore aside all pretenses. The organizations of the various Star Fields moved separately in response to the influence of the sanctions, and it was not until April 26th that a clear pattern was finally formed.

Ever since the return of the Immortals on March 10th, in just a short month and a half, the situation of the Galactic Society had been changing rapidly, full of turbulence. The Beyond Grade A Association had found new allies. The Super Star Cluster Alliance opposed the sanctions and issued a righteous criticism, believing that the three Universal Civilizations were abusing their power. Thus, the Super Star Cluster turned to support the Association, and this resulted in the open confrontation of the Association with the three Universal Civilizations.

Because of the response from various civilizations, many of the Beyond Grade A organizations started to shrink, their branches and bases established in the civilizations also having to relocate. Some moved into the desolate universe belt, while some shifted to the Flickering World as an industrial relocation. The Beyond Grade A organizations that originally had a territory in the Flickering World were like sweet rice cakes, causing the other Beyond Grade As to congregate there like ants.

Among them, some of the Beyond Grade As who had established organizations within the three Universal Civilizations suffered even more, having their industries and bases temporarily closed.

The three Universal Civilizations had mobilized the entire Galactic Society to seal off any development of the Beyond Grade A Association. A large number of Beyond Grade A Organizations had thus been hit, their scale shrinking. The stock prices of their listed consortiums were also plummeting.

At the same time, the organizations that support the Association had also been targeted by the three Universal Civilizations. Among them was Planet Aquamarine, which had their diplomatic relationships completely cut off, forcing them to be self-sufficient. The weaker the organization, the more serious the targeting. In contrast, the Super Star Cluster Alliance did not feel as though there was much impact. They were already used to being targeted, so the situation was already so bad that making it worse made no real difference.

A portion of people believed that the goal of the sanctions was to cut off the wings of the Beyond Grade As. If they had no more followers and industries, then the influence of the Beyond Grade As would be suppressed to the lowest level, isolated from the rest of the Galactic Society. However, others believed that while the three Universal Civilizations were decisive in their actions, this was not a permanent cure, and it might not be able to deal with the Beyond Grade A themselves, let alone attack their organizations.

Both theories had a large number of supporters, but the undisputed fact was that the smell of gunpowder was growing ever stronger in the Galactic Society. As the times became more sensitive, the emotions of the interstellar citizens gradually turned more fanatical, manipulated by propaganda.

Beyond the sight of the majority, the Galactic Black Market in various regions had become a secret battlefield, with frequent incidents and fights. A tug of war for control of the black market had begun.

At a neutral transit station planet in the Shattered Star Ring…

Among row after row of high-rise buildings, several low-altitude, flying vehicles whizzed through the city at high speed, disrupting the flow of traffic and frequently causing accidents.

These vehicles belonged to two groups of people, those fleeing and the pursuers. The pursued had superb driving skills and constantly made use of various difficult maneuvers to avoid obstacles along the way. They drove extremely fast in the complicated road conditions.

"Faster, they're about to catch up!"

"Shut up, don't distract me!"

In the escape vehicle at the front, a lizard man covered in red scales was jumping around anxiously. He kept looking at the rear-view mirror while a burly man in a mechanical suit was operating the vehicle with a solemn expression. In the rear cabin were a group of passengers swaying from side to side.

This group of people were a group of local black-market operators. On the surface, they had a legal shell corporation, but in reality, they had a few secret black market business channels in their hands. They belonged to a group of social clubs that had a name on the black-market organization. As a low-level distribution channel, they had always been living on this neutral planet, enjoying life like gods.

However, not long ago, the social clubs were infiltrated by spies from unknown organizations. Their territories and businesses were attacked by unknown militants one after another, and they suffered heavy losses. The core members of the clubs were also hunted down and could only resort to hiding.

Just a moment ago, their hiding place had been discovered, and they had hurriedly escaped with their vehicles. A few teams of armed enemies had been chasing them relentlessly, and both sides had been running for their lives in the bustling city.

"Who are these people? When we fought them, they were clearly well trained. They don't look like they're scattered soldiers. They're probably professional armed organizations. Why would they come to us?" The burly man's tone was solemn.

The Lizardman was furious. "What sh*t do I know? These people appeared out of nowhere. I don't even know how and when I provoked them!"

"Could it be that our competitors invited mercenaries?"

"I don't care what happens to him. All I care about now is whether I can escape!" the Lizardman shouted.

Just as he finished speaking, the flying vehicle passed by an intersection. Suddenly, a pursuer that had circled to the front appeared out of nowhere and crashed into them.

Boom!

There was a huge shock, followed by a sudden force. The passengers in the cabin did not have time to react and were all slammed into the cabin wall.

The high-speed vehicle was knocked over by the other party slamming into its waist. It rolled in the air before smashing into the outer wall of a building. Sparks flew and metal was torn apart. The vehicle was embedded into the wall, emitting black smoke. The anti-gravity engine flickered a few times before it turned off with a hum.

Everyone was dizzy from the crash.

Clutching his head, the burly man crawled up and kicked open the deflated hatch. He saw that the pursuers had already surrounded him, and the two sides of the enemy's vehicle were loaded with live bullets, aiming at the immobile target.

The traffic accident had attracted a lot of spectators, and they all drove their vehicles to watch from afar, forming a circle. However, the pursuers did not seem to mind shooting in the middle of the city, as if they did not care about the security forces on this planet.

Seeing this, everyone in the cabin looked terrified and desperate.

These gray people who ran the black market also did not dare start a battle in the city. However, these people did not have any scruples at all and were even more vicious than them. They were simply lawless brutes.

"I still have three million Enas in my savings. I can't accept this!"

The Lizardman was scared out of his wits. He collapsed to the ground and could not stand up.

At this time, the burly man grabbed his collar and took out a palm-sized metal ball from his arms. He pressed the button on the top of the metal ball, and the ball lit up.

"Don't! This thing will blow up the entire street!"

The Lizardman immediately tried to snatch it back but was kicked to the ground by the burly man.

"Don't be silly. Didn't you bring this bomb just in case? Since they want to kill us, let's see if they will die together with us!"

The burly man had a vicious look on his face. He raised the bomb high and turned around, preparing to shout.

However, right at this moment, the sound of a meteor falling suddenly rang out as it rapidly approached!

Pew! Boom!

A figure shrouded in red flames descended from the sky and kicked out at one of the pursuers, akin to Buddha's Pa… no, Feet.

A huge force burst out, and the carrier plummeted to the ground, exploding into flames.

This figure jumped and landed in the huge pit created by the vehicles of the people in the black market. He gave a thumbs up and a wide-toothed smile as he stood in front of lizardman and company, protecting them.

"Don't be afraid. You're safe now."

Hearing this, everyone put on an uncertain expression. The burly man turned to look at the Lizardman and asked, "You called for reinforcements?"

"No…" The Lizardman looked confused, doubting himself." Did I?"

The burly man's face twitched, and he turned to look at this sudden support. "Who are you? Why did you save us?"

"Don't ask me. I'm just doing a mission. As for who I am, you should recognize this emblem, right?"

This person turned around and showed a symbol on his clothes. Everyone looked at it and shivered.

There was almost no one in the universe who did not recognize this pattern.

"You're from the Black Star Army‽"

"To be precise, I'm one of the Army's Immortals. You can call me Crispy Chicken Wings." This person grinned. He was indeed a player.

Hearing this, everyone was shocked.

Why have the infamous Immortals suddenly come to help? We clearly had no contact with the Black Star Army at all!

"Wait till I get rid of these people. Stay behind me obediently."

At this moment, the pursuers suddenly opened fire, and densely packed bullets rained down on them. The bullets were extremely fast, almost forming a line. As soon as Crispy Chicken Wings spoke, a blue shield popped out, protecting the paralyzed vehicles of the black market.

The next second, the Pugilist flames on Crispy Chicken Wings gathered in the palms of his hands, forming a red energy wave.

Boom!

A blazing red beam of light pulsed outward like a whip, hitting all the vehicles.

The next moment, these vehicles turned into fireworks in the sky and the people within were killed instantly, scaring the crowd away.

To Grade B players, this was a common occurrence. There was no difficulty involved.

Crispy Chicken Wings clapped his hands and chuckled. "Problem solved."

Seeing this, the Lizardman finally had the strength to get up. He snatched the bomb back from the burly man's hands and turned it off, glaring at him before walking toward Crispy Chicken Wings. "You saved my life. How should I thank you?"

"You don't have to thank me. From now on, I'm your boss."

The Lizardman was stunned for a moment before he exclaimed in surprise, "Are you recruiting me to join the Black Star Army?"

"In your dreams. Do you think you can enter the army just because you want to?" Crispy Chicken Wing did not stand on ceremony and rolled his eyes. "What I mean is, I will temporarily take over your black market business. This is an order from the higher-ups. This is the certificate from your black market organization."

As he spoke, he took out his communicator and displayed a document.

Everyone browsed through it, only feeling shock and surprise.

This was a permit that was recognized by the black market organization. The document stated that the three Universal Civilizations had begun to infiltrate the black market on a large scale, and many of the black market channels had already been uprooted. Therefore, in order to maintain the stability of the galactic black market, the black market organization would send some people to temporarily take over the black market and requested for them to cooperate as much as possible.

Usually, black market organizations would not interfere with ordinary black market operators, but this time, they issued a rare notice.

The people who took over the black markets were all members of the Beyond Grade A organizations, and the players of the Black Star Army were among them.

While everyone was still processing, Crispy Chicken Wings opened the interface and looked at his mission list.

Army Transfer Order: Takeover of the Black Market (1)

Mission Introduction: Due to the sanctions of the three Universal Civilizations, the Beyond Grade A Association plans to further control the galactic black market. The Black Star Army has decided to send you to take over and integrate the black market channels of a planet. However, your contact seems to be in danger and needs your help.

Mission Requirements: Rescue the black market operators who are being chased.

This mission is part of a series of related missions. The final reward depends on the mission rating.

Current Mission Status: Completed

This was a mission issued by the Black Star Army not long ago, and many players had accepted it. They split up and went to different planets to take over the local black market. Because the players rarely had the chance to be independent, they found it interesting and refreshing.

Furthermore, compared to exploring the Flickering World, taking over and integrating the black market of a planet had a lot more problems to consider. The mission environment was more complicated, which was more challenging to the players.

This was just a corner of the black market, and the same thing happened on many planets in the various Star Fields.

"The players have already entered the black market. The situation is not bad…"

In the Black Star Palace office, Han Xiao looked at the star map, nodding as he observed the movements of the players.

The Galactic Black Market was currently the focus of the battle between the association and the three Universal Civilizations. The three Universal Civilizations did not personally take part in the battle, and the people they sent to infiltrate the black market were not direct descendants but subordinates of subsidiary organizations. They had already clashed with the many people sent by the Beyond Grade A Association, both sides suffering from casualties.

Among them, the progress of the army was the smoothest. The players were as useful as ever, unlike the other organizations, which could not be as extravagant as the Black Star Army.

Han Xiao gave this mission to the players. It served two purposes, to provide fertilizer for the players and to allow the players to enter the frontlines of the battle and maintain their interest.

Scattering them out on different planets to manage their own black market businesses was akin to letting them be birds flying in the sky, free as the wind. He was also curious about how these players would react.

At this moment, his communicator vibrated. An officer had sent a message.

"Commander, someone is here to visit you. She doesn't have an appointment, but she claims to be an old acquaintance of yours."

Hearing this, Han Xiao raised his brows.

"Someone I know? How close? What's their name?"

"She said her name is Rossellin."

Chapter 1283: Would You Like Another Brother-in-Law?

"Why is she here? And why didn't she tell me?"

Han Xiao was stunned.

This woman was not a good person. She had left the Black Star Army decades ago and followed the Silver Revolutionary Army to cause trouble. Now that she had suddenly returned, no one knew what she wanted.

"Commander, will you see her?"

"…Let's just meet her for a bit."

Han Xiao nodded. He was quite curious about Rossellin's intentions.

After the butterfly effect he caused, the Silver Revolutionary Army basically did not have the chance to evolve into a big version event like in his previous life. He did not know what would happen to this group. Could Rossellin have come to him for help?

While guessing, Han Xiao stood up and walked out of the office. He walked along the corridor to the reception room. On his way to the logistics department, he called Reynold, who was working extremely hard, and brought him to see his sister.

Very quickly, the two of them arrived outside the guest room. The door opened, and they saw Rossellin.

"Long time no see."

Han Xiao casually greeted Rossellin as he sized her up.

It had been many years since they last met, and Rossellin's appearance did not seem to have changed much. She was wearing a dark blue teacher's robe, and her temperament was even calmer than decades ago.

"That's right. It's been so many years, and you've already become a legendary figure in the universe. Even the three Universal Civilizations view you as the most dangerous person. Thinking back to your honeymoon period with the dynasty, it's truly a pity." Rossellin smiled.

Han Xiao sat opposite Rossellin and casually replied, "What's there to be sad about? Different positions will have different problems to consider. The development of any matter always spirals upward, but it's very normal to experience rise and fall."

"But this isn't a spiral rise, right? If not for the Sanctum Revival you created, this era wouldn't have become what it is today. As expected of you, you easily accomplished what I couldn't. Your ability to turn the situation around is much stronger than mine. Don't you feel any sense of achievement?" Rossellin batted her eyes and teased him.

"You're not yet worthy of letting me feel a sense of achievement." Han Xiao smiled.

Rossellin was not angry. She smiled and turned to look at Reynold as though she had just noticed him. She pretended to be surprised and said, "Hey, little brother, you're still alive. I thought you would've died from overworking by now."

Reynold did not know how to respond.

Although you are my sister, if you continue to spout nonsense, do you believe that I won't give you a firm slap?

Han Xiao shook his head and smiled. "Let's not talk about me for now. You, on the other hand, have not made a single move in decades, at most only helping me a little in Modo. How's your so-called career?"

"Nothing much. What you've done has indirectly obstructed our career. What else can we do? But that's none of my business. I've already quit."

Rossellin shrugged with a nonchalant tone, as if she did not care about wasting decades of her time.

The Intelligent Plague incident had consolidated the hearts of the three Universal Civilizations, and the recent sanctions against the Beyond Grade A Association had also received the approval of a large number of ordinary people who hated the strong. The Silver Revolutionary Army could not break the foundation of the ordinary citizens in the three Universal Civilizations, and thus, their career had come to a standstill.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

This woman actually quit the Silver Revolutionary Army… This was out of his expectations.

"So, why did you come back today?"

Hearing this, Rossellin spread her hands out and smiled.

"I can't stay idle. When I lose my job, I have to find a new job. What do you think, O Great Commander? Will you accept me?"

"If I say no, what will you do?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

"Then I can only pester you…" Rossellin rolled her eyes and deliberately acted like she was about to cry. "With our relationship, you can't bear to see me fall into someone else's arms, right?"

"…Speak properly, don't talk about such things." Han Xiao coughed. "Now that the three Universal Civilizations are punishing us, you must have some other reasons for suddenly coming back."

Rossellin clapped her hands twice symbolically before smiling. "I really can't hide it from your eyes. You also know that my goal is to deal with the three Universal Civilizations, but recently, I suddenly realized that joining the association's faction seems to be more promising."

Han Xiao was speechless.

That seemed to be the case. To a certain extent, the Beyond Grade A Association had already achieved a part of the role of Silver Revolutionary Army in his previous life. Now that they had formed an opposing faction with the three Universal Civilizations, the commotion they caused was not much smaller than what the Silver Revolutionary Army caused back then.

However, the Silver Revolutionary Army in this lifetime did not improve at all, which made Rossellin feel that her future was bleak. Thus, she ran back to join her old employer, resorting to another method to deal with the three Universal Civilizations. Her goal did not change, and with her personality, she would definitely do such a thing.

And if this 'soul character' left, the Silver Revolutionary Army would only have two or three little kittens left. There would be no chance to rise up.

This meant that although he did not deliberately target the Silver Revolutionary Army, it seemed like the butterfly effect he triggered indirectly killed them in the end.

So, was Rossellin abandoning the dark to embrace the light?

Han Xiao shook his head before emphasizing his seriousness as he spoke. "…Alright, since you're willing to bear the brunt and return to the army, I can let you in. However, from now on, you can no longer have any contact with the Silver Revolutionary Army. If you leave the army again, even with Reynold around, I won't let you come back. Do you understand?"

He did not mind recruiting Rossellin again. Although this woman's mind was dangerous, her ability was indeed rare and had strategic significance. She was practically a trump card to overthrow someone's rule. It was best to keep such a talent in his hands.

"Alright, I won't leave you this time." Rossellin batted her eyes again.

Reynold frowned when he heard this.

This woman was not quite right. Was she seducing Black Star to make the Army Commander his brother-in-law?

Damn, how shameless!

Han Xiao remained unmoved, standing up as he spoke. "Alright, I'll get someone to arrange your duties. You two have not seen each other for many years, so you should have a lot to talk about. I still have things to do, so I'll take my leave now."

As he spoke, he turned and walked out of the guest room, leaving behind only his shadow.

After watching Han Xiao leave, Reynold turned to look at Rossellin and said with a frown, "Let me warn you, if you come back with bad intentions, I will be the first to catch you!"

"You don't trust me?" Rossellin raised her brows.

"Humph, I know very well what kind of person you are!" Reynold crossed his arms and said expressionlessly, "Also, I advise you to be more respectful to the Army Commander. A subordinate should act like a subordinate!"

"Yo, it's been decades since we last met, and you're so loyal to Black Star?" Rossellin clicked her tongue in wonder. Suddenly, she rolled her eyes, lowered her tone, and chuckled. "How about it? Do you want to have a brother-in-law?"

"What are you doing?" Reynold frowned even more.

"I think a man like Black Star who can turn the universe upside down suits me very well. What do you think?" Rossellin teased.

Reynold snorted in disdain.

"Those who are eyeing Black Star can circle around this base six times. With just you? Go queue up!"

Chapter 1284: Aurora... No, Feidin's Adventure Records

Rossellin's return was just a small interlude, and Han Xiao left it to his subordinates to make arrangements.

After returning to his office, Han Xiao pinned the surveillance of the army players entering the black market before opening the forums to check the response of the players.

The forums were very active, and the posts regarding the controlling of the black market occupied a large number of pages. The situation on every planet was different, with the environment, characters, and events varying, causing the situation that each individual encountered to be unique.

Some people managed to save their targets in time, like Crispy Chicken Wings, obtaining a group of professional assistants that could continue to develop according to the original black market channel. Some players came a step too late and did not manage to connect with the black market personnel. They would have to build a new black market channel from scratch, which was equivalent to them fumbling in the dark. Many players of the army were sharing the situation that they had encountered, and there were many confused requests for help.

A small number of players who had started to come into contact with the black market also shared their experience and insights on the forums. This was because when Han Xiao issued this mission, he had set it as a collective mission with a comprehensive completion rate, depending on the total degree of control over the black market.

Every player's mission results would be calculated into the overall completion rating. Therefore, it was not enough to just complete the mission alone. If the players wanted a higher reward, they needed others to be on equal grounds with them. Thus, many of the pioneers at the black market were happy to share and help the other army players take over the black market. It was a win-win situation for all.

"The current development seems to be more positive than expected. With the model now, the players might inject new energy into the Galactic Black Market and help the black markets in various areas connect with each other."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Due to the fact that they could not be seen in public, there were very few large black market organizations that could cross Star Systems, let alone Star Clusters. Black market managers like Secret Master were even rarer. Most of them were small black market organizations that were limited to one or two Star Zones, akin to local tyrants.

Even though there was a black market organization that managed the black market in name, the overall structure of the Galactic Black Market was still very scattered.

As for the local black market forces, their partnerships were basically fixed over a long period of time. Most people only knew about their own small territory, and it was difficult for them to expand outward. There were many reasons, one of them being that the flow of information between the small black market forces in different regions was limited.

The way Han Xiao saw it, if the players took over the black markets en masse, they could use the information on the forums and private chat channels to become catalysts, becoming the glue of many black market organizations.

With the incentive of cumulative progress of the mission, most players would be more than willing to cooperate with other players. In that case, the regional black markets that were dominated by the army players might have a chance to build a bridge of cooperation with each other, which was much easier than using any normal methods.

In this manner, the goal of 'integrating the Galactic Black Market' that he had proposed to the association back then could be advanced in a quick manner.

"This is a good move. I'll make the best use of the players' characteristics and hit a few birds with one stone…"

Han Xiao's lips curled up. With all his developments, he had already turned into a chess player behind the scenes, and the chessboard was getting bigger and bigger. Now, it was truly akin to the starry sky.

The players still needed more time. Han Xiao closed the forums, took out his encrypted communicator, and called Oathkeeper.

A few seconds later, the communication was connected, and Oathkeeper appeared on the screen.

"Black Star, what's the matter?"

"You know about the recent sanctions, right?"

"Yes, we all watch the news every day." Oathkeeper nodded. "But you only contacted me now. Do you need any help?"

"You can say that. Since the three Universal Civilizations have decided to restrict me, as the only one in control of the Sanctum Revival, I have to retaliate. What they're most afraid of is that there will be too many Beyond Grade As, so it's best to revive some more people to pressure them."

"But we haven't gathered all the keys yet, so there's no way to revive any more…" Oathkeeper was in a difficult position.

"No, the Sanctum Keys are so precious. Even if I gather all of the necessary parts, I won't use one for this reason… I mean to pull out some more Holy Accord members. After all, your side is the reserve of Beyond Grade As in this battle, and now is the time to use the Holy Accord."

Without waiting for Oathkeeper to reply, Han Xiao quickly continued.

"Furthermore, I feel that the three Universal Civilizations are probably trying to see if I can revive any more Beyond Grade As, so it's best to give them a response. The more Beyond Grade As there are, the more uncomfortable the three Universal Civilizations will be, making them feel that the cost of trial and error is too high. Only then will they be more cautious, and similar tests will be decreased in the future."

"There is indeed such a possibility…" Oathkeeper hesitated for a moment. "I don't object on principle, but you'll have to talk to them about who will come out. There should be quite a number of unreliable people in the second batch. It's best to be cautious."

"I know." Han Xiao nodded. He already had a demographic in mind. Among the second batch of Revivors, the neutral unlucky ones who died in the Calamity of the Pinnacles were the best targets. He could also show them to the Super Star Cluster Alliance and increase their confidence in the deal.

Speaking of which, it had been quite a few days, and the list of resources that the Super Star Cluster Alliance promised to compile in exchange for the resurrections had yet to arrive…

Just as this thought appeared in his mind, a notification popped up on his communicator.

Ding! Ding!

Han Xiao opened the interface and saw that it was the list of resources that the Super Star Cluster Alliance had sent over for the Sanctum Revival.

"Hey, speak of the devil. What a coincidence," Han Xiao muttered to himself and nodded at Oathkeeper. "This is probably the situation. I'll talk to the Revivors in a while. Help me convey my intentions in the next few days so that they know what to do. Also, give me a reliable list based on their performance over the past year."

"Alright then."

Oathkeeper felt weird.

They were clearly partners, but he felt like he was the subordinate instead…

After giving some more instructions, Han Xiao ended the communication and browsed through the list the Super Star Clusters sent.

He only offered ten slots for the first batch, but the Super Star Cluster Alliance was generous and took out quite a number of good items. They were basically all Universal Treasures and Gold Grade blueprints.

All the Super Star Cluster civilizations were after all victors of the exploration era war, and they had fought many against civilizations. While they might not be as rich as the three Universal Civilizations, they were still well off, not lacking in Universal Treasures or Gold Grade blueprints.

However, Han Xiao had hidden the benefits he had gotten from Jayz's treasure and the Sanctums very well. People who were not familiar with him would not know about his current foundation, so the list of resources that the Super Star Cluster Alliance made with confidence did not catch his eye at all.

Han Xiao chose three of the more attractive offers and gave them three slots. He then returned the rest to the Super Star Cluster.

Not long after the message was sent, the Super Star Cluster Alliance contacted him.

"Black Star, your appetite is too big. Don't push your luck. We're already very sincere!"

Hearing this, Han Xiao secretly smirked.

Who were they talking to? Did they not know who had the upper hand?

"I'll decide if you're sincere or not. There are seven more slots. If you don't want them, forget it. Don't buy them if you have the guts."

"…We'll buy it."

"By the way, payment first."

"…You win!"

The contact from the Super Star Cluster Alliance went offline.

There was nothing he could do about it. Having a monopoly of the market meant he could be that domineering. One could complain about it, but they had to buy what they needed.

After rebuffing the contact, Han Xiao turned off the virtual screen and was about to continue studying the Gold Grade blueprints in the workshop.

However, at this moment, his private communicator suddenly received a message from Aurora.

"There's a huge discovery. Come quickly!"

Han Xiao was stunned for a moment before he turned curious.

Aurora was still traveling with Feidin, and they had not contacted each other for quite some time. Usually, she would not contact him if something happened. Now that she had suddenly called him, he did not know what was going on.

However, Feidin was wearing an external Lucky Halo. No matter what happened, Han Xiao felt that he would not be surprised.

…

"By the way… where did you bring me?"

Inside the spaceship, Aurora swallowed her saliva and looked outside the porthole with her eyes wide open.

"I don't know either. It suddenly became like this outside…"

Feidin looked in the same direction with shock.

The two of them were originally piloting the ship leisurely in the universe, but then the environment outside suddenly changed, and the starry sky disappeared, turning into a pitch-black space without a trace of starlight. It was as if they had passed through some barrier, entering an unknown territory.

However, the spaceship's alarm did not react at all, nor did the monitor show any abnormalities.

The two of them were shocked and immediately controlled the spaceship to retreat. However, this pitch-black space seemed to have no concept of distance. Even though the spaceship had accelerated to its hyperdrive state, it remained in its original position and could not leave this vast area of space.

The reason they discovered this was because there was a single coordinate system reference object in this pitch-black space, which was also the source of their surprise.

Looking out the window, they saw a broken mechanical body floating quietly in this dark space. Its size was terrifying, many times larger than the Mechanical Deity they had seen before.

Compared to it, the spaceship was akin to a speck of dust on a normal person's body.

The structure of this body was similar to that of an upright organism. Its flesh and blood were intertwined with machinery, and its skeleton was crisscrossed with metal. However, it was severely damaged, riddled with holes.

What shocked Aurora the most was that her Esper Ability actually felt a weak life force from this body.

This thing… seemed to be alive!

Chapter 1285: Shocking Origins

Buzz!

At this time, the Throne in the cabin that was collecting dust suddenly flashed, and Han Xiao appeared.

The helmet opened, revealing Han Xiao's face. He asked in a curious tone, "What important discovery have you made that's worth calling me here?"

"You're an expert Mechanic, quick, take a look at the big guy outside." Aurora pointed outside the window.

Actually, there was no need for her to tell him. The moment Han Xiao asked the question, he noticed the abnormality of their environment. Following Aurora's finger, he immediately saw this strange body.

"Yo, it's huge! Flesh and machine are fused together. It's a little like grafting, but it doesn't seem to be the case… What is this? Where did you guys find it?"

Han Xiao was shocked.

He did not know what this thing was either. It looked to be many times larger than the normal size of his Mechanical Deity. Its body was covered in wounds, as though it had experienced all kinds of cosmic disasters.

"This is what we suddenly encountered. This space seems to be a sealed domain…" Feidin explained.

Han Xiao nodded as he stroked his chin.

"From the sound of it, this body seems to have been maintaining a strange domain, and you guys accidentally barged in. If it's mechanical technology, it should be a high-level usage of spatial technology, creating a fixed field of folded space around the body or changing some physical constants in this field. This is high-end technology."

"But there's no reaction from the spaceship's detector." Aurora patted the control panel.

"Let me see…"

Han Xiao checked and realized that all the devices were operating normally. His eyes gleamed.

"Hmm, either the device is affected by virtual interference or the other party has some kind of amazing concealment technology. Either way, the technology is extraordinary…"

Aurora's spaceship had gathered quite a lot of Jayz's technological treasures, but for it to have been blinded, Han Xiao naturally took it seriously.

"Could it be a Space Wonder?" Feidin was curious.

"Don't jump to a conclusion so quickly…" Han Xiao waved his hand and took over the controls. "Since the spaceship can't retreat, let's see if we can approach this big guy."

"Are you sure?" Aurora was a little hesitant. "I felt a weak life signal from it, but no matter how I tried to send it a message, it did not respond…"

"This big guy is alive?"

Han Xiao was stunned for a moment before his interest was piqued.

He knew Aurora's ability very well and would not make any mistakes.

Initially, he had thought that this was the remains of a gigantic mechanical body thrown around by some civilization or Mechanic who did not care about public morals. However, since this mechanical body was alive, things became much more interesting…

"Let's go take a look."

Han Xiao only hesitated for two seconds before making a decision. He controlled the spaceship to move forward.

As expected, this dark area seemed to only allow them to advance but not retreat. The spaceship slowly approached the target.

The closer they got, the stronger the contrast between their sizes. The details of the body were enlarged in their vision, making them feel how small they were.

After a while, the spaceship stopped at a long and narrow hole on the finger of the mechanical body. It was like a huge cave that extended thousands of meters into the interior.

The hatch opened, and the few of them got out of the spaceship, stepping onto the rugged ground.

The flesh and machinery beneath their feet were intertwined with each other, making it unsuitable for normal walking.

Han Xiao squatted down and inserted his fingers into a piece of flesh to experience the sensation it gave. He then observed the muscles and veins before nodding.

"Muscles, tendons, and fat. They all look like normal biological tissue, not artificial biochemical tendons…"

As he said that, he exerted some force with his fingers, and a little bit of blood seeped out from the muscle.

Han Xiao looked up and saw that there were solidified bloodstains all around the flesh and blood tissues. They looked black and splattered outward, like blood that was suddenly sprayed out by a slash.

His eyes flashed, and he suddenly thought of Old Man Manison's criminal technology. This body was a little similar to a criminal's biological modification and biochemical prosthetics.

At this moment, Feidin said, "Black Star, I'm not feeling too good…"

Han Xiao and Aurora turned around, only to see Feidin holding onto his chest with his brows furrowed.

"What's wrong?"

Han Xiao's heart tightened.

He reached out and poked Feidin, triggering the combat information. After seeing it clearly, his expression changed slightly.

In Feidin's status bar, a negative status called [Dissolution] appeared. The effect would take 0.01% to 0.5% of his health, energy, and stamina every second. However, under the influence of his Lucky Halo, Feidin only suffered the weakest negative effects.

Why didn't he have such a reaction before? Could it be that this happened after entering this body?

Han Xiao opened the interface and realized that he did not even have the [Dissolution] status. He did not have any notification about judgment being made as well.

Could it be that this effect only targeted those below Beyond Grade A? Was it limited to life forms or dead objects?

He turned to look at the spaceship parked at the side, and after a simple inspection, he realized that the exterior armor of the spaceship was showing signs of rusting and dissolving. The material used to make this spaceship was extremely tough, and even a portion of the Black Star alloy was mixed in. It had its own recovery ability, but even this was not immune to the [Dissolution] state…

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes as a hypothesis started to form.

"This area can only be entered but not left. Whether it's a living thing or an inanimate object, everything will start to dissolve upon entering the body. Interesting, this feels like a flytrap. This is probably a trap that drifts through the universe, and those who accidentally bump into it will not be able to escape and will become its nutrients…"

Luckily, there was a healer with sufficient power in the team. Otherwise, it would have been slightly troublesome.

He signaled Aurora to treat Feidin while he took out a metal needle and stabbed it deep into the flesh on the wall, attempting to cause damage. If this big guy was an individual, it should be able to display combat information on the interface.

Ding!

The next moment, a notification popped up on the interface.

Han Xiao opened it, and his expression changed.

The level, species, and abilities of this body were all question marks. Only its name was not a question mark, but there was no difference. It was called [Unknown Polymerized Entity].

This thing's level is actually so high‽

Even if it was Manison or Sorokin, who had a higher level than him, he could still see a portion of the other party's information. The information of this body was almost all question marks, which could only mean that the difference in level was too big. In the explored universe, Han Xiao estimated that only Wuornos had reached such a level.

"Where did this thing come from…"

Han Xiao's curiosity grew stronger.

He really did not have any impression of this body in his memories. Logically speaking, such a strange thing should not have been unknown in his previous life. He did not know if it was not discovered or hidden by someone.

Han Xiao did not have time to care about Aurora and Feidin, focusing on studying the thing. He tore off a lump of flesh from the ground, broke off a few mechanical parts, and then activated the material detector in his mechanical suit to scan and analyze them.

Not long after, the two analysis reports were shown.

The first was the analysis result of the mechanical parts. It showed that its microscopic structure was very novel. There was no matching material in the database, which proved that the material of this mechanical body seemed to be composed of some unknown alloy.

The second document was an analysis of the flesh sample. No matching biological genes were detected, which proved that the source of the flesh sample was most likely not a known species in the explored universe. However, the existence of the Super Gene was detected from it, which was highly compatible with the Mechanic class. Although the cell activity was extremely weak, it also seemed to contain extremely weak electromagnetic energy.

Han Xiao had a theory, immediately tearing off a few more chunks of flesh to test. Every single one of them had Super genes, and they were all Mechanic cells.

"The flesh and blood came from Mechanics…"

Han Xiao recalled the size of this body, and his face twitched.

If the flesh and blood of the body belonged to the same person, it would be fine. But if it came from different individuals… How many Mechanic bodies did it take to construct such a large body?

"Why don't we test it out?"

Han Xiao shook his head and weighed the flesh in his hands. After hesitating for a while, he activated the [Bold Explorer] skill.

This skill was useless against the character itself, but this body seemed to be different. A piece of flesh that had already been separated could very likely pass the judgment.

As expected, the next moment, the skill took effect.

Buzz!

The world in front of Han Xiao suddenly changed, and images that he had never seen before began to flash back.

It was as if a starry sky had opened up in front of them, and an incomparably glorious galactic civilization appeared before their eyes. As fleets traveled through the starry sky, the territory expanded outward. Planet after planet turned into colonial areas, and cities rose from the desolate planets. Countless spaceships came and went among the planets, and it looked like a prosperous civilization.

However, the next moment, a series of wormholes suddenly appeared in the sky, and an unknown fleet invaded. The flames of war spread to this peaceful civilization, and blood, slaughter, and screams replaced the original prosperity.

As the invader advanced, dark green roots extended out of the void and pierced the planets of the invaded like straws. These planets melted, shrunk, and died at a rate visible to the naked eye. In the end, they all turned into liquid nutrients and were sucked away by the roots, leaving nothing behind.

"This is…"

Han Xiao's pupils constricted.

He was all too familiar with this scene. It was the same as the World Tree War Version!

The World Tree Civilization had invaded this unknown civilization!

Before he could analyze further, the illusion in front of him changed and arrived in a universe.

A large number of Mechanics were gathered there, sitting cross-legged in the middle of the starry sky. Behind them were their own mechanical armies, forming a magnificent formation. Around them were ring-shaped mechanical devices that covered the entire area.

A Mechanical Deity suddenly appeared in the middle of the crowd, releasing a strange energy wave that enveloped the entire area, resonating with the ring-shaped mechanical device.

All of a sudden, the bodies of all the Mechanics in the area exploded, turning into pure flesh and blood, mixing together with their respective armies and then turning into a torrent, pouring into the Mechanical Deity in the center… The size of this Mechanical Deity grew larger and larger, eventually turning into a colossal body. Its flesh and metal fused perfectly, and its appearance was like an indomitable mechanical prosthetic giant!

However, before Han Xiao could be surprised, the scene changed again. The gigantic mechanical body that was still intact a second ago suddenly became tattered, as though it had gone through countless battles. Its appearance was very familiar. It was the mechanical body that Han Xiao and the others had met.

This damaged machine seemed to have been scrapped. It lost all its momentum and slowly drifted in the universe. In the end, it was captured by a huge black hole and swallowed, disappearing without a trace.

At this time, his perspective zoomed out once again. The unknown civilization's territory had completely turned into darkness, almost cleaner than the desolate universe belt.

The fleet of the World Tree Civilization was like a customer who had eaten his fill. They retreated in satisfaction, leaving behind an empty universe.

This was the last scene of the illusion.

Han Xiao shivered. The effect of the skill disappeared, and his vision returned to normal.

His eyes were still filled with shock as he muttered to himself, "I seem to have discovered something incredible…"

Chapter 1286: World Tree's Shadow

The information brought by [Bold Explorer] was huge. Han Xiao was both shocked and curious.

What he knew about the World Tree Civilization was only limited to the information available during the war in his previous life. As for the detailed history of the World Tree Civilization, he only knew it briefly, mainly because the information the players in his previous life knew was also quite limited.

However, he did know the basic situation. The growth of the World Tree Civilization was basically filled with war. They kept exploring the universe, conquering and destroying countless civilizations and races. The three Universal Civilizations were not the first to be discovered; they were not special from the World Tree's perspective, just more prey on their path of conquest.

Through the images he saw earlier, Han Xiao roughly figured out the origin of this mechanical body.

This unknown civilization should have been the ruler of a certain area in the unexplored universe. According to what he saw, its scale was not inferior to any one of the three Universal Civilizations. The three Universal Civilizations only ruled this area of the explored universe. Other civilizations existed in the wide unexplored universe, exploring further and expanding their territory just like the three Universal Civilizations.

Although the explored universe had already entered the galactic society era, in an infinitely bigger perspective, the entire universe was still in the 'exploration era'.

In the past, the World Tree Civilization discovered this unknown civilization. Hence, they traveled through space and invaded, stirring up the flames of war, biting off their territory bit by bit… The way the World Tree Civilization invaded was not just simply occupying the target civilization's territory. Most of the time, it devoured the enemy's planets completely. Therefore, lost territories were almost unretrievable.

The opponent had to either defend against the World Tree Civilization's attacks or yield their territory gradually, losing resource-rich planets that would become the World Tree's fertilizer, forming a vicious cycle. In Han Xiao's previous life, the three Universal Civilizations faced this exact situation.

Clearly, this unknown civilization was no match for the World Tree in terms of military power. Hence, it tried to find a breakthrough in the form of individual strength. Through some kind of unique fusing technology with Beyond Grade As as the core, countless Mechanics willingly sacrificed themselves, hoping to create an even stronger individual being.

Although the illusions Han Xiao saw were the only source of information, he had a feeling that this unknown civilization's goal should be to artificially create a Super that exceeded the Beyond Grade A territory!

However, the illusions did not show if it worked. All he knew was that the mechanical body was defeated, fell into a black hole, and disappeared without falling into the hands of the World Tree. This unknown civilization was destroyed in the end, devoured completely along with its territory, not leaving any traces behind. It became another victim of the World Tree Civilization.

"Such a horrifying enemy…"

Han Xiao mourned for this unknown civilization for a few seconds and then sighed.

God only knew how many revolutions and disasters a civilization had to experience and overcome to grow to the universal level. After conquering all these obstacles step by step and creating a glorious civilization, the inheritance and hard work of countless generations were destroyed so easily, disappearing in the universe forever.

Countless years of hard work vanished overnight.

Although he had witnessed the terror of the World Tree Civilization before, seeing this again, Han Xiao still felt pressured.

If not because he knew how horrifying the World Tree was, he would not have done everything he could to delay the World Tree's arrival. Even though he had many trump cards he never had in his previous life, he still could not say that they would win this war with full confidence.

"Now's not the time to worry about this. What's going to come will come sooner or later. It's just a matter of time…"

Han Xiao shook his head, exhaled softly, and put his focus back on this mechanical body.

"This big guy's level is very high, probably above four hundred. But it doesn't feel like it has reached the higher territory to me…"

Han Xiao pondered.

Although he had yet to enter the higher Grade, he already had some ideas and knew that the God's Trait Transformation was something he had to overcome.

The method this unknown civilization used was to forcefully stimulate quality change using quantity and complete the evolution. Therefore, they sacrificed tons of Mechanics. However, the life hierarchy of this mechanical body did not seem to evolve.

Even though Han Xiao could not understand the principles of the technology this unknown civilization used for the time being, it did not stop him from intuitively feeling that this was the wrong path. It was more of a bet than an actual attempt.

Therefore, this thing's total level was most likely not an accurate indicator of its strength. It was like having many 'subclasses', which gave it a lot of levels, but its actual strength did not undergo a revolution.

Nonetheless, it was definitely an improvement. It might have touched the edge of the higher territory… Even so, it was still beat up this bad by the World Tree. It was indeed quite horrifying.

"This mechanical body contains the essence of tons of Mechanics of an unknown civilization. I should be able to derive a lot of new technology from it, especially this unique fusing technology that's somewhat similar to the Felon technology but quite different in its own way…"

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

The value of this mechanical body might be on par with Jayz's technology treasure. It was filled with the technical essence of different Mechanics.

Among them, the most valuable should be this fusing technology. This exact technology might not be useful to him, but it could give him some insights to come up with something new.

While his thoughts were spinning, Aurora, who was standing to the side, saw that Han Xiao did not say anything despite studying it for quite a long time. She could not help but curiously ask, "Any discovery?"

Han Xiao nodded, smiled, and said, "You've really brought me a big surprise this time."

Then, he gave Feidin a meaningful look with an even more content expression.

Feidin was really his lucky star!

He guessed that this mechanical body should have drifted in the universe and finally fallen into the explored universe through a wormhole.

This Star Field's name was Blackhole Edge. It was a place where large wormholes frequently appeared, so things like this were not rare.

In Han Xiao's previous life, this mechanical body was never discovered. However, it might not have been because no one found it. It was also possible that it was not thrown into the explored universe by the wormhole. This should have something to do with the butterfly effect he caused. After all, wormholes were always very random.

Now, however, Feidin had come across this big guy… Han Xiao could not help but be amazed by Feidin's luck. He was like a walking portable 'adventure trigger'.

Aurora came over and stuck around Han Xiao to keep asking him about what he discovered. Han Xiao thought about it, skipped most of the information, and explained the nature of this mechanical body ambiguously, acting as if he discovered this information through technological analysis.

"This means that this big guy should now be asleep because it's severely injured?" Aurora's eyes spun, and she said with anticipation, "Should I send in life force and help him recover?"

As soon as she said that, before Han Xiao replied, a notification popped up on the interface.

You have triggered the hidden mission [Visitor from Afar]!

Mission Introduction: You accidentally discovered the wreckage of a unique mechanical body from an unknown civilization. There seems to be a weak sign of life in this wreckage. It should have a lot of secrets, and you might be able to acquire some valuable intelligence from it.

Mission Requirements: Repair the mechanical body and awaken it.

Basic Reward: 5 Billion EXP, 2 Random Rewards, and 1 Character Summon Card.

Bonus rewards will be given based on the Mission Rating. Mission Rating is given based on the extent of the mechanical body's repairs.

Remarks: This mission might affect the developments of some events and cause unpredictable impacts. Please choose carefully.

"A mission?" Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

This mechanical body was unconscious and heavily damaged. Who knew if it still had an individual consciousness? If he asked Aurora to heal it, it might create many unstable factors.

The unknown impact mentioned in the remarks of the mission should consist of mainly two things. Firstly, the World Tree's information might be leaked all over the world by this guy. Secondly, this guy's strength was unknown, which might be a threat.

Furthermore, if this mechanical body regained its ability to move, how was he going to reverse-engineer it? Of course, studying an immobile object was the easiest. He could do it in any position he wanted!

Whether emotional or logical, Han Xiao did not plan to have his plan disrupted by this mission. He shook his head.

"No need, keep it this way. I'm going to study this thing thoroughly first."

"Alright then, call me when you need me." Aurora did not mind.

Although she was the first one to discover this mechanical body, she did not mind letting Han Xiao decide what to do with it. It was a sensitive time, and she did not want to cause trouble for Han Xiao.

Han Xiao nodded. He came to the edge of this long wound and tried opening the secondary dimensional army box outside it.

Mechanical Force lightning bolts jumped around like dancing golden snakes, opening a gate. Tons of mechanical soldiers flew out. This strange area did not seal up the secondary dimensions too like when he was in the Celestial Star Alliance dimension.

Very soon, these mechanical soldiers spread out like ants moving on the surface of this mechanical body, searching for the core that maintained this territory.

Han Xiao planned to store this mechanical body first in case someone discovered it while it drifted in space. This territory sealed up usual movements but not the quantum network, otherwise Aurora would not have been able to send him a message so easily.

Scanning reports were sent to Han Xiao one after another. Not long after, the entire mechanical body was scanned. The mechanical devices in most areas were no longer working, except for a small area at its chest. One of the devices in it was what activated this territory.

The mechanical soldier rapidly dug a hole in the mechanical body's chest and turned off the device from inside.

Buzz!

The next moment, the territory was shut down. The black space around disappeared and returned to the normal cosmic space.

"It's deactivated."

Han Xiao nodded, summoned the engineering machinery army, planted a directional wormhole generator, and set the target coordinates as the mechanical life civilization in the Black Star Army's territory.

After a while, an enormous wormhole appeared. The mechanical troops pushed the mechanical body into the wormhole. A few minutes later, Han Xiao received a message from Psionic Prime saying he had received the cargo.

Then, Han Xiao retrieved all of his troops, cleaned up any traces, turned to look at Aurora, and said with a smile, "Your discovery this time is very helpful to me. You've done a great job."

Aurora's eyes sparkled. "Do I get a reward then?"

"What do you want? I will grant it as long as it's not too overboard."

"Hmm… I haven't decided yet. I'll tell you when I have." Aurora giggled.

"Alright then, take it as I owe you a favor."

Han Xiao shook his head, swapped into the King, and teleported home right away. He could not wait to study the technological secrets of the mechanical body.

He had a feeling that he might be surprised by what he would obtain from this mechanical body.

Aurora and Feidin remained in place and looked at each other.

After half a minute, Aurora softly said, "What are you looking at? Go to the ship."

"…Are we going to continue traveling?" Feidin's lips twitched.

"Of course! We've helped Black Star again this time. We might discover more things!'

Aurora was thrilled.

She had lived too long under the protection of Black Star and Hila. She always wanted to help Han Xiao. Now that she finally had, she felt full of motivation and passion for adventures.

"Can you swap me with Nero?" Feidin said weakly.

He had already followed Aurora for more than a year. If he had known he would be kidnapped by Aurora like this for so long, he would not have separated with Chen Xing back then.

In the past, they spent all the time together in his mind, but now it had become a long-distance relationship…

If he had to describe how it felt, he would say it was a decision he regretted very much!

Chapter 1287: One Arrow

Planet Apostle was located at the center of the Sigma Star System. It was an enormous planet and the home of Black Star's mechanical life civilization. Crisscrossing mechanical buildings filled its surface, and mega buildings were everywhere. It was full of the sense of industrial beauty.

As the mother planet of the mechanical life civilization, it went through modifications many times. The mechanical lives emptied the insides of the entire planet using planetary engineering technology, replacing the majority of the planet with metal. It had become almost fully mechanical; the Planet Apostle was basically a portable galactic war fortress. With the population of the machinery civilization rocketing, the size of the planet also increased. At the start, it was only normal-sized; now, it was gigantic.

Four enormous satellites surrounded Planet Apostle. They were mainly used as galactic mega machinery by the mechanical lives.

At this time, an enormous wormhole crack appeared beside one of the satellites. A mechanical army dragged the gigantic unknown mechanical body out like ants.

Streams of light flew out from Planet Apostle and hovered not far from the mechanical body. It was the Apostle Weapons, including Psionic Prime.

With the increase of Han Xiao's technology level, these Apostle Weapons also actively updated their body parts time and again. They looked very different from before. If their original appearances were like ordinary free players, they now looked like whale players.

At this time, a flash of light flickered beside Psionic Prime. Han Xiao arrived through teleportation. The various Apostle Weapons had received word earlier and all greeted him.

Light flickered in Psionic Prime's electronic eyes. He looked at this mechanical body, and a virtual screen with a curious emote appeared on his head as he asked monotonously, "Lord, what is this?"

"A mechanical wreckage that contains unknown technology. It's for my study. I'm leaving it with you for the time being. I don't want too many people to see it, so I can't put it in Black Star Palace," Han Xiao replied.

Psionic Prime nodded. "I'll have a secret lab built just to store this mechanical body. Should I document it now?"

"Hmm, go ahead. This big guy's name will be SWY-001 from now on."

Han Xiao casually gave it a code. There was no special meaning to 'SWY'. It was just the initials of the Pinyin for 'no idea what this is'. He felt this code name relayed the idea very clearly and decided to use this code for anything unknown in the future he came across.

While SWY-001 was being transported, Han Xiao turned and took a look at the machinery civilization and nodded in his mind.

After developing for about eight decades, with the army providing resources, the machinery civilization expanded tremendously in the Sigma Star System, displaying their galactic industrial level of growth. They achieved self-sufficiency and were thriving. Plus, its population was exploding; it had already become one of the important sources of army staff for Han Xiao.

Even without the bonuses of his Mechanical Force, the machinery civilization was more than capable of dealing with an ordinary Star System civilization. After all, the biggest advantages of machinery civilizations were their highly efficient resources distribution, highly united mindsets, and close to zero need for reproductive and entertainment activities. Yet, they would not come across negative societal problems like normal civilizations would. Everyone in the civilization was a perfect soldier. It could be said that the industrial system of machinery civilizations was made for war.

Han Xiao could not help but think of the Black Spirit Race, which was developing in the neighboring Ednea Star System. They also had a hive mindset that allowed them to possess the ability to distribute resources extremely efficiently, learn the technological skill tree collectively at an incredible speed, and come up with new directions for their technology at the same time. They were also developing extremely rapidly; they had already started to send their people into the galaxy and were transforming into a Star System civilization.

With the astonishing learning ability they possessed because of the mental network, the Black Spirit Race raised many scientists and had already provided a lot of talents to the logistics department and the Super Academy.

However, due to the differences on the individual level, the Black Spirit Race took a path that varied from the war machine path of the machinery civilization. It created a new culture. Comparatively, the Black Spirit Race was more recognized as a civilization by the galactic society.

Both civilizations were growing rapidly. With these two civilizations hand in hand, the Black Star Army's self-sufficiency ability was quite outstanding. Han Xiao was rather satisfied with the growth of the two civilizations. They only spent decades catching up to the standard of a Star System civilization, which was astounding.

Although this was partly because of the Black Star Army's full resources and technological support, under the same circumstances, Planet Aquamarine was still very far from becoming a Star System civilization.

"Comparisons sure hurt. Planet Aquamarine probably has no other advantages other than having bred many talents…"

While he was sighing, the engineering team finally transported all of SWY-001 over. The directional wormhole then spun, shrunk, and disappeared.

Han Xiao focused his mind and ordered the mechanical army to quickly build a lab around SWY-001.

The Galactic engineering technology was very efficient. In a short time, the brief structure of a gigantic lab was already built that wrapped around SWY-001.

"Let me see what treasure lies within you…"

With a delighted mood, Han Xiao walked into the research area and could not wait to summon all kinds of research devices. He instantly threw himself into the reverse engineering process.

The first step he took was to search the memory module of SWY-001. Very soon, he discovered a damaged memory chip module and an enormous organ with brain tissue. However, be it the mechanical technology or the biological technology, they were all beyond his expertise.

Han Xiao made the mechanical assistants take out the memory chip, placed it into a specially made data analysis device, and started reading the information inside it. At the same time, he also ordered another group of assistants to bring out a needle-shaped cable and push it into the pale brain fluid of the organ. It then started to read the memories stored within.

Very soon, reports appeared on the screen. Due to the fact that this mechanical body was created by fusing many Mechanics, the memory module seemed to contain the life experience of all these Mechanics who sacrificed themselves. The memory files of SWY-001 were heavily damaged and contained tons of meaningless information, so the analysis was quite slow.

Han Xiao had a few research targets. One was to directly obtain the blueprint knowledge of these Mechanics through digging deeper into the memory module. If successful, it would save him a ton of time, and he would not have to reverse engineer all the parts of SWY-001's body.

Letting the device continue to read the information, Han Xiao searched and found the master artificial intelligence control module. There was a very high possibility that it contained the logs of all this mechanical body's functions. It was basically like an instruction manual for him.

However, the master artificial intelligence control module was protected by a virtual firewall that used the basic code of this unknown civilization, which was different from the galactic society's virtual technology. He also had to break it down to the fundamentals like with the Virtual Mutiny Virus from the Intelligent Plague.

This was not difficult for Han Xiao now; it only had to take his time.

According to SWY-001's traits, it was very possible it had two consciousnesses. The soul consciousness that was sleeping in the biological brain and the artificial intelligence consciousness stored in the mechanical memory chip. Therefore, as long as he could penetrate the firewall and rewrite its artificial intelligence, he might be able to brainwash it.

After all, Han Xiao had learned the Felon technology, so he was no stranger to something like this.

While he was being busy, a notification suddenly popped up on the interface.

You have acquired some insights from the current research.

+16.4% Unique Talent Progress.

Current Progress: 61.1%.

"Progress for my Unique Talent? Today is really my lucky day!"

Han Xiao's movements paused, and his eyes sparkled.

In the past decades, he had only triggered progress for his Unique Talent three times. Now its progress finally increased again. Had this notification not popped up, he might have forgotten about it.

During the version update, his EXP inventory was tight, so he did not use Awakening Points to progress his Unique Talent development. However, since the players had returned, he would consider taking this route.

Nonetheless, Promotion was his priority now. Han Xiao did not plan to use his EXP in other areas; he planned to accumulate enough for his Promotion before using the remaining EXP to increase the levels of his abilities and obtain Awakening Points.

After all, he did not know what the requirement of stepping into the higher territory was and had decided long ago to increase his Energy Rank as much as possible before his next Promotion. The God's Trait Transformation was one route; acquiring another Unique Talent was not bad too.

…

Having obtained SWY-001, Han Xiao's research focus shifted. He spent most of his time analyzing SWY-001 in the lab, using some leisure time to speak to the Holy Accord members one by one, convincing some of them to only appear in public when the time was right.

Meanwhile, in the outside world, the three Universal Civilizations and the Beyond Grade A Association did not continue fighting on the surface. However, their fight in the black market became more and more intense as time went on. The players who took over the various areas of the black market received challenges time and again. Most people overcame these obstacles by working together and slowly pushing the progress of uniting the black market.

In the Endless Nebulae, at a certain transit station planet in the Didora Star System…

Kaching… kaching…

The sound of footsteps that sounded like someone was stepping on shattered glass echoed in a dark room.

Army Commander's Big PP leaned against the wall. His body was covered in wounds, and a puddle of blood had formed under his feet. He was in the heavily injured and immobile state; all he could do was open his eyes wide and glare in the direction the footsteps came from.

Very soon, the footsteps approached. The outline of a large silhouette gradually became clear under the dim lights. It was a man holding a blood-colored mechanical heavy axe that was dripping with blood.

Behind him was a mess. The floor was covered in corpses, and blood was splattered everywhere. The walls were riddled with bullet holes, and tons of shells and metal fragments scattered across the ground. An intense battle seemed to have happened here.

This was a base in the black market that had been taken over by Army Commander's Big PP not long ago and had started to operate properly.

However, today, one man had come and single-handedly destroyed this black market channel, killing every single person in the base. Army Commander's Big PP was the only one left alive. He had been killed many times and depleted his revival count. He was completely powerless because…

This man was a Calamity Grade!

The mechanical suited warrior stopped before Army Commander's Big PP and opened his helmet, showing a face covered in brown scales like a pangolin with the face of a man. He said coldly, "You're the last…"

"Dafis, we never had problems in the past. Why are you doing this‽ Were you hired by the three Universal Civilizations' subsidiary organizations?" Army Commander's Big PP clenched his teeth.

Having operated the black market for quite some time, he knew about the organizations around. This pangolin looking guy in front of him was the leader of a renowned civilian armed force, a Calamity Grade Mechanical Pugilist!

Hearing this, Dafis giggled with mockery.

"Do I have to tell you before killing you?"

"You arrogant prick! You destroyed my mission. I'll remember you, so just you wait!" Army Commander's Big PP clenched his teeth and snarled angrily.

"What? You want to take revenge? As a Grade B Super? Just because you're a so-called Immortal?"

Dafis' face was cold. He was unaffected.

Then, he slowly raised the heavy axe in his hand and said coldly, "You're too weak. It doesn't matter how many lives you have… It's your honor to die by my hand."

As he said that, the axe slashed down, and blood spilled everywhere.

This time, Army Commander's Big PP did not revive again. He had used all of his revives for these six days.

Seeing this, Dafis turned around and walked away without turning back, leaving only corpses behind.

Army Commander's Big PP was forced to log out immediately and could not log in again for one day. He could only access the forums.

"F*ck, you forced me to do this!"

Army Commander's Big PP was filled with rage.

He had worked hard to take over this part of the black market, but now that it had been destroyed by a Calamity Grade, his mission was over. He could only start again in another area.

The more he thought about it, the angrier he got!

Filled with flames of fury, he could not take it anymore. He clenched his teeth, opened up the group chat on the forums, and said in the army channel, "My black market got destroyed by a Calamity Grade! Brothers, we've kept a low profile for so long. Anyone interested in fighting a boss and earning some glory for the army commander? I'm willing to pay!"

The channel remained silent for a moment, then messages filled the screen like a waterfall. The things they were saying were all similar.

Who?

Where?

When?

How much?

With one arrow shot into the sky, millions of warriors answered the call!

Chapter 1288: Guild Crusade

The post about fighting a Calamity Grade became popular very quickly on the forums. As the players' strength kept growing, they started eyeing up the Calamity Grades. Now that someone had brought it up, it immediately triggered the impulses tons of players had suppressed in their hearts.

The last time they killed a Calamity Grade was in Version 3.0 during a big operation organized by the army. After that, the army never organized anything like it. The post received a lot of responses.

However, as the public stargates everywhere were closed to all Beyond Grade A organizations, most players displayed their regret of not being able to help due to distance issues. After all, most people still had to look after their own black markets. Plus, this was only a proposal of a player, not a big mission, so it had limited rewards. As such, most people were only willing to show support on the forums.

However, there was also a group of people who were strongly interested in this matter.

In the base, Jupiter closed the private chat window on the interface, turned around to look at the room of pillars and elites of the Guild of Gods, and nodded firmly.

"I've already spoken to that player. We'll be in charge of this operation. The boss' activity area is the Didora Star System of the Endless Nebulae, not far from us… We happen to have many guild members nearby operating the black markets, so it'll be easy to dispatch them."

The guild's pillar Poseidon hesitated and asked, "This will affect the mission progress of many guild members, won't it? Plus, this is not even a mission. Is it worth it for us to put in this much effort?"

Jupiter nodded heavily. "Of course! This is an amazing opportunity to gain fame. Our club hasn't achieved much in the last few Pro Leagues. If we can make some achievements on our side and increase the popularity of the club, everyone will get a bonus!"

The Guild of Gods guild was the professional guild under the Temple of God club. As their professional team did not achieve good results on the professional scene, the guild had not had a great time in the past few versions. All the fame was grabbed by Dynasty, Long Sky, and Rivervale.

As versions changed, the guilds accumulated more and more strength. They started having ambitions for things they never dared to think of in the past. If they could eliminate a Calamity Grade, the club would also benefit from it.

"Are you sure it'll be effective? The players already killed a Calamity Grade in Version 3.0. It won't be as sensational to do it again, will it?" Poseidon was hesitant.

"Stupid! How did that Atimo die in Version 3.0? It was a faction event organized by the Black Star Army. Way too many people participated, so no one got famous because of it. However, if our guild kills a Calamity Grade on our own, it will be completely different! It'll be the first guild kill!" Jupiter poked Poseidon's head heavily.

Hearing this, the guild pillars present all agreed.

Although the army already used the 'Human Wave Tactic' to kill a Calamity Grade, the first guild kill meant something different. It would definitely be remarkable.

The only superior achievement would be a solo kill, but everyone knew that no one in the players was that strong yet.

"Poseidon, isn't it too risky? Can we really kill a Calamity Grade on our own?" Poseidon scratched his head.

"We'll have to try it. I think there's a chance. After all, it's no longer Version 3.0 now," Jupiter said in a deep voice.

When they killed Atimo, the army created an environment where Atimo could not escape. With hundreds of thousands of players reviving again and again, they finally killed him using the 'Human Wave Tactic'. After all, the difference between Grade B and Calamity Grade was far from the difference between Calamity Grades and Beyond Grade As, so the Human Wave Tactic was still effective.

Of course, as a guild, they could not just send as many people as the army did. However, the average strength of the players now was unlike in the past; they were thirty levels higher on average, and the elites were all above level 150. They were now seniors among Grade Bs.

Plus, the Black Star Army had always been updating its equipment and technology. The equipment and weapons the players were using now were also much stronger than during Version 3.0. They even had trump cards like the Evolution Badge, so their combat capability was quite impressive.

Therefore, Jupiter felt that the guild should have the capability to kill a Calamity Grade, and it was worth gambling.

Hearing his explanation, the guild pillars were convinced. They were all thrilled and filled with anticipation.

This was not a mission, but they did not care.

Jupiter looked around and loudly said, "Since no one has any objections, we shall go fight the boss now. Let's go!"

…

In the Didora Star System was the Heavy Iron Guards headquarters.

It was a huge galactic fortress that looked like a base made of countless rectangular blocks of various sizes. Its structure was very neat, layered, and edged.

A huge pattern was engraved on the front armor of the galactic fortress. It looked like the helmet of a heavy mechanical suit. This was the organization symbol of the Heavy Iron Guards.

The Heavy Iron Guards was a renowned civilian armed force in the Didora Star System. Most of its members were Mechanical Pugilists. On the surface, it was just a civilian armed force, but it was said that it had a strong background and a secret indescribable connection to the Feeney Civilization that ruled this Star System.

The leader of this organization was 'Earth Core' Dafis. Rumor had it that he was a claw of the Feeney Civilization who did immoral jobs for them.

At this point of time, inside the office at the main base, Dafis was attending to a distinguished guest. They were having a great chat, and laughter came out of the room from time to time.

"Haha, thank you for personally escorting this batch of cargo. I've already had my people check it. It looks quite great,"

Dafis' tone was filled with satisfaction as he spoke with a smile.

In front of him was a man wearing a dark yellow robe who also looked like a pangolin and was a member of the Feeney race as well. However, a large portion of his body was prosthetic, and his electronic eyes were shining with a red light. His body sank deep into the sofa, clearly showing how heavy he was. His organs and limbs were almost all prosthetics, and his body was covered in metal.

"Of course, when did we ever send you any cargo that was bad quality? This batch contains all our new official military weapons the military specially approved to sell to you. Others couldn't buy it even if they wanted to."

This prosthetic man spoke with a vocal device at his throat with a simulated enthusiastic tone.

He was the emissary of the Feeney Civilization who had been in charge of contacting the Heavy Iron Guards on behalf of the upper echelons. The two of them were indeed working together; the Feeney Civilization provided Dafis with resources, and in exchange, Dafis worked for them.

The Feeney Civilization had a liking for mechanical prosthetics, seeing prosthetics as the definition of beauty. It had always been a top market for mechanical prosthetics. Almost everyone had some prosthetics. Some civilians even changed their entire body into different machines except for their brains. Mechanics also made up the majority of Supers in the civilization, and Mechanical Pugilists were mainstream.

"Don't worry, I know why you're here. I've taken your things, so of course, I'll complete the mission properly." Dafis grinned. "I'm about done with what you guys asked me to do last time. According to the information you provided, I've already gotten rid of the nails the Beyond Grade A Association has planted in the black markets in the nearby Star Zones. There are only a few planets left."

"Oh? Many of them are Immortals of the Black Star Army, so they can't be killed. Are you sure you've handled all of them?" the emissary asked casually. He grabbed the glass on the table and drank the black, sticky liquid inside. This was a heavy metal drink especially designed for prosthetic people that would be dissolved into different elements through their prosthetic organs. It was very nutritional for them.

"Immortals, so what? As long as their black-market channel is destroyed, they'll have to either start from nothing or piss off."

Dafis was not concerned.

The emissary put the glass down and said curiously, "I heard from your subordinates that some of those Immortals you killed said they'll take revenge. Aren't you afraid?"

"Can they? These people are powerless. They only dare to talk that way because they won't die, or they would've tucked their tails and fled. If they try to take revenge, I'll just kill them again."

Dafis snorted, expressing his disdain while also sounding a little sour.

With his strength, he looked down on everyone with inferior strength. However, any Super would envy the players' immortality, and he was no exception. Therefore, he never held back when fighting them.

He could not get it, so he had a twisted sense of hatred toward them, feeling uncontrollably sour.

"I have nothing to worry about then." The emissary nodded. "Nonetheless, this is a mission from the three Universal Civilizations, so it's best to be cautious. Plus, the black market was originally controlled by us and provided us a lot of profits. The Beyond Grade A Association thinks they can send some random people to take over our black market just because they have the black market administrators' support. They're just daydreaming."

Some of the upper echelons of the Feeney Civilization were the umbrella of most black markets in this Star System, making their own wallets thicker from them. However, when the Beyond Grade A Association planned to unite the black market, it disrupted their money-making.

At this sensitive time, the three Universal Civilizations spoke with multiple Star System civilizations and asked them to work with them to disturb the association's people in the black market. The Feeney Civilization was one of said civilizations.

The Endless Nebulae was very far from the Shattered Star Ring, so the Black Star Army's hands could not extend that far. Plus, they were a Star System civilization protected by the Peace Treaty. Holding on to the three Universal Civilizations was much more beneficial than fawning over the Beyond Grade A Association. Therefore, the Feeney Civilization supported the three Universal Civilizations and told Dafis to eliminate the people the association sent to operate the black market, killing two birds with one stone.

"They won't be able to with me here." Dafis waved casually. Suddenly, he narrowed his eyes and said, "Don't forget what you promised after it's done…"

The emissary chuckled and said, "Don't worry, we've been working together for so long. The people above never thought of going back on their word. As long as you can handle this problem properly, not only will we support you to continue expanding, but we're even willing to let you become one of the controllers of the black market behind the curtains. You will get your dividends from the black market as promised too."

"Of course I trust you guys." Dafis smiled with satisfaction.

He had chosen to take the risk of offending the Black Star Army, of course, for his own interests. No way was he going to risk his life without enough profit.

Due to the Feeney Civilization's liking of mechanical prosthetics, the profit the black markets of this area earned through smuggling machines every year was an outrageous figure. Dafis had been tempted by it for a very long time. Now, he just had to remove the nails the outsiders had planted there, and he would be able to take a bite of this huge cake. To him, this was a perfect opportunity.

Thinking of the bright future where he could earn more than enough cash to swim in, Dafis was so overjoyed even his cells felt more active than usual.

However, at this time, a change suddenly occurred!

Boom!

A huge explosion suddenly sounded in the base. The two of them both felt the base tremble. The glasses on the table fell onto the floor, and the heavy metal drink spilled all over like a puddle of black oil.

Then, a blaring alarm rang, and the warning lights lit up, painting the entire room red.

Dafis stood up instantly, summoned his aide-de-camp, and yelled, "What's happening‽"

"Boss, the base just got bombarded. The enemy's ship cannons are too strong. The protective shield cracked, and some of them already charged into the base. The artificial intelligence center is now sending troops over!" the aide-de-camp hastily replied.

"Who dares to attack my headquarters? Are there Calamity Grades?" Dafis was shocked and furious.

"I—I don't know, there's no symbol on their spaceships but no Calamity Grade energy source has been detected…"

"They have no Calamity Grade, yet they dare attack my headquarters‽"

Dafis was enraged. He pushed the aide-de-camp aside and headed out of the room.

This time, the emissary said with a worried tone, "Should I hide for now?"

"What's there to be afraid of? I'll handle the problem and come back in no time."

Dafis walked out without even looking back.

The aide-de-camp was just about to follow behind when the emissary suddenly grabbed his arm.

He turned and saw the emissary said, "Er… I'd better hide. Do you have a safehouse here?"

…

More than ten completely black battleships hovered outside the base, continuously launching attacks.

Boom!

Dark red beams from cannons dashed right across and landed on the protective shield of the Heavy Iron Guards' space base, creating countless cracks.

Charge cabins and airdrop cabins covered in shields continuously shot out from under the battleships, bolting onto the surface of the base through the cracks. Some were destroyed in midair by the base's artillery cannons, but some penetrated the base's armor, leaving holes behind.

"Keep sending people down! All those who board the enemy headquarters successfully, remember to bind your revival flag!"

Inside the main ship's command room, Jupiter issued orders loudly with excitement.

All the people in this fleet were players of the Guild of Gods, which took quite some time to gather secretly. After obtaining enough intelligence, they charged toward Dafis' headquarters.

In order to kill a Calamity Grade, the Guild of Gods went all out. These battleships were all assets of the guild that were equipped with tons of war weapons. Although there were not many of them, their technology was very advanced and very high quality. It was basically overkill to use them against a civilian armed force, all just so that the members could quickly board the enemy base.

At this time, the guild channel was filled with messages that refreshed the screen every second.

"Nice, I got in!"

"People behind, come quickly! The enemy's reinforcements are here."

"Mages and Psychics control the battlefield. Give the Mechanics time to summon their machines!"

"Don't waste time on minions. Force the boss out!"

Inside the base, the players who had boarded were on a slaughter. They were all high-level Grade B Supers, killing tons of guarding troops like harvesting crops.

At this time, a huge pressurizing presence rapidly approached.

With a loud bang, the metal wall on one side was broken open, and Dafis rushed in holding that heavy axe in his hands.

Dafis looked around and locked his eyes onto Army Commander's Big PP—he had an impression of this guy whom he had killed ten times. He was furious.

"It's you‽"

Army Commander's Big PP crushed a Grade C Mechanical Pugilist with a cannon attack, turned around, and grinned.

"Surprised? I told you I'd be back!"

Before Dafis could reply, Army Commander's Big PP pointed at him with his gun and yelled, "Brothers, that's him. Get him!"

The next moment, the eyes of everyone focused on Dafis. The excitement of seeing a prey appeared in their eyes.

Even with how experienced Dafis was on the battlefield, being stared by a ton of Grade B Supers still made him intuitively shiver.

However, the next moment, the rage in his body exploded. He raised his mechanical heavy axe and charged right into the battlefield, blasting away two players in his path.

"You're all… looking to die!"

On the side of the players, they yelled almost simultaneously, "Team MT! Go!"

Chapter 1289: Lawless

Boom!

Explosions occurred nonstop, and beams of flames blasted from inside the base, penetrating its armor and creating countless holes. The location of the explosions kept changing, and the battlefield was shifting rapidly.

Inside the base, the troops of the Guild of Gods were already in an intense battle with Dafis while more and more players were landing from above like pouring rain to join the battle.

Swoosh…

The enormous blade of the axe detached from its handle, covered in blue Mechanical Force electric sparks and spinning like a rotary saw. Everywhere it passed, blood and flesh spilled, and shattered mechanical parts were all over the place. A silver spinning chain connected the blade and the handle, dancing like a wild dragon. It looked messy, but it actually controlled the movements of the blade to a highly precise degree.

Mechanical Pugilists were masters in technological weapons. They created their own techniques based on their weapons, which became their special 'styles'. Therefore, Mechanical Pugilists who used the same styles basically all used the same mechanical weapons. This axe style Dafis used was called 'RC-03 Rope Axe'. The essence of it was controlling the chain. It was great for fighting in complex environments and was one of the styles Dafis excelled in.

Ka-cha!

The spinning axe blade flew past the players, winding through them on the way and burying into the chest of a player who turned into an Aberration. It continued spinning and sliced open large pieces of bones and flesh.

"I caught him!"

This player adjusted his pain senses to the lowest, so it did not hurt at all. He grabbed onto the spinning axe blade, ignoring how it made blood gush out of his hand like a river.

The Aberrations of the MT team all pounced over, each grabbing onto a part of the chain and pulling it, while the damage output team poured all of their attacks on Dafis' body.

Dafis twisted his waist and created a yellow spinning energy shield around him that blocked the players' attacks. Amid the colorful explosions, the shield was rapidly filled with cracks.

In this short moment, Dafis made a command in his brain. The neural signals flowed into the control module of the axe. In an instant, the chain tightened. A plasma wave appeared around the chain and knocked away the hands of the many Aberrations.

Then, the axe suddenly went into overload mode. With a loud bang, the spinning speed of the blade rocketed, instantly cutting off the hands of the player who grabbed it and retracted along with the chain, slashing all the Aberrations on the way in half and returned to the handle. Dafis swung it around his body, sent out a silver shockwave from the axe blade, and blasted away many Pugilist players who wanted to get close to him.

Although he was tremendously outnumbered, Calamity Grades were much stronger than Grade Bs. The players had no choice but to fill this strength gap with their lives. Before Dafis got exhausted, the players would have almost no chance of catching him off guard.

"Keep going, Secondary Tank team, go!"

"Damage team, remember to spread out!"

"Teams on the outside, stop the minions and don't let them come in!"

The Guild of Gods' formation was shattered time after time, but they went back to charging forward without fear. The captain commanded the battle efficiently in the team channels.

To players, the most troublesome part was that they could not control who the boss attacked. The only thing they could do was send the MT team forward and make a line of defense with their flesh.

Even so, Dafis would still choose to go around the MT team to attack the fragile backline. Most of the time, the players could only adapt and improvise. Luckily, the Black Star Army's armor was very tough, so the damage dealers would not be killed instantly.

Above the base, the Guild of Gods' fleet was clashing with the Heavy Iron Guards' fleet.

On this battlefield, they were the ones who were outnumbered. The Guild of Gods' fleet was at a small disadvantage. However, with the aid of the more advanced technology on their ships, they could still continuously disrupt the opponent's formation and hold on.

The command room was shaking nonstop. Jupiter's hands pressed on the command table as he stared closely at the fight with Dafis displayed on the screen. He said with a deep voice, "This won't work. The efficiency of the siege is too slow. This won't last long… Ignore their fleet, aim all weapons at the boss, and provide firepower support!"

"What about the people around him?" Poseidon asked.

"We don't have the leisure to mind the casualties on our side. Tell them to be mindful and dodge the attacks as much as possible," Jupiter said decisively.

As the order was given, the more than ten guild battleships turned their cannons at the same time and locked onto Dafis, who was inside the base. Light beams and tracking missiles fired one after another.

A loud alarm rang on the internal radar inside Dafis' mechanical suit. Irritated, he hastily dodged aside. The next moment, beams of light penetrated where he was earlier and chased after him.

The players had been warned earlier and dodged the attacks, but some still did not make it and were turned to ash.

If the opponents were only a group of Grade B Immortals, it would actually not be a big problem for Dafis. However, with the accurate fire support of the fleet, he was troubled.

The players were not afraid of being killed, but he was. Ordinary Calamity Grades could not last long under the high energy ship cannon attacks, and he was only a Mechanical Pugilist, which did not have the highest defenses, nor did he dare to test it out.

The fight went on intensely. The base was a mess. The Guild of Gods' fleet was restrained by the enemy ships, only able to provide support occasionally. The shockwaves of the bombardments gradually created wounds on Dafis.

Seeing the Immortals getting killed by the attacks of their allies while the rest were still charging forward, Dafis' mouth twitched uncontrollably.

"Tsk, these maniacs…"

He could not help but feel a little bit regretful like he had poked the hornet's nest.

Weird, I'm not the only Calamity Grade the three Universal Civilizations bribed, and there are Calamity Grades hunting the Immortals everywhere. I've never heard of anyone who faced their revenge. Why am I so unlucky?

Dafis dodged five explosions and looked at the corpses of his subordinates all over the floor. His expression became more and more gloomy.

Although he was not afraid on his own, the others in the base were not as strong as him. Grade B Supers were already the backbone of the Heavy Iron Guards, yet they were almost powerless under the attacks of the Guild of Gods. A ton of officers who followed him for many years had died.

They were all talents he had put in a lot of efforts to recruit; it was not worth it at all!

"These Immortals came prepared. If this goes on, my energy and stamina will keep dropping. Things won't look good then. Plus, they're here for me. If I keep fighting here, it'll only kill more of my men…"

Dafis hesitated for quite some time before taking a deep breath and making the decision.

The next moment, the energy inside his body started boiling. He swung his axe and spun it like a gyroscope, releasing an arc-shaped vibrating shockwave that expanded from the axe blade.

Swoosh!

A blue shockwave exploded and expanded rapidly. The powerful shockwave instantly blew away all the players nearby. Most of them were stunned momentarily.

The players who recovered first hastily got up and were surprised to see that Dafis did not continue attacking. Instead, he broke through the wall and sprinted out, quickly disappearing in everyone's sights.

"He's fleeing‽"

Their expression changed as they hastily started chasing.

However, they realized that Dafis had already flown into space and changed his mechanical suit into galactic travel mode. Thrusters shot out flames from behind. His speed kept increasing, and he fled further.

"Stop him!"

Jupiter's expression changed. He quickly commanded the fleet to ignore the incurred damages and penetrate the Heavy Iron Guards' line of defense, wanting to chase after Dafis.

However, at this time, alarms suddenly rang on all the battleships' radars.

A small fleet appeared at the edge of the battlefield and rapidly approached. Their exterior armor had the symbol of the Feeney Civilization. They said in the public channel, "This is the Feeney Civilization police patrol. We have detected unusual energy reactions here. Everyone stop where you are and prepare for a check!"

The law enforcement is here too? Dafis, who was fleeing, thought.

His headquarters were in the Feeney Civilization's territory, so, of course, there was law enforcement there. Usually, they minded their own business. He did not know if they wanted to stop him too.

While Dafis was pondering, he suddenly received a communication from his mechanical suit. It was the Feeney Civilization emissary who visited him and was in the safe house of his base.

"You keep going and leave. The law enforcement won't bother you." The emissary cut to the chase.

"You called them?" Dafis understood.

"Who else? Or are you going to protect me?" The emissary was not in a good mood. "I'll tell them to buy some time for you. Get as far away as you can. I can't help you if they chase you after that!"

He was just there as a guest and never expected to be in such danger, so he blamed Dafis for it.

As he was afraid of being killed by the aftershock, he urgently used his authority to call the law enforcement to stop the battle, at the same time forcing Dafis away… From the way he looked at it, since these Immortals were after revenge, as long as Dafis left, they would be lured away too. This way, he would be safe.

"I'll go now." Dafis nodded. He initially wanted to eliminate the enemy together with the law enforcement, but now he had no choice but to agree to leave. He did not want to see the emissary in danger too.

The emissary hesitated for a moment and said, "Planet Burger is just around the corner. That's a colonial planet for low value citizens. I've already spoken to the manager of the planet, so you can go to Planet Burger. Although they don't have a large garrison there, those enemies won't dare violate the Peace Treaty and attack a colonial planet."

"Okay."

Dafis hung up the communication and accelerated at full power output. Although the Guild of Gods had set up spacetime stabilization anchors and limited his hyperdrive, his regular flying speed was fast enough. He turned into a stream of light and gradually disappeared in sights.

Seeing this, Jupiter panicked.

We're only halfway through and the boss has just escaped, what do we do now?

"Aiyo, I told you your plan wasn't reliable. They can escape even if they can't win. You think we're in a dungeon?" Poseidon sounded unhappy.

Although they could weaken a Calamity Grade with their lives or even have the chance to kill him, it was very difficult for them to stop a Calamity Grade if he wanted to run. After all, the desperate situation Atimo was in was tough to replicate. Plus, Dafis was not a naïve kid who could not read the situation; he fled as soon as he saw the situation was not good for him. No way he was going to stay here and fight head-on with a ton of Immortals like an idiot.

"Shut up!" Jupiter scolded him. Veins popped up on his forehead. He then opened the public channel and shouted, "Black Star Army carrying out business, please let us through!"

"I don't care who you are! This is the Feeney Civilization's territory. No one can do whatever they want! Stop your ships and be checked immediately, or we'll see it as a crime!"

Having received orders from the emissary, the captain of the law enforcement force did not back down. He continued commanding his troops to stop the guild's fleet.

"Then, why didn't you stop that guy who ran away‽" Jupiter was extremely annoyed and marked Dafis's direction.

"None of your business! This is your last warning. Stop your ships immediately!" the captain yelled angrily.

Jupiter clenched his teeth. Having spent so many resources, giving up halfway would be a huge loss. He planned this operation, so he would definitely take the blame for it. He immediately made up his mind.

"We're going to finish this boss today no matter what! Advance! Get rid of whoever's in our way!"

As he said that, the guild fleet no longer hesitated and fired at all the enemies, be it the Heavy Iron Guards or Feeney Civilization's law enforcement team, trying to open a path.

Some of the players who were still in the base returned through traction beams. Some simply used up all their energy by attacking randomly and killed themselves to revive in the ships.

The two sides fought for some time. Most players returned to the ships except for a few who were still in the base. Army Commander's Big PP's was one of them.

"Fu*k, since you ran away, your home will vanish!"

Army Commander's Big PP was extremely annoyed by the fact that Dafis had fled. He took out a sphere portable bomb right away.

This was a small dark energy annihilation bomb he had spent quite a lot of his savings to purchase. Before the Guild of Gods contacted him, he originally wanted to use this thing to 'die together' with Dafis, and now he decided to just activate it.

The next moment, a dark red explosion erupted!

Boom!

Light rapidly expanded and devoured the entire base, turning the metal of the base into atoms.

The emissary who was in the safe house waiting for the law enforcements to pick him up was blown to ashes before he could react. He died on the spot painlessly.

Not only him, all members of the Heavy Iron Guards in the base were reduced to atoms. No one survived.

The law enforcement force captain was shocked.

"Are these people crazy? How dare they use such a dangerous weapon here‽"

Just like the psionic bombs, the dark energy annihilation bomb was also a highly dangerous weapon prohibited by most civilizations and severely punished when discovered.

Even some wanted criminals did not dare do this. Was the Black Star Army not in the Lawful Faction? Were they not afraid of damaging their reputation‽

The law enforcement captain was intimidated. The emissary was already blown to pieces anyway, so he decided to let the guild fleet through, afraid that these maniacs might send him a dark energy annihilation bomb too.

Without the law enforcement's obstruction, the guild broke through the siege and chased after Dafis.

Battleships were designed for galactic travel; they were much faster than Dafis. The distance between the two sides quickly decreased.

Dafis noticed the battleships chasing behind him. Complaining that the law enforcement fleet could not even slow them down in his head, he had no choice but to keep running.

Having left the spacetime stabilized area, the two sides entered hyperdrive mode at the same time, turning into two streams of light, one thin and one thick.

Not long after, a planet appeared in their sights. It was the low-value colonial planet of the Feeney Civilization, Planet Burger.

The residents on this kind of colonial planet were all those who were not willing to work, using the government's money to maintain the lowest standard of life. Almost all civilizations had planets like this that usually had zero visitors.

"I'm here!" Dafis looked overjoyed as he quickly sent a request to land.

As the emissary had already informed Planet Burger of his arrival, his request was instantly approved. The garrison fleet outside the atmosphere did not stop him. Seeing this, Dafis dashed into the atmosphere without hesitation and headed toward one of the cities.

At this time, the Guild of Gods fleet finally caught up and stopped outside the planet. The garrison fleet of the planet gathered in front of them and stopped them from advancing.

Their spaceship suddenly received a message. A prosthetic man appeared on the screen. He was the planet manager of Planet Burger, and his attitude was very cold.

"I'm the manager of Planet Burger. You're not welcome on this planet. Please leave immediately, or I'll contact the nearest garrison to banish you."

Hearing this, the guild pillars inside the main fleet looked at each other and were in a dilemma.

"President, what do we do now? This colonial planet clearly wants to protect our target." Poseidon looked at Jupiter, whose eyes were glowing red, and said cautiously, "We should retreat for now. According to the laws of the galactic society, we can't attack colonial planets…"

Jupiter looked troubled. He then clenched his teeth and forced out the following words.

"I don't care! We'll kill the target today no matter what! Don't let him run again. Fire!"

Meanwhile, Dafis landed in a city. The streets were quiet with only a few pedestrians who were looking at him confused.

Ignoring them, Dafis looked up at the fleet hovering outside the atmosphere. Frustration and irritation flashed through his eyes.

This was a huge loss. A ton of his officers were killed, so his heart was bleeding.

If not because of the concerns he had, he would have tried to kill all those Immortals. He did not want to seek help from a planet at all.

"Never mind, I'll let these people live for today, then find them one by one in the future…"

Dafis clenched his teeth and took out the communicator to contact the emissary. He had fled very quickly earlier and still did not know that his headquarters were already destroyed.

As he made the call, no one answered.

While Dafis was feeling confused, he suddenly had a sense of danger and hastily backed away!

Boom!

The next moment, cannon beams fell from the sky like pouring rain. The entire street was shattered!

"What‽"

Dafis' expression changed drastically. He looked up at the fleet that was firing at the city with disbelief.

They fired at a colonial planet just to kill me, ignoring the civilian casualties‽

Don't they know what kind of deed this is? Even the Beyond Grade A Association that's fighting head-on with the three Universal Civilizations wouldn't do something like this!

A chill shot up his spine to his brain, and his flames of rage were instantly frozen.

Dafis' heart was filled with shock.

These people are lawless!

Chapter 1290: Traitor?

Ta ta ta!

Rounds of ship cannon attacks landed in the city following Dafis, creating craters one after another. Everywhere the attacks landed, tall buildings turned to ruins, flames rose from the ground, and screams echoed.

Along with the pouring bombardment, airdrop cabins descended from the sky, penetrating the buildings like meteors and partially burrowing into the ground.

The hatches opened, and Guild of Gods players swarmed out like a black tsunami to surround Dafis. An intense battle erupted once again.

The planet's garrison fleet was also startled. They hastily fired at the guild fleet. The two sides exchanged intense crossfire outside the atmosphere. The anti-aircraft weapons and railguns of the planet were also activated. Closely packed electromagnetic rail cannon attacks bolted across the sky toward the guild fleet. Looking down from above, the garrison bases around the city that was attacked shot out anti-gravity carriers one after another, carrying ground troops to prevent the battle in the city.

Although Planet Burger was a low-level colonial planet, it still had a military defense force. However, in terms of individual strength, the strongest defender was only Grade B. After all, the Feeney Civilization was just a Star System level civilization with only ten or so Calamity Grades; they did not have the luxury to station a Calamity Grade on such a low-level colonial planet.

On the communication screen of the guild's main ship, the Planet Burger manager's expression changed drastically. He was both shocked and enraged, and he yelled, "How dare you violate the Peace Treaty‽ Are you trying to become the Feeney Civilization's enemy‽ I demand you stop immedi…"

Before he could even finish, Jupiter slammed the button and hung up the communication right away.

His eyes red, he yelled, "All backup teams! Enter the charge cabins and take over all the garrison fleet on this planet! Attack whoever's in our way!"

Since he had made up his mind, he might as well do it till the end and attack the troops of the colonial planet too, eliminating all obstructions of the first guild kill.

Although the guild's fleet was outnumbered by the planet's garrison, their biggest advantage was individual strength. As long as one or two players could board the enemy battleship, they could kill the whole crew in it and take over the ship, increasing their own strength. After all, there was no way this kind of low-level colonial planet could put one Grade B on every battleship.

"He's lost it. He's lost it…" Poseidon mumbled on the side, saying what all the guild pillars were thinking.

Jupiter suddenly turned around, stared deadly at him with a dangerous look, and said word by word, "What did you say?"

"Brothers, with me, charge!"

Poseidon's expression instantly became firm. He waved his hand and headed toward the charge cabin with a group of elites. It looked like he was bravely heading into a battle with no return. His emotional change was very smooth.

Very soon, charge cabins carrying players shot out like missiles, biting into the enemy ships. The garrison's battleships fell into the Guild of Gods' control rapidly one after another, turning around to fire at the ground, making Dafis' situation worse.

Some airdrop cabins even landed on the base that controlled the anti-aircraft weapons. Tons of players charged forward to paralyze Planet Burger's military force.

There were battles happening in many places on the planet's surface and outside the atmosphere. Explosions appeared continuously as cities were blown into ruins one after another. It was complete chaos.

Planet Burger's manager was both furious and panicking. He hastily requested support from the nearest galactic garrison base while reporting the attack on the planet to the artificial intelligence core of the Feeney Civilization through the emergency military channel. He also sent the report to the various key departments.

About two minutes later, he quickly received a serious call from an upper echelon.

"What are the details? Who are the enemies‽"

"The enemies are a group of Immortals. According to the law enforcements' report, they claim to be the Black Star Army's men and are chasing after a Calamity Grade…" The Planet Burger manager quickly described the situation, stating that the cause of all this was that he received a message from the emissary to protect Dafis.

He actually did not know about the relationship between Dafis and the Feeney Civilization, but since the emissary's position was higher, he could only obey. He kept subtly hinting that he was only obeying orders and was not the one to be blamed.

After hearing the explanation, the Feeney Civilization upper echelon seriously said, "I've understood the situation. Go restrain the attackers for now. The nearest garrison base will send troops over right away and arrest them!"

Hanging up the communication, Planet Burger manager heaved a sigh of relief. Protected by his bodyguards, he quickly walked to the safe house underground while telling the secretary to contact Dafis on the way.

At the same time, inside the city that already became a battlefield, Dafis suppressed the shock in his heart and fought intensely with the Guild of Gods players. In order to dodge the attacks from the sky, he could not fight at his full strength and planned to retreat.

He was appalled by how absolutely lawless the players were. From the way he looked at it, it was unwise to keep fighting with these maniacs.

Dafis felt more and more regretful about having messed with these people.

At this time, the internal communication device of the mechanical suit suddenly rang. It was a call from the planet manager's secretary relaying the planet manager's message.

Dafis' eyes sparkled. "You're saying that reinforcements are on the way, so I have to restrain these Immortals as much as I can so that when they arrive, these brutes will all be eliminated?"

"Yes, the upper echelons have already dispatched the garrison. Reinforcements will arrive very soon."

The secretary's tone was respectful. Although Dafis was the one who caused this, he was the only Calamity Grade at the scene and was a member of the Feeney Race too. Planet Burger needed his help for the time being.

"… Okay, I'll stall them."

Dafis hesitated for a moment but agreed in the end.

It would not be easy for him to escape. The mechanical suit's travel speed was no match for the guild's fleet. If he left Planet Burger and lost the help he had, he would be in an even more dangerous situation. He felt it was better to stay there and work with the Feeney Civilization, wait for the government troops to arrive, and wipe out all the Immortals.

Anyway, he was in a good state for now. These enemies could not threaten his life for the time being. Furthermore, a ton of his subordinates had died, and he was filled with anger. His desire to fight back was tough to suppress.

Hanging up the communication, Dafis stopped getting distracted by the thought of retreat, raised his mechanical chain axe, and charged into the players' formation. Everywhere he passed, electronic sparks exploded, and blood poured everywhere.

At the same time, in the SWY-001 research lab…

"Master, hum… Something's happened!"

Han Xiao, who was studying the nervous system of SWY-001, received the message from Phillip. He moved his eyes away from the research report and turned to Phillip.

"What happened?"

"In the Endless Nebulae Star Field, a group of army Immortals are attacking the colonial planet of a Star System civilization…" Phillip switched to the surveillance footage and explained the situation.

"What? They challenged a Calamity Grade on their own?"

After hearing the full situation, Han Xiao's eyes narrowed, and a complicated expression appeared on his face.

"This day still came…"

He had known long ago that as the average strength of the players grew, they would challenge Calamity Grades on their own sooner or later. It was destined to happen.

Players were always the representatives of anarchism. The stronger they became, the more uncontrollable they were as they would gradually ignore all kinds of restrictions. The reason they had always seemed peaceful was that they did not have enough strength to really influence anything, and he had managed them well.

However, at Version 5.0, the players' peacefulness had almost reached the limit, and chaos started to surface.

In his previous life, this was one of the key fuses of the Calamity of the Supers. Even with his influence now, there was no way he could change the players' nature.

"Tsk, this won't be easy to settle…"

Han Xiao shook his head and sighed.

He understood the situation. The enemy was someone who obstructed the players from taking over the black market. There was no problem with the players grouping up to attack him, and Han Xiao was not going to oppose that.

However, the part that troubled him was that they violated the laws of the galactic society…

At least be mindful of your image when attacking a boss!

This meant that there were disadvantages to both rewarding them and punishing them. The former would make the players even more unconcerned with the laws, while the latter would hurt the leeks' feelings and damage their sense of belonging to the faction. Neither were things he wanted to see.

The person Han Xiao was most annoyed by was none other than the moron Jupiter…

'Black Star Army carrying out business, please let us through'? Is your face even bigger than mine? Did you eat the Face Face Fruit too‽

Even if you decided to fight a boss no matter what, at least don't expose who you are!

Han Xiao was speechless. He exhaled and slowly said, "… Too reckless. No matter what, it's best not to take the blame for this. The top priority now is to clean the evidence as much as possible."

While speaking, Han Xiao pressed between his brows and entered the quantum network. With Phillip as the transit station, his data stream quickly arrived in the guild battleship.

The battle on Planet Burger became ever bloodier. The defenses of the planet were mostly shattered by the Guild of Gods. Tons of their battleships were seized and made the guild stronger.

The battlefield around Dafis kept shifting on the planet surface. Four cities had already turned into ruins. Facing the guild players' unending chase, Dafis' energy and stamina were depleting very quickly. He started to feel exhausted, and wounds no longer regenerated on his body. His status gradually worsened, and his combat capability unavoidably weakened.

Boom!

Dafis spun and swung his axe, flattening a Pugilist player on the wall, and hastily gasped for air. Not daring to stop, he quickly took many big steps backward and dodged the attacks of more than a dozen Cannon Masters. The place where he stood moments ago became a crater.

Not only were his muscles sore, but his brain was hurting like it was stabbed by needles too. After all, the mind was not the Mechanical Pugilists' strongest suit. The Psychics and the mind Mages of the Guild of Gods contributed a lot, attacking Dafis' consciousness every second. He basically could not dodge them at all and could only take the damage head-on. These attacks made up at least sixty percent of all the damage he took.

"Hu… Hu… The reinforcements are still not here."

Dafis checked his status and was not looking too good.

From the moment he fell from his peak state, the issues began to snowball. He was almost at his limit.

One who had never been surrounded by the players could not understand how horrifying it was, and Dafis finally felt it now. He initially thought he could last a very long time. Only now did he realize that he had completely underestimated just how difficult it was to deal with these maniacs. He misjudged the strength difference between him and the players.

If reinforcements don't come soon and I keep staying here, this might be the end of me…

The thought of wanting to retreat appeared in Dafis' mind again.

However, at this time, he suddenly felt something and looked up at the atmosphere, surprised.

"Finally!"

An enormous fleet was quickly approaching. Its formation was neat and fearsome. It was indeed the government military army the Feeney Civilization had sent. There were almost two thousand battleships. The guild fleet had no chance of matching up to it!

The Planet Burger manager who was hiding in the underground safehouse saw the images of the battlefield and was overjoyed.

"The army is here! Hahaha, these brutes are done for!"

In the guild main fleet, Jupiter noticed this hostile army too, and his heart sank.

Sh*t, this looks like the local government army!

We took too long. Seems like I underestimated the difficulty of this BOSS. A Calamity Grade who's free to move around is too tough to deal with. Is this mission still too difficult for the guild?

Looking at the huge reinforcements, Jupiter began to despair. However, he then clenched his teeth and ordered the fleet to continue firing at Dafis.

"President, are we still not going to retreat?" Poseidon asked in the channel.

"Retreat, how? We're already here. How can we give up halfway? If we leave, the resources we've spent will really all be wasted… All members! We must kill the boss today even if it costs all our revival counts!"

Jupiter clenched his teeth and told the troops to get ready to fire at the reinforcements.

However, this enormous army suddenly stopped at the edge of the battlefield. Not only did they not fire, but they did not even move anymore.

As minutes passed, Dafis, the Planet Burger manager, Jupiter, and the players all became confused.

What, are these reinforcements here just to watch the show?

The Guild of Gods was lost and had no idea what was going on. However, since these reinforcements did not attack them, they did not attack these reinforcements either and focused on attacking Dafis.

The Planet Burger manager panicked.

"What are they waiting for? Why are they not attacking‽"

He was panicking hard. He tried to contact the reinforcements many times but received no response at all.

The joy on Dafis' face gradually froze. He was at a loss and could not understand what was happening.

Under the influence of shock, he could not help but making wild speculations

Why aren't the reinforcements firing?

There's a big problem!

If not because he was waiting for the reinforcements, he might not have stayed to fight with the enemy. Yet, when the reinforcements had arrived, they only watched on the side and did not seem to want to join the battle…

Is this the Feeney Civilization's plan? Keeping me here with an excuse so I'll be murdered in cold blood by the Immortals, killing two birds with one stone?

Is it because they feel I know too much, and now that they had no use of me, they're deliberately letting me die‽

Dafis was shocked by his own speculation, and he immediately panicked!

"Damn it, I'll be done for if I keep fighting. I can't rely on the Feeney Civilization. I have to leave!"

Dafis clenched his teeth and went into overload mode. His powerful energy blew the surrounding players away. Then, taking a round of focus fire head-on, he charged up into the sky. His mechanical suit's thruster operated at full power output. He turned into a stream of light and flew toward the atmosphere, wanting to escape the battlefield.

However, at this time, the Feeney Civilization reinforcements at the edge of the battlefield suddenly fired, shockingly aiming at Dafis, who had just escaped the atmosphere!

"What‽"

Extremely shocked, Dafis hastily turned on his shield.

The next moment, he was entirely engulfed by the attack and took the full damage of it.

Boom!

After a chain of explosions, he fell from the sky and crashed to the ground, stirring up tons of dust.

Ka la ka la…

His already heavily damaged mechanical suit turned into pieces and shattered all over the floor. Dafis lay in the middle of the enormous crater facing up as blood gushed out from all the organs on his face. His entire body was suffering from burns. Some parts were even charred and giving off white smoke. The bones and organs in his body were a mess. He was severely injured.

A ton of players rushed here from afar. Seeing this, Dafis clenched his teeth and forced his body to stand up. He was still shaking and had yet to recover from the stunned state the powerful attack had caused him. He could barely stand properly.

Looking at the Immortals surrounding him, Dafis felt the terrible state of his body, and a bitter smile appeared on his wounded face.

"Ahem… so this is it, getting tricked by the Feeney Civilization in the end…"

Dafis coughed with pain and knew that this was his final moment.

Thinking of the bright future the Feeney Civilization had promised him, Dafis was filled with only regret.

In the end, I trusted the wrong people…

Taking a deep breath, Dafis felt like a hero facing his doom. Filled with frustration, sorrow, and rage, he yelled at the nearby Immortals, "You want my life? Come take it! I won't stay here and…"

Before he could finish, the players around him attacked from all directions.

Boom!

Chains of explosions flooded Dafis.

At the moment he lost consciousness, Dafis was filled with even more regrets.

Couldn't you… wait for me to finish my last words‽

The explosions lasted for more than ten seconds before everything stopped. Dust settled, and air became clear. A completely burnt corpse lay on the ground with absolutely no signs of life.

Seeing this, the many players paused for a second and suddenly started cheering.

"Nice! We finally killed him!"

"We got the first kill! First kill!"

"That was so f*cking exhausting. This boss knew how to give himself more screen time. I was so confused."

"Did anyone record the entire thing? Send me a copy!"

Inside the guild main ship, Jupiter saw the guild kill Dafis with his own eyes and was finally relieved. The anger that filled his mind was finally gone.

Having earned the first guild kill, all their efforts and the resources spent for this mission were not wasted!

Jupiter looked at the Feeney Civilization government army on the side that had an unknown goal and frowned again.

The consequences of killing the boss without caring about anything else seemed quite severe. He now had to think about escaping, and that fleet was probably not going to watch them leave…

He knew that the chances of escaping were extremely low and almost negligible.

Jupiter scratched his head.

How about we… all just die here?

Chapter 1291: Impact and Stand

On the ground, the Guild of Gods players posed and took pictures with Dafis' corpse. After being overjoyed for a little while, they all quickly realized the same thing and knew that this was not the end yet. They quickly wiped the smiles off their faces, took out their weapons, and looked at the Feeney Civilization's army in the sky.

Jupiter stared closely at their fleet. Once they made any move, he would immediately tell the others to flee.

However, the two fleets looked at each other like this for as long as five minutes, yet the Feeney Civilization still did not attack them and remained at the edge of the battlefield. It was as if they had made up their mind to just watch the show.

Jupiter's expression also turned from grave to confused.

He realized he could not figure out the Feeney Civilization's position anymore. At the start, they protected Dafis, yet they watched him die when their army was here, even firing at him, nailing his coffin and helping them to complete the kill. Once the dust had settled, the Feeney Civilization's army still watched on the side and did not seem to want to arrest them…

Whose side are you on really?

"President, they're all intimidated by your presence." Poseidon's fawning voice appeared in the channel.

Humph, you've been disagreeing with me and disrupting the morale of our people all this time, but now you finally thought of fawning upon me? It's too late!

Jupiter snorted in his mind, contemplated, and said, "Retrieve the players on the ground, but keep an eye on the movements of the enemy fleet at all times. If things don't seem right, immediately kill yourself and revive on the ships."

As the order was given, the guild fleet started using retraction beams to retrieve the players on the ground while paying full attention to the Feeney Civilization's army. As soon as they showed any signs of attempting to stop them, they would turn around and flee right away.

However, the Feeney Civilization never reacted at all. They just remained stationary and watched the Guild of Gods clean up the battlefield and retrieve their players. Seeing this, the guild fleet became more daring and sped up the retrieving of the players.

Even when the guild fleet had retrieved all the players, the Feeney Civilization still did not make any move.

"Weird, why aren't they doing anything?"

Jupiter was confused.

Nonetheless, since they were not going to stop them, he did not plan to stay there any longer. Suppressing the confusion in his mind, he ordered the fleet to retreat.

The guild fleet rapidly left Planet Burger and disappeared. At this point, the Feeney Civilization army finally moved. Part of its fleet chased after the guild fleet, while other ships landed on the surface to clean the city ruins and rescue the survivors.

The command ships stopped at the dock, and the hatch opened. The fleet commander walked down the gangway with a frustrated expression and saw the Planet Burger manger walking toward him angrily right away.

After the guild fleet retreated, only then did the Planet Burger manager dare climb out of the safehouse underground. He had been waiting there for quite some time and started questioning the commander immediately.

"What was going on? You didn't pick up my communication request, nor did you pick up my calls. Didn't the people above say they sent you here to assist us? Why didn't you attack? Even letting these brutes leave? What the hell are you people here for‽"

The fleet commander did not look happy either. Suppressing the frustration in his heart, he explained, "All of the fleet's artificial intelligence systems stopped working earlier. Someone took over all our ships. We could not control them at all. Plus, our communication channels with the outside world were all cut off too. We could not contact anyone."

The Planet Burger manager's enraged expression froze. He said with shock, "What happened?"

"Someone paralyzed our fleet, most likely a Beyond Grade A Virtual Mechanic…" The fleet commander lowered his voice subconsciously.

Startled, the Planet Burger manager quickly looked around as if he suspected someone was monitoring him.

"Don't be so nervous, I'm just speculating," the fleet commander said.

He was filled with frustration. Initially, the order he received was to work with Dafis to capture these brutes. However, when he arrived at the scene, he was shocked to realize that the fleet's artificial intelligence system was not working at all. Not only that, someone even controlled their spaceships to launch a round of fire at Dafis. He could do nothing but watch Dafis die and those brutes leave. Only after that did he regain control of the spaceships.

The enemy's hacking was untraceable. The crew of the fleet had absolutely no way of fighting against it, and they could only stare at the 'Candy Crush' on their screens.

If these brutes really came from the Black Star Army, Black Star might have done this personally… It was because of this speculation that the fleet commander did not dare to make any extreme moves. Even after he regained control of the ships, he only sent a small fleet after the enemies while he cheekily remained on the planet.

"Then… what do we do now?" The Planet Burger manager was still shocked.

The fleet commander sighed. "I've already reported what happened here to the upper echelons. Let's wait for their response. This is not a decision we can make."

At this time, his communicator rang. An upper echelon of the Feeney Civilization came online, looked at the two of them, and said with a deep voice, "This was a private battle. The two sides conflicted in Dafis' headquarters, and the law enforcement went to investigate. Dafis used the law enforcements to escape all the way to Planet Burger and landed on the planet surface without having obtained approval, wanting to make use of the planet's garrison fleet to stop his enemies. Because of that, he brought disaster to the planet's residents. Before we could banish him, the second group of brutes came and attacked the planet. Understood?"

The Planet Burger manager was stunned for a second, then understood the meaning behind this and hastily nodded.

Planet Burger suffered huge casualties, and it became a big matter in the civilization. The upper echelons wanted to reduce its influence and remove their responsibility for the matter. Therefore, from now on, Dafis had absolutely no connection with them; everything he did was based on his own will.

The emissary did not exist, nor was he, the planet manager, ordered to protect Dafis. As long as they did not say anything, on the surface, Dafis was using them and brought the disaster to Planet Burger. Planet Burger was just the victim… This way, the rage of the Feeney Civilization citizens would be transferred onto these brutes, and the upper echelons did not have to take the blame for it.

"What about us?" the fleet commander asked.

The upper echelon glanced at him and slowly said, "You guys were dispatched to stop this disaster. Dafis brought the disaster, so the army prioritized killing him, successfully eliminating the brute who caused this. After that, you let the other group of brutes leave because they took citizens of the Planet Burger hostage. Hence, your army let them leave for the time being, only chasing after them later, shifting the battlefield, all to reduce the civilian casualties, understood?"

"Understood."

The fleet commander heaved a sigh of relief while giving the upper echelon a thumbs up in his mind.

It was still the same matter, but just by changing how they described it, it felt completely different. Not only were most of the responsibilities removed from them, but they also emphasized their image of protecting the safety of their citizens.

Marvelous!

At this time, the upper echelon suddenly changed his tone. He said with a bit of anger, "Of course, this is just to calm the citizens down. As for those Immortals, we will openly condemn their actions and bring the attention of the public to them. We will also report to the Civilization Conference and ask the three Universal Civilizations to give us an explanation!"

"Emphasize that they're the Black Star Army's men?" the Planet Burger manager asked.

"No, we can only say they might be from the Black Star Army. Just emphasize that they're Immortals…" The upper echelon clenched his teeth.

The fleet was taken over instantly. It was most likely the doing of a Beyond Grade A Virtual Mechanic and not just an ordinary Beyond Grade A; it might very likely be Black Star himself.

The reason the Feeney Civilization was not afraid of offending the Black Star Army was that the army was too far from the Endless Nebulae. However, since Black Star might have acted personally, they had to hold back to a certain extent.

However, the Feeney Civilization was not going to just put up with this. They suffered severe civilian casualties, so as the victims, they had the moral high ground. They were definitely going to make a big deal out of it.

Of course, they also considered the possibility of Black Star having the evidence of them protecting Dafis.

However, this risk was not enough to turn them into cowards. The Feeney Civilization clearly knew that even if they were found out to have protected Dafis, they would still have the moral high ground. The side that actively slaughtered civilians would always be the side that was wrong. Them protecting Dafis would not be the main cause of it, but the fact that these Immortals did not retreat and still attacked… This was the logic of the galactic society, the rules set by the Peace Treaty.

Actually, the upper echelons very much wanted to insist these Immortals were from the Black Star Army. However, when they tried finding evidence earlier, they discovered that all evidence that pointed toward the army disappeared. This group of Immortals suddenly became a 'ghost team' with unknown origins.

These upper echelons knew that someone had erased the evidence. While they were frustrated, they could not do anything about Black Star.

Nonetheless, the fact that they were Immortals was already a clue. After all, the entire universe now knew that the organization with the most Immortal members was the Black Star Army… The Feeney Civilization was only giving the three Universal Civilizations ammo for their conflict with the association. As long as this happened, their plan could be executed even without solid evidence.

…

Several days later, an announcement made by the Feeney Civilization in the Endless Nebulae caused a sensation in the galactic society.

The topic of the announcement was the Planet Burger Massacre, where a large number of citizens were killed. The Feeney Civilization expressed strong condemnation for such a violent deed, stating they would find whoever was responsible and make them pay. Driven by those with motives, the message that it was a group of Immortals who were suspected to be members of the Black Star Army who attacked the colonial planet was spread quickly, attracting wide attention.

If it was wanted criminals who attacked a colonial planet, this would be a police matter at most, and the galactic residents would not dwell on it much.

However, the big boss of the Beyond Grade A Association was suspected to be involved in this. As a giant organization of the Lawful Faction, they violated the Peace Treaty and slaughtered civilians. At such a sensitive time, this matter immediately became a political issue and sparked intense public discussion!

That was especially so when the Feeney Civilization reported this to the Civilization Conference, crying and asking the three Universal Civilizations to pressure and question the Black Star Army, hoping to investigate and find out the truth. The matter became even bigger.

In the next few days, the three Universal Civilizations took the ammo from the Feeney Civilization, fully activating their propaganda machine, and started to verbally condemn the Black Star Army in all directions. At the same time, they increased the matter to involve the Beyond Grade A Association too, strongly questioning the association's purpose and its 'justice'.

The Star System civilizations were within the protection range of the 'Peace Treaty'. Such a violent act of slaughtering civilians on a colonial planet caused everyone to be enraged. Even the Super Star Cluster did not dare show support to the association at this point of time and remained quiet.

Emotions needed a place to vent. Driven by the advanced situations, although the Feeney Civilization only claimed that the brutes were suspected to be from the Black Star Army and had no proof, ordinary people did not care about that. They directly assumed that the Black Star Army was responsible for it. Their fear and hatred toward the Supers and Immortals that had been suppressed for a very long time turned into overwhelming verbal condemnations… After all, they had the most Immortals in the entire universe, so who else could they scold?

Han Xiao became the main target of the condemnation. With the advanced civilizations controlling the tempo, tons of civilians ignored what he did in the past and infinitely exaggerated the importance of this matter. They started to question why a leader who allowed his subordinates to do such horrible acts could receive the 'Stuarts Peace Prize' and the 'Galaxy Medal'. How could he possibly have the right to be respected by the galactic society?

There was no way the three Universal Civilizations were going to let such an amazing opportunity slip past. They started to go all out to damage Han Xiao's image—as long as they could take away the 'reputation amulet' that they had once built for Han Xiao, they would have the 'moral high ground'.

With the operations of the advanced civilizations, the Planet Burger massacre became a fuse that intensified the conflicting emotions of the ordinary people and the Supers.

Countless galactic residents were worried. As ordinary people, no one wanted to be dragged into wars between Supers and die for no reason.

The influence this matter had on the ordinary people was that they supported the three Universal Civilizations' pressure toward the Beyond Grade A Association more and more. From their perspective, of course, they wished that all Supers could be strictly controlled by civilizations so that disasters would not fall onto them one day for no reason.

Suddenly, the people's request to attack the Beyond Grade A Association received more and more support… However, that was where it stopped. The three Universal Civilizations only used this opportunity to damage their reputation; they did not plan to make a move yet.

Faced with such aggressive accusations, the Black Star Army only made a simple announcement, saying it would investigate internally and only make an announcement when they come to a conclusion. Plus, the Black Star Army warned the Feeney Civilization not to accuse them without evidence. Then, they remained quiet no matter how noisy the outside world got.

…

In a desolate universe belt in the Endless Nebulae, the Guild of Gods fleet was slowly flying.

Tons of guild pillars were standing and sitting around while looking at the forums casually, giggling with joy from time to time.

"President, look, our deeds have already been written into the Galaxy Chronicles. Our first guild kill has been acknowledged."

Poseidon was overjoyed.

Jupiter looked at the forums. The Guild of Gods making the first guild kill of a Calamity Grade had filled the pages for many days and gained a ton of fame for the club. He was also rewarded by the upper echelons of the club because of this.

However, looking at the praise on the forums, Jupiter was not that happy but distracted.

Poseidon noticed and asked, "What's wrong? You don't look too happy."

Jupiter shook his head and said with a worried tone, "Don't you all watch the galactic news? It's a mess out there. We caused big problems for the army this time…"

The emotions of the galactic society got worse day by day, and Jupiter was very worried.

However, he did not regret it. After all, achieving the first guild kill was too amazing an achievement. He would probably make the same choice even if he went back in time. Only, he could not help but be worried about how the army would deal with this.

Those members who caused problems for the army in the past did not end up well, so he had examples to learn from.

Although the Guild of Gods did not do this on purpose, since the matter had become so big, Jupiter was unsure what the army's stand was on this.

He had been waiting for the army to contact him all these days, but it never did, and he became more and more anxious.

Buzz!

Suddenly, the spaceship's communication system suddenly activated on its own, attracting everyone's attention. Han Xiao's remote projection suddenly appeared in front of them.

"Army Commander‽"

The various players present, including Jupiter, were all startled. They did not expect Black Star to come so suddenly.

Han Xiao scanned over everyone and stopped at Jupiter. With a poker face, he cut to the chase and said, "Don't you owe me an explanation?"

Jupiter's heart skipped a beat, and a resigned expression appeared on his face.

He knew he was in the wrong. What he did caused huge problems for his faction. Facing the questioning of the leader of his faction whom he had spent five versions with, he did not know what to say.

Seeing that he did not say anything, Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and purposely paused.

When he secretly saw that some of the guild players around started recording, he then continued.

"You acted on your own without reporting to the army, which is why things escalated to this point, giving our enemies reasons to make the public condemn us. I'm very dissatisfied with this."

Hearing this, their hearts sank.

However, Jupiter expected this. It would be weird of Black Star did not react to such a huge matter.

He sighed.

"… How will the army punish us?"

Han Xiao looked around, viewing everyone's expressions, snorted, and said, "I'll be straightforward. This time, the army won't give you any punishments. We're all old comrades from the Planet Aquamarine, so just this time… I'll settle it for you! But if there's a next time, don't blame me for following the rules!"

Everyone was stunned.

Seeing Han Xiao's tone earlier, they were all mentally prepared to be punished by the faction. When they suddenly heard this, they froze.

Chapter 1292: Villain and Background

Jupiter originally thought he would be heavily punished this time but was stunned. Suddenly, his memories since Version 1.0 resurfaced. He was both relieved about not having to be punished and touched by Han Xiao's words.

As a professional guild leader on a salary, what he had in mind had always been how to operate the guild better. Although he also had some emotional attachment to the Black Star Army after so many years, he did not see the army as his own faction like the normal players. The interests of the guild were his priority.

However, at this time, he still felt great warmth in his heart. He felt a sense of nostalgia in Han Xiao's words.

However, though touched, Jupiter still could not help but ask, "Is this really ok? We caused bad influences after all…"

Han Xiao waved. "I understand the situation. If you people attacked a colonial planet out of nowhere, the army would strictly follow the rules and deal with you. However, your target was an enemy who kept disrupting your mission, and your mission in that area could not be carried out if you didn't kill him. Since I told you guys to take over the black market, I gave you some freedom. Although I'm not very satisfied with how you guys overdid it… since the Feeney Civilization chose to protect your enemy, they're an obstacle to our progress of taking over the black market, and they have to deal with the consequences of it. I can't let them bully my men."

"But the public opinion…"

Han Xiao interrupted him and casually said, "Although you guys were the fuse, the main conflict is still between us and the three Universal Civilizations. Even without this incident, they would find something else to shift the public opinion against us. I'm not going to punish the army's members because of my opponent's method of fighting us. Therefore, you guys don't have to pay for the pressure from the outside world this time."

Jupiter coughed and softly said, "But you became a target of the public too. Aren't you worried about your reputation…"

Han Xiao shook his head and said, "I hope you guys can reflect on your mistake this time. It's perfectly fine to eliminate enemies. If you come across enemies who disrupt the army's mission again, do what you need to, but be mindful of the impact it might cause and make sure to do it cleanly. Unless left with no choice, don't drag civilians into it. Request the army's assistance if you need to, but don't act alone again like this time and cause a large impact."

Then, Han Xiao looked around at everyone's pleasantly surprised faces and nodded in his mind. He believed these b*stards all understood his hint.

Ever since the start, he never wanted to completely forbid things like this but allowed it. He only wanted to guide them and make sure they did things cleanly, which he could not say out loud directly.

From the way he looked at it, what had happened had already happened. No matter what explanation he gave the outside world, it was not going to end up well. Therefore, he might as well ignore the public opinion guided by the three Universal Civilizations and let the army members do what they wanted to do, increasing the threat of the 'Cancer of the Universe' while removing the positive image the army had.

Before he opposed the three Universal Civilizations, the three Universal Civilizations had always been promoting him and increasing his reputation, making the galactic residents give him all kinds of titles and auras. They did these things both to praise him and restrain him; it was a double-edged sword.

With reputation, the actions of the army were restricted. If they did something that violated the rules, they would suffer for it. This was the rope the three Universal Civilizations tried to put on the army.

Han Xiao knew very well that as the form of conflict became more complex, remaining in the rules set by the opponent would only make things more difficult. Therefore, although the players caused a big mess this time, it could be a chance to adjust his strategy.

Wanted criminals like EsGod did tons of extremely evil things, but most people were only afraid of them and did not dare say anything. This was because they knew they were evil villains and did not dare mess with them. One of the important reasons the outside world dared to condemn and scold the Black Star Army was that, in their hearts, the Black Star Army was once 'good', and 'good' entities could be messed with.

After being 'good' for too long, others fear him less and less… Those many civilizations who responded to the call of the three Universal Civilizations and obstructed the association from uniting the black market more or less had this attitude. They felt that they had the Peace Treaty 'amulet', so they thought the Black Star Army would not dare violate the rules and do anything to them.

Clearly, this mindset was part of the reason the Feeney Civilization used its colonial planet to protect Dafis. If they really cared about the casualties of their citizens, they would not have done that.

If the other civilizations learned from them and improved on it, the association's work would only get tougher as time went on.

If the threat of the Cancer of the Universe increased through the Planet Burger incident and the outside world could see that there were a group of violent brutes in the army who were not afraid of violating the rules, some civilizations and Calamity Grade organizations would think twice before deciding to stand against the association…

Play and mess around all you like, but don't take the Cancer of the Universe lightly!

As long as things like this happened several times and they became afraid and intimidated, a lot of trouble could be avoided, which was beneficial to speeding up the takeover of the black market.

However, these things could not be said out loud. Therefore, the army was not going to admit to any accusations and would insist they were false. As for the truth, the outsiders would have to guess.

As for the public opinion… the three Universal Civilizations controlled the most powerful promotion tool, so his reputation would be damaged sooner or later. Han Xiao was already prepared for it. There was definitely a price to pay for standing against the three Universal Civilizations. Plus, his reputation and image were unreal.

Armed organizations were not civilizations, after all. The things they cared about were different. In the current situation, public opinion did not matter at all. No matter how bad it got, when it came to what mattered, the three Universal Civilizations would not dare make a move.

When he was working with the three Universal Civilizations, a positive reputation was beneficial for the army to obtain more partners and create a profit network. Now that the three Universal Civilizations had made a law that prohibited any civilization and consortium from working with the association, reputation no longer played a part. The image of being 'good' was useless; instead, being 'bad' worked better.

Because of exactly this, Han Xiao did not mind switching the army's reputation. To him, they were just different paths. As long as it could help him reach his goal, he would use whichever was better.

When the World Tree war broke out, the negative image would be meaningless. No one would care about such trivial matters then.

Of course, even though he decided to take the 'bad' path, there was still a limit to things. Therefore, he still had to restrain the players' actions to a certain extent. Hence, he personally criticized Jupiter and the others to subtly express his attitude. Causing small scale accidental casualties when fighting bosses was fine, but doing it deliberately was not allowed.

With what had happened, if the players crossed the line again in the future and he 'followed the rules' to punish them, most players would accept it.

Since he was going to insist that the army was not involved to the outside world and not stop the other players from imitating it, plus the Guild of Gods made the symbolic first kill which received much more attention among the players and acted within the limits, there was no need to give them any punishment today. Of course, he was not going to reward them either. The guild had to pay for the cost of fighting a boss.

Although this somewhat went against the 'punish all mistakes' rule, there was no right or wrong to most decisions made in complicated situations, only what was suitable or not. The rules had to be adjusted often.

Another reason for this was that Han Xiao knew very clearly who the teammates worth earning currently were—the players were the foundation of his rapid growth. His level 360 Promotion was extremely crucial and had to be done as soon as possible. Therefore, knowing his priorities, there was no need to hesitate.

As the enemy started it, unless the players retaliated too strongly, Han Xiao was neither going to stop them nor punish them. Otherwise, he would give them a feeling that they could only get beaten and not fight back, which would impact their sense of belonging to the faction severely, making them frustrated and possibly leave the faction.

Back in Version 4.0, the Black Star Army fought with multiple small factions. The small factions chose to restrain them and blame the players, while the Black Star Army protected its members and poached their players. Han Xiao was an expert in harvesting leeks; he was not going to make such a rookie mistake.

After all, players could not be easily restrained by simple management methods. Them challenging Calamity Grades was something that was bound to happen. Han Xiao knew the players' mindset very well.

Since we can't fight bosses properly here, we can just leave this faction. No way are we not going to fight bosses.

Han Xiao knew that not everyone had a strong sense of belonging to the faction.

As players grew stronger, their need for the faction would gradually decrease. Strength was what mattered most. With strength, they had the right to negotiate their prices and could be treated well anywhere. Plus, Han Xiao never doubted the players' interest in creating their own factions.

At this stage, the importance of profit had decreased among the factors that attracted the players to remain in the army. Instead, sense of belonging and habits proportionally increased. His long-term investments in the past netted more and more returns.

Therefore, Han Xiao spoke with the Guild of Gods personally to promote his 'emotional attachment' to the forums.

He already controlled the spaceship artificial intelligence, so the players could only use their interfaces to record. Therefore, this video would only circulate between the players. No one else would be able to see it.

"I understand. We'll definitely report to the army in the future for operations like this," Jupiter answered.

"Hmm, good." Han Xiao nodded. "Work hard and control the black market of this area soon."

After saying a few more words, Han Xiao ended the communication, and his remote projection disappeared.

The Guild of Gods exchanged looks and were all smiling with relief.

This feeling of being protected is amazing!

"Poseidon, I recorded the conversation. Should I put it on the forums?" Poseidon asked.

"Yes!" Overjoyed, Jupiter waved and said, "This is Black Star's personal stand, which means we have new information that's beneficial to everyone. Post it on the guild's behalf!"

Chapter 1293: Black Star Decides How Peaceful the Galaxy Is

The Guild of Gods' first Calamity Grade kill remained popular on the forums. Players were talking about it all the time. Although the Temple of God team had gotten quite a lot of blame in the past few years, they finally recovered from this first kill. Many players acknowledged and praised their achievement while feeling curious about the army's attitude toward this matter.

Although the galactic society was condemning this incident, the players did not give a damn. They all saw the post the Guild of Gods posted, which showed the entire incident, and Dafis clearly opposed the army. Plus, the Feeney Civilization protected Dafis first. From the way they looked at it, the Feeney Civilization deserved it and brought it upon themselves.

However, the condemnation from the outside world did indeed bring trouble to the army. Therefore, many players were waiting to see what the army would do to the Guild of Gods.

Meanwhile, seeing that the Guild of Gods started it, the other large clubs also had the same thoughts.

Although the first kill was gone, killing a Calamity Grade boss was a display of a guild's strength. The way the clubs looked at it, when more and more guilds killed Calamity Grade bosses, it would most likely become one of the basic criteria of becoming a big guild. When recruiting new members, if they saw that this guild had not even killed a Calamity Grade boss before, they would instantly be less attracted. Clearly, the big guilds of the various countries did not want to lose competitiveness.

However, their thoughts were only limited to that for the time being. Since the Guild of Gods did it first, the other guilds were waiting to see how the army dealt with it. They were going to make plans based on the army's stand. One way or another, they had to fight bosses, only with different methods.

Observed by many players, the Guild of Gods' official account released a video. The content of it was their conversation with Han Xiao. In just a few minutes, it was pinned to the top manually and received wide attention on the forums.

The players were surprised by Han Xiao's attitude and excitedly discussed it.

[The Germinal Organization Leader Is Always Watching: No punishment, Old Black is so generous!]

[Coolest Kid on Planet Aquamarine: Hahaha, I knew the army commander would be sensible. Otherwise, anyone could just hide on colonial planets after attacking us, and we wouldn't be able to attack them. This is the right decision.]

[Princess Feet: The army commander expressed his intention clearly. As long as we don't go overboard when fighting back, the army will back us up. Nice.]

[Army Commander's Big PP: Thank the Guild of Gods brothers for avenging me, amazingly done!]

[Poseidon: Now this is a reliable leader. Old Black never changed.]

[Bun-Hit-Dog: I'm new here, is this how he treats his old comrades? I'm so touched.]

The many players analyzed and discussed on the forums, confirming Black Star's intentions.

Firstly, when the guilds fought bosses, as long as it was an enemy, not only would the army not stop them from doing it, but it would also encourage it to a certain extent. For example, the army could provide some technological support, help them to create an undisrupted environment, and trap the target.

If they accidentally caused casualties while fighting bosses, as long as they had a reason such as someone protecting their enemy and they did not overdo it, the army would not punish them. Although Black Star did not clearly state what would be considered overdoing it, with the Guild of Gods example, as long as they did not go beyond that, it would definitely be fine.

Many Chinese players were very touched by Han Xiao's words. As for the majority of players who joined in the later versions, although they did not have much emotional attachment toward Black Star personally, they still felt good about the army's way of dealing with the incident.

Many guilds were also less worried.

They were worried that the Guild of Gods might be heavily punished, such as getting sealed by the Spacetime Amber. They did not want their guild pillars to face the risk of having their accounts 'banned' and would have no choice but to consider leaving the army. But since the faction's stand on this was sensible, they did not have to prepare for the worst.

…

Over the next ten days or so, the three Universal Civilizations continued to stir up public discussion about the topic. All kinds of verbal condemnations kept increasing. The public wanted the Black Star Army to give them an explanation and get rid of those who were involved.

However, the Black Star Army remained firm. The Black Star Army could explain how the Feeney Civilization protected Dafis on purpose, but there was no need to. They only stated that they were still investigating the matter and would not give in to such an accusation that had zero evidence, completely ignoring the public opinion the three Universal Civilizations deliberately stirred up.

The civilizations in the various Star Fields searched for the details through all kinds of channels. None of them believed what the three Universal Civilizations pushed the public to believe easily. They knew that there were definitely some things that were not publicized, and the truth could not possibly be as one-sided as the public believed. However, Planet Burger was indeed attacked. Even if there was more to the incident, the laws were indeed violated. Hence, the various civilizations were only watching and did not do anything.

Seeing the Black Star Army's attitude in this storm, many Star Systems sensed something.

The Peace Treaty set by the three Universal Civilizations had always been their protection. Anyone who violated the laws would be strictly punished. This was one of the key reasons they remained the rulers. For all this time, the Black Star Army had been following the laws like a tiger hiding its teeth and claws. The public gradually forgot about just how dangerous this tiger was out of habit… However, in a special time like now, if the Black Star Army no longer followed the laws strictly, could the three Universal Civilizations restrain them?

The answer was clear—hardly, if at all.

Currently, the three Universal Civilizations had used the laws against the association and closed the galactic society toward it. This was much more severe than the punishment of violating the laws. However, with that, the three Universal Civilizations had no further method of punishing the association anymore other than to start a war, which the association was not afraid of at all… The various civilizations knew that if the three Universal Civilizations were willing to start a war, they would not have waited this long.

In this situation, the various civilizations no longer felt that the three Universal Civilizations had the ability to force the association to follow the galactic laws. This meant that the strength of the protection from the Peace Treaty would definitely decrease.

Of course, judging from the Black Star Army's attitude, they probably did not intend to openly violate the galactic laws. However, as for the things that were in the gray area, Black Star most likely no longer held back. As for the three Universal Civilizations, they would definitely make a decision that caused the least problems for them. As long as the association did not deliberately attack a civilization, the three Universal Civilizations would most likely only make the public condemn them. The three Universal Civilizations doing something about it was not going to happen.

Having understood these things, many civilizations that answered to the three Universal Civilizations' call started to hesitate. If the Black Star Army no longer restrained themselves, the effects of the laws decreased tremendously. Clearly, continuing to oppose the association was no longer wise. Even if they stood on the three Universal Civilizations' side, they would only be used and would have to deal with the damage on their own in the end.

Facing this situation, many civilizations made similar decisions.

When these two giants fight, we're the ones suffering. We can't mess with either side, so it's better to keep a low profile. Responding to the three Universal Civilizations is one thing, but we'd better turn a blind eye regarding the Beyond Grade A Association's act of uniting the black markets everywhere. The three Universal Civilizations can send their own people to stop them all they like. We're not going to put in as much effort anymore.

This decision quickly circulated between the upper echelons of the various galactic civilizations. Even the Feeney Civilization was no longer as confident when seeing this. When they were interviewed by the media, although they still condemned the act, their word choice became less extreme and more cautious.

…

"Cancer of the Universe…"

Holmes browsed the messages on the quantum network and had a grave look.

He was a Calamity Grade super who operated an armed force in the Sea of Star Spirits. He was quite famous in the local Star System.

Ever since the Planet Burger incident got so big, Holmes had paid close attention to it.

He had come to know Dafis when he went to the Endless Nebulae on business in the past. The two of them became friends and occasionally chatted. Because of that, he knew about Dafis' recent work.

Inspired by Dafis, Holmes also secretly worked with the local civilization and did what Dafis was doing. Through obstructing the act of uniting the black market, he obtained resources and benefits from the civilization.

However, this incident startled Holmes.

He was not as strong as Dafis. When Dafis messed with the Cancer of the Universe and got chased all the way till he was killed, he became alarmed too.

While secretly obstructing the association, Holmes had killed some Immortals too. He could not help but be afraid of the Immortals grouping up and targeting him. He was not as arrogant as Dafis and did not think he could deal with the revenge of tons of Immortals.

There were risks to opposing the association to begin with. Holmes only agreed to working with the local civilization because they promised to protect him when needed.

However, the Black Star Army's response to the Planet Burger incident scared him. The Cancers of the Universe were very firm about taking revenge, so much so they were willing to violate galactic law. While the Black Star Army refused to admit anything… how useful could the protection the local civilization promised him be?

"The risk is getting higher. If the Cancers of the Universe come to take revenge, my life will be in danger too… I can't keep doing this."

With a worried expression, Holmes took out the communicator and called his contact in the local civilization.

Very soon, the contact appeared on the screen and smiled respectfully.

"Your Excellency Holmes, what can I do for you?"

Holmes cut to the chase and said with a grave tone, "From now on, our partnership will be terminated. I will no longer deal with the association's men taking over the black market for you guys."

The contact was stunned, surprised. He said hastily, "This is… so sudden. Is there anything you're not satisfied with in the agreement? We can talk about it. I'll…"

Holmes interrupted him and said with a deep voice, "My mind is set. Tell your upper echelons, the partnership stops here. I quit."

As he said that, not giving the contact a chance to reply, Holmes hung up the call right away. He stood up, walked back and forth in the room, and was still a little worried.

Hesitating for a while, Holmes clenched his teeth and walked toward the dock.

"I can't stay in my headquarters. The enemies might come. I shall go somewhere to hide for some time."

…

In the Central Galaxy, the three Universal Civilization leaders' conference room…

"Hmm, the Black Star Army's response is expected. Black Star indeed won't fall for this."

Louis looked at the report from the Public Opinion Control Department and nodded at the other two.

"Humph, of course. If Black Star was naive enough to respond and sell out his men, he'd be too easy to deal with. We wouldn't have to put in this much effort." Marbruce crossed his arms and snorted.

The Feeney Civilization provided them with an opportunity, and they took it; that was all. They only wanted to damage Black Star's positive reputation and never expected to force Black Star to obey using the public opinion. That would clearly be daydreaming.

The church's pope tapped the table and said, "Although Black Star's positive reputation is decreasing and we have the moral high ground, he also used this to defuse the locks we had on him, which will only make the various civilizations fear him more. Instead of causing problems for him, it's become a problem for us."

"Using the cancers of the universe to do the dirty work and intimidate others, what a good plan." Louis frowned. "According to the intelligence, many Star System civilizations are already unwilling to continue sending people to hold the black market. Looks like we have no choice but to send our Immortals too."

"Hmm, cancers of the universe against cancers of the universe, it's the most efficient way." Marbruce nodded.

The three Universal Civilizations had raised some Immortals too. To them, letting Immortals fight each other was clearly more efficient than spending their direct troops. After all, they would not feel hurt if the Immortals died.

The church's pope said with a deep voice, "But the Immortals are very difficult to control and restrain. If they make a mess…"

The three of them exchanged looks and were all troubled.

The players in the three Universal Civilizations were just as difficult to control. They caused quite a number of problems, but the three Universal Civilizations did not have any good methods of dealing with them. They had punished them many times, but some of them just left the faction and joined some other organization. Some even became wanted criminals. Because they controlled these Immortals too strictly, they lost quite a number of them.

As Version 5.0 began, the strength of the players started to increase again. The three Universal Civilizations realized the seriousness of the matter too and suspected the Immortals had the potential to become Calamity Grades.

If that day ever came, the cancers of the universe would be the most suitable opponents for the cancers of the universe. Therefore, they had to have enough Immortals in their hands and could not afford to lose any more of them. Hence, the three Universal Civilizations gave the players special treatment, not punishing them unless absolutely necessary. However, they still could not stop the Immortals from leaving. The three Universal Civilizations had always been beleaguered by this matter.

Hence, the three of them were very envious of the Black Star Army. The Immortals who they could not control were already very obedient in the Black Star Army's hands. In the entire universe, the Black Star Army restrained the Immortals most effectively.

Now, the Black Star Army showed signs of taking away this restraint, and if it really did it…

Marbruce shook his head, changed the topic, and said, "Sigh, let's skip this for now. The most important matter now is to confirm if Black Star can freely use the Sanctum Revival."

The other two shook their heads but still looked grave.

If the Black Star Army's Immortals continued to grow, it was very likely that in the future…

Black Star would become the one to decide how peaceful the Galaxy was!

Chapter 1294: Memory File and First Unique Talent

As time passed and the galactic civilization saw that the three Universal Civilizations still did not make any move, they realized the situation. Knowing the three Universal Civilizations could not do anything to the Black Star Army, the public gradually condemned the Black Star Army less.

On one day, the Super Star Cluster Alliance received an anonymous piece of information that stated how the Feeney Civilization protected Dafis. The Super Star Cluster Alliance then released this piece of information without hesitation and promoted it, quickly shifting the public opinion in another direction.

At this point, the masterminds behind this incident basically all got what they wanted and stopped making moves. Without those who guided the public opinion, very soon, voices online quietened down. The galactic society was never in shortage of topics and news, other new events quickly attracted the attention of the galactic residents.

However, the impact this incident caused remained.

The various civilizations adjusted their strategy, no longer willing to participate in the conflict between the three Universal Civilizations and the association. They stopped part of their disruptions of the black market, making the work of the various Beyond Grade A organizations easier.

Without the local civilizations working for free, the three Universal Civilizations dispatched their own Immortals to interfere in the black market conflict and deal with the Black Star Army's Immortals.

The conflict between players had no restraints. In the next month or so, the two sides fought intensely. Many planets with black markets became battlefields. With the technological aid from the army, the various big guilds eliminated hostile Calamity Grade Supers one after another. The Cancer of the Universe title became more and more recognized.

Han Xiao, however, did not pay attention to how boisterous it got in the outside world. While the two sides were fighting night and day, he spent most of the time in the lab, reverse engineering SWY-001 continuously while building new Universal Treasures to increase his God's Trait Transformation stage.

One day, he finally made a breakthrough in the reverse engineering of SWY-001.

…

In the bright research lab, SWY-001's enormous body was fixed in the middle covered in tons of operating multifunctional mechanical arms, doing all kinds of reverse analysis.

Mechanical assistants flew around SWY-001 in midair, transporting parts from time to time like bees.

Han Xiao hovered in midair at the same height with SWY-001's head. Beside him was a round anti-gravity worktable. Tons of neatly arranged virtual screens surrounded him, showing all kinds of parameters nonstop. He commanded the various research teams through this worktable.

"The deciphering is finally done…"

Han Xiao let out a deep breath.

After more than a month, he had finally deciphered the many modules of SWY-001. Of course, the memory file was the most important among them. He already deciphered it completely and turned it into readable data.

On the virtual screen, tons of information was displayed. The meaningless data was all filtered out, leaving only the essence of SWY-001.

Han Xiao browsed through. The useful information could mainly be classified into three groups. One was the various technology this mechanical body used, another was the blueprints in the memories of those Mechanics who sacrificed themselves, and the last was their memories about that unknown civilization.

The name of this Universal Civilization eliminated by the World Tree Civilization was 'Karma Republic' after translating it into the galaxy common language.

Unlike the explored universe, the Karma Republic was the only Universal Civilization in the area it was in. It took over all the other races in its area, turning them into its own subsidiary civilizations and had absolutely control over them. The Karma Republic even distributed all of their territories and lands.

They created a surveillance system and came up with Civilization Levels. They made the rule that the results of the research and developments of all civilizations had to be reported, copied, and given to the Karma Republic. If they made breakthroughs, they would gain 'Civilization Points'. With enough points, the civilization would be allowed to level up and receive better privileges with the Karma Republic's approval.

If a civilization could not make any technological breakthroughs in many years and could not reach the minimum point of a certain period, that civilization would be downgraded. The Karma Republic would retrieve all kinds of privileges including its territories.

The galactic society level of the Karma Republic was very strict. Although the competition between civilizations gave them a certain amount of motivation, overall, the atmosphere of the entire society was still quite boring. After all, all of their developments were monitored and controlled by the Karma Republic. They could see the end of their path right away. Most civilizations had no choice but to spend the majority of their resources on research projects to maintain their level or level up. As for the lives of their citizens, it was kept at the minimum.

Most citizens were only surviving too. Under the strict control of the Karma Republic, the cost of violating the law was way too high, so there was no point in doing it. The Super knowledges were also strictly controlled by the Karma Republic and could not be spread freely. The only way to learn them was legally.

If things went on normally, the Karma Republic's civilization strength would continue to rise as time passed, absorbing the nutrition of so many subsidiary civilizations at the same time. Sadly, they met the World Tree Civilization and were wiped out in the end.

As Super knowledges were strictly controlled, the Karma Republic had firm control over the various civilizations under them. However, because of that, they lacked high level combatants and had fewer than twenty Beyond Grade As. Plus, due to the lack of conflict, there were only two peak Beyond Grade As.

Both had its pros and cons. The three Universal Civilizations were worried about individual strength going out of control but accumulated tons more high-level combatants because of it. Chaos would breed more strong individuals. The Karma Republic did not have such worries, but when facing an exterior enemy, they ended up not having enough high-level combatants.

Facing the overwhelming attack of the World Tree Civilization, the high-level combatants of the Karma Republic almost collapsed on the spot. In the end, they were forced to use a technology called 'Fusion Mechanical Ascension' that only Mechanic Supers could use.

Through focusing the strength of one peak Beyond Grade A, tons of Grade As and Grade Bs, they aimed to help this peak Beyond Grade A break through the limits and turn into a real 'Mechanical God', stepping into the higher territory. However, it failed in the end. Although they did obtain a much stronger individual, he did not evolve and was defeated in battle surrounded by the people of the World Tree Civilization.

Han Xiao looked at the information of the technology. The interface showed that the name of the blueprint was [Fusion Mechanical Ascension]. Other than the functions he already knew, the side effect was that the user's personality would change and become a collective consciousness.

"This technology can't reach its planned goal, but it is a breakthrough for them nonetheless. It's not very useful to me on its own, but the modules formed after the fusion are very powerful. Maybe I can reverse engineer them, imitate their structure, and create a new Mechanical Deity?"

The SWY-001 was the combination of flesh and machinery. The flesh provided tons of Super cells that gave the machinery the Mechanical Force it needed. He had [Polar Channel Flow—Blood Rage], so he should be able to achieve the same effect if done correctly.

If he could successfully imitate SWY-001's form, he had a feeling that his Mechanical Deity would undergo a huge change.

Other than [Fusion Mechanical Ascension], Han Xiao also obtained tons of blueprints from the mechanical body's memory file. However, only the peak Beyond Grade A's memories had a few Gold blueprints.

Han Xiao recorded all that technology before looking at the decipher page of the memory chip.

He was done deciphering the quantum network code of the Karma Republic and broke through the firewall long ago, so he could already rewrite SWY-001's artificial intelligence program.

Han Xiao hesitated for a while before closing this page. He did not want to make modifications to it before finding out the connection between the artificial intelligence consciousness and SWY-001's biological consciousness.

"Speaking of which, I'm not sure if there's some kind of bonus to studying SWY-001 or not, but the trigger rate of my Unique Talent is quite high for some reason."

Han Xiao looked at the interface. In the past month of studying SWY-001, the progress of obtaining a Unique Talent was triggered again and was at 75.8% now.

According to the previous progress it made every time it was triggered, a Unique Talent would be formed after triggering it two more times.

However, he had no idea when these two times would happen. Since he was only a quarter away from completing the progress, Han Xiao leaned toward completing it using Awakening Points. He did not do it in the past because his progress was too low, but now that he was very close to completing it, the cost became much lower.

The players had already been online for quite some time, and he had accumulated quite a lot of EXP. Although he was still far from the Promotion at level 360, leveling up a few levels was not a problem. Plus, when he used Random Rewards to try to acquire Mission Completion Cards, he sometimes got lucky and obtained Awakening Points too.

"Let's try it. It should be doable."

Han Xiao put all his EXP into leveling up all the way to level 344 before it ran out.

He took out one Awakening Point, put it into his Unique Talent, and a notification popped up.

Use 1 Awakening Point to increase the progress of Unique Talent? [Confirm/Cancel]

Confirmed.

According to the level of this Unique Talent, 1 Awakening Point = 2.8%–3.2% progress.

Unique Talent Progress +3.02%.

Current Progress: 78.82%.

"A three-percent increase for one point on average…"

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. This was much better than expected.

He would be able to obtain a Unique Talent with just about seven or eight more Awakening Points this way.

According to the rules of the Awakening Points, a hundred points could activate the basic structure of a Unique Talent, and the accumulation of progress would only start after that. Converting one Awakening Point to three percent, the cost of obtaining a Unique Talent from nothing would at least be 134 Awakening Points.

He had naturally activated the basic structure of his Unique Talent, then slowly accumulated the progress to about seventy-five percent, meaning he saved 125 Awakening Points.

"At most eight Awakening Points, which I have right now and don't even have to level up abilities for. The cost is completely acceptable. I'll do it."

Han Xiao rubbed his hands. With excitement, he put one Awakening Point after another into the progress of his Unique Talent.

Very soon, with enough Awakening Points, the progress finally reached a hundred percent!

A notification popped up on the interface.

Unique Talent Awakened.

Please select one main focus for the talent from the three options below.

Basic Attributes.

Special Resistances.

Main Class Enhancements.

"Oh? So, this is how it is…"

Han Xiao raised his brows. He had thought the effects of a Unique Talent were completely random, but it turned out that he had a certain extent of freedom in choosing his preferences. This reminded him of creating his Racial Talent back when he became a Beyond Grade A.

There were not many choices. It was probably because the Unique Talent progressed naturally.

Maybe if he used Awakening Points since the start, he would be able to completely design it to his likings.

Han Xiao hesitated for a while, then chose the Main Class Enhancements.

Main focus confirmed.

Please select one secondary focus for the talent from the three options below.

Machinery Building.

Virtual Technology.

Machinery Combat.

"The two Unique Talents of old Manison are building and Virtual Technology, which should be strong enough for me…"

Han Xiao considered for a while, then chose the third choice.

Secondary focus confirmed.

Please replace one of the bonuses from the three options below.

Long-range Attacks.

Mechanical Force Enhancements.

Machinery Efficiency Enhancements.

"Replace one effect, huh? This means that these last three options are the bonuses given by the talent in the end."

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, pondered for a few seconds, and chose the first one. It was the only one that was slightly weaker than the other two.

Replacement complete.

[Long-range Attacks] randomly switched to [Class Main Attribute Bonus].

All preferences confirmed, creating Unique Talent…

Creation complete.

You have received Unique Talent [(Unnamed)—Han Xiao]!

(Unnamed)—Han Xiao: +10% INT. In battle, +1.2 Mechanical Force multiplier, +1.3% machinery efficiency multiplier. All multipliers are applied after other bonuses.

Remarks: (To be filled).

You have received your first Unique Talent.

Difficulty of activating the next Unique Talent increased. Initial level of the next Unique Talent increased, meaning higher bonuses and more preferences.

Chapter 1295: The Second Key and Invasion Operation

"Overall multiplier bonus, huh? Quite powerful."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

The bonuses of this talent clearly reached the Molding Talent level.

Given his current Intellect, the ten-percent Intellect increase would give him a few thousand Intellect points. With the Mechanical Force strength and the Machinery Efficiency bonuses, his actual combat capability increased significantly. One of his Apostle Weapons could now fight a high level Beyond Grade A for some time.

Judging from the interface's description, the difficulty in awakening Unique Talents increased each time he obtained one, but the effects would also be stronger. Old Manison had both a single bonus talent [Virtual Technology Innovation] and a large-scale bonus talent [Billion Mechanic Empire]. Clearly, Manison obtained the latter many Unique Talents later than the former. Yet, Han Xiao acquired it easily.

"Sigh, Old Manison, oh Old Manison, how sad for you…"

Han Xiao sighed and was so sad he laughed.

Since his Unique Talent would get stronger after each one he acquired, he could not complain about his first Unique Talent. Only, he had no idea when he would trigger the brief structure of the next Unique Talent.

"I wonder if Old Manison has talents that increase the chances of awakening Unique Talents…"

Han Xiao subconsciously licked his lips and was tempted.

Thinking back, he had to admit that Old Manison really had a rich inventory. Sadly, he was an ally on his side now, or he might really be tempted to hack into Old Manison's database… After all, others' databases were way too tempting to Mechanics.

Putting this impulsive thought behind, Han Xiao looked at the interface. The name and the remarks of the talent had yet to be filled up, and he had a headache about it.

As an 'expert' in naming things, he had extremely low confidence in his ability to name things.

"What should I call it? I have to think of a proper name this time, or what will happen if the players get this talent through Character Summon Cards one day?"

Han Xiao pondered for a while and filled in a name he felt was acceptable.

Having confirmed the name, the content of the talent was updated on the interface right away, and he could not change it again.

Emperor of War—Han Xiao

Remark: Born for wars.

"This name should be normal for this kind of fighting talent."

Han Xiao felt it was fine, but he was not very sure about his naming sense. However, since he had already named it, he stopped dwelling on the matter.

As he was about to leave the lab and try out his new talent at a desolate planet nearby, his communicator suddenly rang.

He took out to look at it, and to his surprise, it was the head of the Land of Four Gods, the elderly whom he beat up before, 'Mystery Mage' Joey Terrain.

He accepted the communication request, and Joey appeared on the screen.

"What is it? Have you contacted me because you guys made up your minds?" Han Xiao sounded interested.

Joey looked a little gloomy, took a deep breath, and said softly, "We agree to join the Beyond Grade A Association, but we hope to keep our freedom. Plus, the coordinates of the Land of Four Gods must remain a secret to the other members. We'll attend the plenaries, and if something important happens, we'll also provide assistance, but we won't be forced… Is this okay?"

Han Xiao smiled.

These four b*stards finally made up their minds. This was probably their limit.

"Sure, this is a good start. With you guys, the association will become stronger. I won't publicize the coordinates of your secondary dimension, and the association doesn't force its members to do anything. However, I'll mention you guys are Beyond Grade As who retired. Plus, you guys have to be at the venue yourselves when showing up for the first time. Is that ok?"

"Sure." Joey nodded and hesitantly said, "So, about the Sanctum Revival…"

"Don't worry, you're one of us after joining the association. If you guys die, I'll revive you."

"That's good…"

"Alright, send me all of your information later. I'll register you guys into the association and arrange for your welcome ceremony."

After chatting a bit longer, Han Xiao hung up the call. About ten seconds later, he received the personal information of the four of them and told Phillip to arrange the procedures to have them join the association.

He thought for a while before calling Oathkeeper. He had already spoken with some of the Holy Accord members to have them appear in public when the time was right. Since Joey and the others were joining the association too, he might as well have them join at the same time so that it would be easier and more convenient.

Very soon, Oathkeeper appeared on the screen.

"Black Star, what is it?"

"Hmm, it's about the welcome ceremony of a new batch of Holy Accord members. I've already made the arrangements, so you can have them come to the Flickering World now," Han Xiao said.

"I'll tell them." Oathkeeper nodded. He hesitated for a moment before suddenly saying, "Black Star, there's one thing I have to tell you. The second set of the Sanctum keys have almost all been collected."

"… So soon?"

Han Xiao was surprised.

Oathkeeper was in charge of this matter, and Han Xiao did not pay close attention to it. He thought the Holy Accord would need a few years to collect the second set of keys. He did not expect them to be this efficient.

"Yes. The resources list the Super Star Cluster Alliance provided included quite a number of materials for the Sanctum keys that are very difficult to purchase elsewhere, but these advanced civilizations had them. Some more sensitive materials that are banned from circulating on the market are surprisingly circulating on the black market, and you gave them to us, which increased our progress greatly," Oathkeeper explained.

"I see." Han Xiao understood and felt relieved like invisible weights were lifted off from his shoulders.

He would only really be confident about facing the cleansing with the second set of Sanctum keys. He no longer had to act like it in front of the three Universal Civilizations.

"Which Sanctum?"

"The First Sanctum this time."

Han Xiao was delighted.

The Third Sanctum he entered the last time contained knowledge mostly about biology, genes, and Esper Abilities. Although he acquired quite a lot of knowledges, it was not very compatible with his class. However, the First Sanctum seemed to be closely connected with machinery technology. If he could enter it once, he would probably obtain the technology that suited Mechanics best, which would be incredible.

It just so happened that his authority level in the First Sanctum was even higher than the Third Sanctum. He currently had seven fragments. Entering the First Sanctum would give him one more, meaning he would have level eight authority when he entered and would be able to do many more things while inside.

"What about the collection of the keys of the other Sanctums?"

"I'll show you…" Oathkeeper sent him a set of data.

The Holy Accord recorded the progress of the several Sanctum keys, so it was easier to see. At this point, other than the First Sanctum key, which was at ninety-two percent, the second highest was the Third Sanctum key, which was at sixty-seven percent. The others were all around forty percent, except for the Sixth Sanctum, which was only at seven percent.

Han Xiao looked at the progress before looking at the material lists of the various keys. "I'll pay attention to these materials too. Keep up the good…"

"Hmm, you keep up the good work too. The organization will treat you generously." Oathkeeper said it and felt extremely good. Before Han Xiao could respond, he hung up the communication right away.

Han Xiao placed the communicator down, scratched his head, and had a weird expression.

Usually, he was the one who spoke like that to Oathkeeper. However, this time, Oathkeeper suddenly changed his tone and took him by surprise.

Interesting, he's not happy with being ordered around by me, so he wants to gain small advantages over me verbally?

Humph, childish…

I'll definitely say it quicker than you next time!

Han Xiao curled his lips and decided not to be concerned. Besides, everybody knew who was making the calls.

"The second set of keys is almost ready. I can consider showing some of my cards to the three Universal Civilizations now…"

Han Xiao focused and pondered.

According to his judgement of the situation, one of the most effective ways to defuse the stalemate between the three Universal Civilizations and the association was to seek peace after a war. Let the three Universal Civilizations start the cleansing and let the two sides fight all they wanted. When the association suffered from severe losses, they would revive all their members and display the truth about the Sanctum Revival not having a limited number of uses.

This way, while learning a painful lesson, the three Universal Civilizations would realize there was no way they could restrain the Beyond Grade As. Then, they would most likely abandon their current strategy and focus on studying the Sanctums. The balance achieved through this should last for a very long time.

However, although this method would have limited damages to the Beyond Grade A Association, the three Universal Civilizations would suffer severely from it. After all, the destroyed fleets, armies, and killed soldiers could not be revived. If the three Universal Civilizations' direct members died in this war, even though the Sanctum Revival could revive them, Han Xiao was definitely going to postpone their revival to after reviving the association's members.

He had two goals, one to deal with the World Tree, another to protect the Beyond Grade A class to not take the Celestial Star Alliance's path. The former was more important.

"Before the World Tree war breaks out, it's best not to cause too much damage to the military force of the explored universe. Therefore, the intensity of the conflict has to be controlled; the association can't start a battle, and the current situation has to be maintained. This plan can only be executed if the three Universal Civilizations actively start a cleansing…"

Han Xiao let out a deep breath.

From another perspective, stopping the cleansing was possible. In order to avoid damaging the explored universe's strength, he might have to go against his initial plan and share the World Tree Civilization's information in advance so that the war would break out earlier…

However, whether the three Universal Civilizations believed it or not was not for him to decide.

"Hope the three Universal Civilizations don't play with fire. Maintaining the current state is good enough…"

In the Primeval Star River, somewhere in a desolate universe belt, a spherical galactic fortress hovered. It looked like an enlarged metal brain. This was a Super Long Range Virtual Mind Wave Enhancer. On its surface were matrix-style quantum network bases that could hide the data sent to a certain extent and enhance the strength of a Virtual Intrusion.

Two round mechanical devices flew around it. This was the Federation of Light's Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device. Outside it, highly advanced stealth devices hovered like buoys and shrouded the area, preventing all kinds of detection means, including prophecies.

At this point of time, the avatars of Mornisa and several Beyond Grade A Mechanics sat inside the Virtual Mind Wave Enhancer on their own seats. They were all direct members of the three Universal Civilizations.

After preparing for about two to three months, the three Universal Civilizations finally agreed to this operation. The participants were all direct Beyond Grade A mechanics. Led by Mornisa and assisted by the three Universal Civilizations, they had gone to the Primeval Star River to hack into Manison's database.

The three Universal Civilizations took out many cutting-edge devices, even sharing the computing power of their civilizations' main artificial intelligences to help with the intrusion, all to successfully break into Manison's database and take him by surprise.

"Virtual Mind Wave Enhancer and Intrusion Style Quantum Network Base Matrix operating at full power output, Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device entering preheating stage… Federation of Light, Crimson Dynasty, Arcane Church main artificial intelligence computing power shared. Hacking route adjusted. Preparation complete. Please give the command."

The emotionless voice of an artificial intelligence sounded in the room.

Mornisa looked around at the teammates present, and a red light flashed across her avatar as she firmly said, "Guys, let's do it!"

Chapter 1296: Siege

Inside the wide factory filled with mechanical devices, many mechanical arms were working constantly. Teams of mechanical assistants worked day and night, and countless assembly lines produced all kinds of machines.

Manison hovered midair in the factory and meditated with closed eyes. Golden electric arcs jumped on his body like snakes. His brain was operating rapidly, focusing on training his computing power. This was something most Virtual Mechanics did every day.

While he traveled in the sea of data, an alarm suddenly rang from the firewall at the link between his mind and the quantum network, echoing loudly in his mind!

"Alert! Alert! Abnormal data detected, infiltrating the database firewall!"

Manison suddenly opened his eyes, his focused state interrupted.

"Someone's hacking into my database?"

He frowned and subconsciously thought of Han Xiao.

The last time someone did this was many years ago. Could it be that b*stard Black Star this time?

Although they were now on the same side, Manison never stopped expecting the worst from Black Star.

His consciousness sunk into the quantum network. Through the network nodes, he instantly jumped to the firewall that was hacked. The next moment, the scene before his eyes changed drastically, and he came to a virtual world formed of data streams.

In front of him was a thick firewall like layers of translucent protective shields, and endless code flowed on its surface. This was what protected his virtual artificial intelligence center and his multiple databases, making it invisible on the quantum network so that ordinary people could not find it.

Anyone who could hack into it would either be a Beyond Grade A or the main artificial intelligence of an advanced civilization or a large organization. Regardless, the attacker did not come with good intentions.

At this time, a large pile of slightly illuminated dark purple data stream was stuck to the surface of the firewall like a slime, rolling and moving nonstop to corrode the firewall. Large portions of purple spread out. At a micro perspective, the two sides' data codes were slaughtering each other at the point of contact. The shattered bits of the firewall reformed and became the purple data stream's bits, devoured and assimilated by this strange data stream, causing its size to slowly grow.

Inside the firewall, a data stream rose from the ground and turned into the appearance of Manison's Virtual Soul. He looked at this with narrowed eyes, extended his palm, and grabbed a data stream. The two sides of the data stream extended outward, and it turned into the shape of a staff in Manison's hands.

He tapped the ground with the staff, data streams rose from the ground like lava and quickly became a fully armored AI soldier army, standing behind him.

Having completed the preparation for battle, only then did Manison speak with a poker face. "Dare to invade my territory but don't dare show yourself?"

As soon as he said that, Mornisa's virtual figure appeared outside the firewall. Looking at Manison who was protected by the firewall, she coldly said, "We meet again… teacher!"

"So, it's you." Manison narrowed his eyes. "What, you still haven't given up?"

In the past, Mornisa tried to secretly steal his technology because she found out some secret routes from him, so her ambition pushed her to do it. However, back then, Mornisa was not strong enough and failed; Manison discovered her plan and scolded her heavily. Afterward, Mornisa joined the Federation of Light, and this matter was left unsettled.

In all these years, Manison had taught many Mechanics, Mornisa being the most talented one among them. After Mornisa became a Beyond Grade A, he originally wanted to support her to found her own organization, make her his ally, and indirectly expand his forces. Sadly, Mornisa stabbed him in the back, and this plan was abandoned. Since then, the two of them had been colleagues instead of teacher and student.

However, although their relationship was not good, they did not instantly become enemies. On the contrary, the two of them maintained a certain extent of information partnership all this time. Mornisa occasionally provided some not so crucial internal information to Manison, from the way Manison looked at it, she was her way of fawning upon him and keeping him from attacking her.

He considered himself as someone who knew the personality of this student quite well. She was someone who would not give up easily once she set a goal for herself and would definitely find all methods possible to achieve it. She was not going to give up stealing his technology so easily.

Therefore, Mornisa's invasion was out of Manison's expectations but within his understanding.

Hearing this, Mornisa snickered. "Teacher, times have changed. Black Star's rise took away the faith of the Machinery Faith; you're no longer the invincible Mechanic Emperor you were decades ago."

Hearing Black Star's name, Manison snorted in his mind and did not refute it. He said, "Even so, beating you will still be easy."

"I'm not so overconfident to think I'm capable of fighting you alone…" A sarcastic smile appeared on Mornisa's face as she said, "I came with help this time!"

As soon as she said that, unusual data streams rose simultaneously from a few other directions and suddenly crashed into the firewall. Tons of code fragments shattered. Along with the data streams, a few other Beyond Grade A Mechanics appeared.

With the support of the part of the computing power of the main artificial intelligence of the three Universal Civilizations, the speed at which they broke through the firewall received astonishing bonuses. Defense blocks were shattered one after another, and layers of firewalls were filled with holes.

He was surrounded instantly!

Manison's expression changed slightly. These people were all direct members of the three Universal Civilizations. This was clearly a joint operation from the three sides.

Dealing with the invasion of several Beyond Grade A Mechanics was already troublesome enough, yet on top of that, the three Universal Civilizations even shared part of the computing power of their own main artificial intelligence to assist them.

The main artificial intelligences of the three Universal Civilizations had the highest computing power in the entire universe. They were improved and updated by Beyond Grade A Mechanics one generation after another, even fusing the memories, experience, and part of these Mechanics' consciousnesses. They could be considered the strongest tools in the Virtual Technology field. Without them, the three Universal Civilizations' core database would have been infiltrated many times.

However, usually, most of the computing power of the main artificial intelligences had to be used to maintain the operation of the civilizations' affairs, so their strength was not displayed. If all of their computing power was focused in one, it would be extremely horrifying.

Since the three of them were working together to assist several direct Beyond Grade A Mechanics, this kind of power was tough for one person to match up to. Sure, Manison was strong, but he still had limits.

Plus, because of Black Star, he was no longer at peak strength. He could not help but feel powerless.

"The three Universal Civilizations really think quite highly of me, huh," Manison said with a deep voice.

"Blame yourself for being so cocky in the past, always trying to steal the Federation of Light's secrets. The federation has put up with you for a very long time, only letting you off because you were their loyal ally. You should've known this day would come. I only made the suggestion to the three Universal Civilizations and made it come sooner.

"They want to cleanse the secrets you stole and the intelligence of the various civilizations in the Primeval Star River you collected… As for your technology, they're just rewards for me."

Mornisa's tone was filled with mockery and glee.

Manison snorted. Knowing there was no point in saying anything, he stomped the ground with his staff.

The next moment, the artificial intelligence soldier army charged forward to stop their invasion, while Finette appeared with many artificial intelligence lives and joined the battle.

At the same time, beams made of data streams suddenly shot out from the firewall, evaporating large portions of the invading data stream. The firewall's formation also started to shift. The traps within were activated one after another to stop the enemies' data streams.

As he opposed the three Universal Civilizations back during the Intelligent Plague, Manison planned ahead and reinforced his firewall afterward, as well as added a lot of Virtual Technology measures, all to prepare for this situation.

"You're still the same. But, even if you made preparations in advance, can you stop us today?" Mornisa's eyes flickered.

"Try me." Manison was not affected.

The enemies' invasion was stronger than he expected. He had already used all measures he had and was still unsure if he could hold on.

The two sides' data stream continued slaughtering each other, analyzing and defusing each other's tricks. The amount of information processed every second was unimaginable.

The passage of time in the Virtual Domain was different. It relied on the speed of the individual's mind. To the Beyond Grade As, every second felt countless times longer.

Facing the powerful attacks, Manison started to show signs of defeat. The thickness of the firewall kept getting thinner, holes started to appear, and part of the low-level data at the exterior of the database was exposed.

The enemy's data needles penetrated through these holes and stirred up a tsunami within, sending out data streams even deeper… The secret database at the most inside was their key target of this battle.

Although the situation was not good, Manison's mood was still unaffected. He carefully tightened his line of defense, fighting the enemies firmly and accurately, cleaning out their data streams.

While Mornisa controlled her data stream and tried to penetrate Manison's defenses, she taunted with a mocking tone, "Teacher, your abilities have become quite a lot weaker. Losing the bonuses from ruling the Machinery Faith and falling from your peak strength sure doesn't feel good, does it?

"Why don't you seek help from Black Star? Black Star would probably generously help someone he defeated… Oops, almost forgot, we blocked all communications to the outside world. We will have gotten what we came for by the time you send a rescue message.

"Black Star has been suffocating you, taking away what belongs to you time after time. I'm only surprised by how you can put up with how he treats you. If it were in the past, how could you let him be? Tsk tsk, you've really gotten more cowardly now you're older, or did Black Star scare the sh*t out of you?"

Harassment came one message after another, all hitting where it hurt in Manison's heart.

However, he maintained a poker face. His computing power was unaffected, and he coldly said, "… You done?"

Hearing this, Mornisa suddenly felt as if a blood red 'danger' appeared above her head.

Just as she was about to react, Manison's Virtual Soul lit up and locked onto her.

The next moment, a strange data stream appeared.

Mornisa's sight turned blurry. Her Virtual Soul was dragged into a silver data world filled with countless machines by an irresistible force. An enormous silver giant stood before her; it was indeed Manison.

Manison looked down, his eyes like a god looking at mortals. He opened his mouth, and his voice echoed in this world.

"Are you prepared for a beating?"

Mornisa mocked, "Since I dared come to you, I prepared long ago. Getting beat up in exchange for your technology is worth it. Plus, this is just Virtual Paramount. How long can you trap me here?"

"Not long… but more than enough to thrash you, rebellious student!"

Manison bent his waist. His fist fell instantly and bashed Mornisa's Virtual Soul into a patty.

The entire world shook!

Chapter 1297: Change

Boom! Boom! Boom!

Countless cannons roared, launching attacks toward Mornisa. The silver giant Manison thrashed Mornisa's Virtual Soul.

In the Virtual Paramount territory, Mornisa was completely powerless and could do nothing but take Manison's thunderous attacks. Agony rushed into her mind like a tsunami, wave after wave. Her mind almost stopped working. Her Virtual Soul was buzzing with white noise and looked extremely unstable.

"Argh!" Mornisa screamed and wailed. Although she was mentally prepared to get a beating from Manison, when her consciousness felt such intense pain, she could hardly endure it. She could feel the murderous intent from Manison's attacks.

This pain reminded her of the lesson Manison gave her when she failed to steal his technology for the first time.

Back then, Mornisa had just become a Beyond Grade A. It was a time when she was arrogant and overconfident, and she did not know much about how strong the senior Beyond Grade As were. After she failed, she got absolutely crushed by Manison; all attempts to fight back were meaningless. She was just as helpless as she was now, being tortured like a powerless doll.

At that time, Manison adjusted her perception of reality, and the deep fear pushed Mornisa to join the Federation of Light.

This humiliating memory had been suppressed at the bottom of her heart. At this time, this mental scar of hers was reopened. Mornisa could almost feel her soul shivering intuitively. She clenched her teeth and endured the torture, hoping Manison would soon stop.

After an unknown period of time, Mornisa, who was doing her best to endure the pain, suddenly felt refreshed and left the Virtual Paramount territory, returning to the Virtual Intrusion battlefield where an intense battle was still carried out.

Mornisa's mind almost collapsed. Although the actual amount of time she was controlled was very short, she felt like she had been tortured nonstop for more than a decade. It felt like countless mixers were stirring up her brain, turning her brain tissues into a mess.

Furthermore, in order to keep hacking, she could not stop working her mind and had no choice but to remain conscious, making the pain even worse.

In the moment right after she left the Virtual Paramount territory, her mind still remained stunned for a second. Her computing power plummeted, and the attacks on the area she was in charge of suddenly slowed down.

In this short instant, Manison who was prepared for it suddenly released a sea of data streams, attempting to break through the communication lock and send a message to the outside world.

Buzz!

Suddenly, layers of light curtains rose at the edge of this virtual battlefield. The data lock barrier formed by the main artificial intelligences of the three Universal Civilizations cut off the data sent to the outside world. These enormous streams of data bumped into the barrier and exploded like countless mosquitoes rushing onto an electric net, instantly vanishing.

"Ahem, don't think you can easily send a message out while I'm wounded. I expected this…" Mornisa was still in a weakened state, but she still snickered when she saw this.

Maintaining the same poker face, Manison waited for Virtual Paramount to cool down while fighting against the invasion as well as trying to send a message to the outside world by any means necessary.

With his Virtual Technology, it was almost impossible for them to lock him down completely, but he still needed some time to break through.

Mornisa endured the pain in her mind and intercepted a message sent to the outside world. It was a distress signal sent to the Beyond Grade A Association.

Seeing this, though wounded, she still sneered. "That egotistical Mechanic Emperor finally learned to ask people for help? Where did your pride go?"

Manison glanced at her and did not respond.

He knew that after this distress signal was sent, Black Star would most likely be the one to come. God only knew how he would ridicule him.

If possible, he did not want to have any connections with Han Xiao, mostly to prevent Han Xiao from seeing his database. After all, [Virtual Purification—Restore] was his nemesis. However, in this situation, it was tough for him to hold on, so he had no choice but to call for help.

One side was resisting and trying to seek help, while the other side was invading and locking down the information. The situation remained in a stalemate for quite some time.

Despite Manison's efforts to continuously mend his firewall, his line of defense kept shrinking in the face of the Beyond Grade A enemies and the main artificial intelligences of the three Universal Civilizations. More and more needles stabbed into his databases one after another, stealing the data he had accumulated over many years.

Virtual Paramount went off cooldown many times, and Manison used it every time on Mornisa and gave her a heavy beating.

It was not like Mornisa could suggest that Manison target her other teammates, so she had no choice but to endure all of it. Her injuries got worse and worse. If not for her teammates who were helping her, her consciousness would have been very close to being unable to maintain the intrusion.

Suddenly, an invading data stream finally penetrated the firewall and infiltrated the secret database. It only lasted for a short instant before being wiped out by Manison.

However, in that short time, this data stream absorbed a ton of nutrients and transmitted part of Manison's secret data back.

A Mechanic sent a message to his teammates. "We got his key technology data!"

"Keep going!" Mornisa's heavily damaged consciousness suddenly became energetic like she was on steroids.

It was like suddenly finding gold after mining for a very long time; all the torture she had gone through felt worth it!

However, Manison, who had remained calm, found a gap in the barrier and finally sent out a distress signal.

"Sh*t, he managed to send out a signal!"

Mornisa's joy only lasted for a few seconds before her heart sank.

Her tone was arrogant, but she was actually quite worried inside. If the association's Mechanics came to help, this mission would definitely fail.

That was especially so if the unfathomable Black Star came. That was a man who kicked her teacher who she once admired more than anything down from the top. Just thinking about it made her feel fearful.

If Black Star came, Mornisa would flee instantly… She dared to backstab Manison, who was no longer at his peak, but she did not dare touch Black Star, who was right at his peak.

"Don't panic, we still have some time," a teammate said with a deep voice.

Mornisa focused her mind, clenched her teeth, and tried her best to steal as much information as possible before reinforcements arrived. At the same time, she removed a large portion of the three Universal Civilizations' main artificial intelligences' computing power from the message blocking barrier and moved them to focus on invading.

Since Manison's distress signal was out, there was no point spending so much effort to block his communications. The others also all focused on invading.

With no time to spare, their invading strength increased again. Data stream needles stabbed into one key database after another. Manison could only frown and resist with all he had.

After some time, a direct Mechanic who was calculating the time suddenly said, "That's about time. If we remain here, reinforcements are going to arrive."

"Retreat!"

Mornisa clenched her teeth. They were far from turning Manison's database upside down, but she did not dare continue.

Glancing at Manison's hole-filled firewall, they retrieved their computing power and retreated the way they came.

At this time, Manison's Virtual Paramount went off cooldown again. Before the invaders left, he dealt Mornisa another heavy blow.

Mornisa shivered. Her Virtual Soul became even more faint as she retreated and disappeared with her last shred of consciousness.

In the Virtual Mind Wave Enhancer somewhere in the Primeval Star River, their consciousnesses returned to their bodies.

"Go, quickly…"

Mornisa only had time to say two words before her avatar collapsed onto the floor and her Lord's Descent got deactivated.

She had been Manison's focus and was already at her limits at this point. As soon as the mission was over, her consciousness returned to her main body right away, and she almost fainted… It would take her at least a year to recover from the injuries she had suffered.

Judith glanced at her avatar on the floor, shook his head, and said, "Leave her alone and retreat with the data we stole. The Mechanic Emperor might come any time."

The others nodded and activated the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device right away.

The two rings around the Virtual Mind Wave Enhancer started spinning and accelerating, and their afterimages formed a sphere.

The next moment, with a flash of blinding light, the entire Virtual Mind Wave Enhancer left through teleportation while the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device self-destructed and shattered into ash.

…

Inside the Virtual Domain, Manison looked at the mess the enemies made in his territory and slowly said, "Count the losses and give me a report."

"…Understood."

The main artificial intelligence responded and started checking the status of the various databases.

Very soon, a list was given to Manison.

He looked at the enormous losses on the list, closed his eyes with resignation, and sighed. His expression looked like he was laughing at himself.

Karma finally came…

About eighty percent of the information of the various large organizations he stored in his databases was stolen. He had obtained this information through monitoring these organizations for many years. Quite a big portion of the information was secret, especially the information of the few Super Star Cluster civilizations of the Primeval Star River.

A ton of the blueprints he accumulated through research over all these years were also stolen. The only good news was that core technology such as the Felon and the Indestructible Mechanic Empire were all memorized in his mind and had never existed in the database, or his loss would have been even bigger.

Buzz!

At this time, a data stream appeared out of nowhere and turned into a man. He looked at the wreckages, tutted and said, "Yo, what a refreshing scene. The Mechanic Emperor, who once invaded the databases of people everywhere, got invaded today. How the tables turn."

Manison looked up, and who else could it be but Black Star?

He was not in the mood to respond to Han Xiao's teasing and said, "You're late."

"I'm not telepathic. I came fast enough. You should say the enemies fled in time."

Han Xiao landed before Manison, looked around, rubbed his chin, and said curiously, "How many of them came to be able to do this to you?"

"Several direct Mechanics and the main artificial intelligences of the three Universal Civilizations." Manison gave a simple description.

"Wow, they really think of you quite highly."

Han Xiao raised his brows.

Even he was not confident he could deal with this if he was in the same position as Manison. After all, his Indestructible Body was not very useful in the Virtual Technology field. It was no surprise Manison lost so much.

Manison frowned and said, "I would've crushed them if this was in the real world."

Although he was strong in battles in the Virtual Domain, it was nothing compared to his full combat capability. After all, Virtual Technology was an independent ability, and mechanical armies were useless in the Virtual Domain. With the inventory he had, he would have completely trashed these invaders in a few minutes in the real world.

In the real world, he and Black Star could fight ten enemies at once, but no one possessed this amount of overwhelming strength in the Virtual Domain.

Han Xiao shook his head and asked, "What have you decided to do next? Eat this up or retaliate?"

Manison glanced at him and said, "Depends on you."

"Depends me on?" Han Xiao was stunned.

"Aren't you the Beyond Grade A Association president? I'm a member of the association too, so you'll make the call."

"… Who are you? Release the real Manison!"

Han Xiao was taken aback.

What the hell? You made such a big loss, but not only are you not suggesting fighting back, but you're even respecting my opinion as the president? This isn't like you, Old Manison!

It's over, either this b*stard's soul got swapped, or his heart was too heavily damaged, so his personality became twisted!

Looking at Han Xiao's expression that was filled with disbelief, Manison said impatiently, "What look is that? What's so hard to believe? Anyway, this matter will be dealt with depending on your suggestion."

Of course, Manison was not happy about his database being invaded, but he was not so enraged that he had to take revenge.

One reason was that the loss was not unrecoverable. His core technology was all stored in his mind and was not leaked. Another reason was that it was now a sensitive time. With concern for the big picture, he did not want to disrupt the tempo of the fight between the association and the three Universal Civilizations.

Although he had made a loss this time, the three Universal Civilizations had worked together on this mission against him. They committed so much effort and so many resources to it that Manison had to admit his defeat. Plus, after his position in the Machinery Faith was snatched by Black Star, he gradually had lower and lower requirements for his reputation. He felt he had become calmer inside, no longer concerned about the title of the strongest Mechanic in the Galaxy. It had not belonged to him for a very long time anyway.

Manison sighed in his mind. Maybe because I'm really getting old, my temper keeps getting smaller…

"Your personality has really changed…" Han Xiao said before turning serious. "Don't worry, this is a matter of the three Universal Civilizations robbing an association member's private assets. They won't get away with it easily."

"What are you going to do?"

"Hmm, condemn them first and see how they respond."

"They'll just say I stole the Federation of Light's secrets before and claim this is just punishing me for it."

Manison shook his head.

"Oh, this is indeed a good reason. They have the moral high ground, after all. If that's the case, the question will be thrown back to the association… Doing this to you at this time, the three Universal Civilizations are testing us."

Han Xiao pondered and said, "The three Universal Civilizations' so-called 'punishment' is simply cover. They're testing to see if the association will retaliate for you and see how confident we are. If we only condemn them and don't act, it'll look like we don't have any confidence. If we retaliate, the extent of it will reflect how confident we are.

"This was also to continue damaging the association. They have the moral high ground, so if the association retaliates for you, we'll look tyrannical, and they'll be closer to 'justice'. If the association doesn't do anything, the association members would be worried and unhappy, which is not good for unity."

Hearing this, Manison nodded in agreement.

The three Universal Civilizations had made a move on a core member of the association at such a sensitive time; their intentions were clear, but the association had to deal with it.

However, at this time, Han Xiao suddenly said, "However… we have not considered a colossal change that might occur. If this change occurs, the three Universal Civilizations will not react as I just said."

"What change?" Manison frowned.

Han Xiao looked at him and calmly said, "Let me ask you a question, and you must tell me the truth… The data you lost this time, did it include the Virtual Mutiny Virus you secretly faked?"

Absolutely not mentally prepared, Manison froze.

Then, his expression suddenly changed drastically, and he stared at Han Xiao in confusion.

When the f*ck did you find out my secret‽

Chapter 1298: Argument

"What are you talking about‽"

Manison glared at Han Xiao. Having his biggest secret exposed, a storm was happening in his heart.

He had never told anyone he secretly studied the Virtual Mutiny Virus, so how did Black Star know?

Prophecy? Doesn't make sense, my base is covered in Information Form disruption devices, so others can't even find where my main body is, let alone that I've been studying this technology.

Is he faking it‽

"Don't lie. Since I've pointed this out, of course, I've obtained solid information," Han Xiao added. "As the president, I have to know my key members well. What you thought is a secret is no secret to me. Plus, I also know your research has already shown results… This is very important, so tell the truth."

Manison looked at Han Xiao's calm expression and felt a chill in his heart. Suddenly, panic appeared in his mind for the first time in an extremely long time. He felt as if all his secrets were transparent to Han Xiao.

No matter how dangerous the situation he was in earlier when being invaded, his emotions remained completely unaffected. Now, just speaking with Han Xiao, his calm mood was broken instantly, and his mind was shaken.

This *sshole Black Star… is really my fated nemesis.

Manison clenched his teeth in his mind.

He was in a dilemma. He really wanted to insist on hiding it, but he decided to tell the truth in the end.

"Since you knew, why didn't you stop my research?"

Han Xiao smiled in his head. It's not like I can control what you research about… Plus, what I have is better.

The Virtual Mutiny Virus Manison made was only a semi-finished product. As for him, when he completed the [Intelligent Plague] mission with an S Mission Rating back then, he obtained the original [Domino Virus]. Though incomplete, it was not something a mere forgery Manison created could compare to.

However, there was no need to tell Old Manison this. Han Xiao coughed and said, "Only because there was no need to."

Hearing this, Manison started making guesses and narrowed his eyes.

"Humph, I got it. You actually wanted this insurance too, but because you wanted to be elected president, you deliberately watched me do the dirty work. You don't oppose us having this dangerous technology, but it won't affect you this way."

"… Whatever you think."

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. To be frank, he liked talking to people who loved making speculations. He did not even have to come up with excuses, and the other person would do it for him. It was really quite convenient.

"Humph, we're the same, after all." Manison snorted.

Han Xiao thought he might as well follow Manison's speculation, so he said seriously, "But I still don't agree with the path you wanted us to take. That hasn't changed."

Manison subconsciously wanted to argue, but as he thought of the Sanctum Revival method Han Xiao revealed that was indeed much more effective than what he planned to do, he could only shut up.

Seeing this, Han Xiao paused and continued, "The Virtual Mutiny Virus is a weapon of mass destruction to the galactic society. It's more than powerful enough to overthrow all order and turn the entire explored universe into chaos. Back when I personally shattered the virus core, in the eyes of the public, this dangerous technology disappeared forever, so they stopped worrying. However, if the three Universal Civilizations find out this technology surfaced again, things will be different."

"I think the three Universal Civilizations will be more wary." Manison did not seem concerned.

"You still want to be so stubborn and take one path to the end. It'll soon be too hard to turn back…" Han Xiao sighed.

Though the association was confronting the three Universal Civilizations, the two sides were only intimidating each other, which formed a balance. However, if the Virtual Mutiny Virus appeared again, it would be seen as holding the entire galactic society hostage. Even if the association had no intention to use the virus, the nature of this conflict would change completely.

After all, the Virtual Mutiny Virus was too powerful. It could shatter the order of the galactic society and turn into a universal level disaster. When this technology was controlled by an individual and turned into a modifiable virus weapon, its threat would multiply tremendously once again. The individual could totally invent countless generations of the virus and release them all at once, crushing the galactic society's average artificial intelligence technology.

Without even having to think about it, there was absolutely no way the three Universal Civilizations would allow anyone other than themselves to have a hold of such a deadly weapon. It would be the equivalent of giving someone else the power to control the life and death of the galactic society.

Furthermore, Han Xiao would be affected too. The outside world all thought that he had destroyed the virus, so if Manison was discovered to possess it, even if Han Xiao was not related, conspiracies would definitely receive a lot of recognition. The outside world would think Han Xiao only put on a show back when he destroyed the virus core, while he actually formed a partnership with Manison behind the curtains.

This way, his image would shift to the complete opposite side and he would really become the common enemy of the universe. The association would be dragged down along with him too… Fighting the domineering three Universal Civilizations as the oppressed side would be a justifiable battle for their rights and would receive a lot of support. However, if the association forced the three Universal Civilizations to obey through holding the entire galactic society hostage, the entire situation's nature would change, and the number of people supporting the association would plummet.

"There's never been a way to turn back to begin with," Manison said slowly. "You've always talked about intimidation and balance. When will all that end? If we don't obliterate the three Universal Civilizations' ambitions completely, they'll never give up controlling the scale of individual greatness. A balance without strategic deterrence isn't sustainable. Isn't it good to let the three Universal Civilizations know we are capable of rapidly destroying the entire galactic society?"

Han Xiao rubbed his temple and said, "Sure, the galactic society is very important, but when their rule is strongly threatened, the three Universal Civilizations will be willing to pay any price to eliminate their enemies. Although it's not easy to form a galactic society, at least it can be rebuilt. But if they lose their ruling position, the three Universal Civilizations would rather wipe out everything and start anew. The three Universal Civilizations are acting cautious and fearful now, but once something crosses the line, they'll have the decisiveness to destroy everything and be reborn. They'll never be threatened. This is not something we want to see happen."

Having spent so many years in Galaxy, he had seen things clearly. The production power of the galactic era was astonishing. When the production chains of the society no longer needed people to participate, to some advanced civilizations, population was only a renewable resource that was not even that valuable. They granted their people the rights they enjoyed only because of the functions they provided, not the people themselves.

Most of the time, the more advanced and stronger a civilization was, the less it had to care about the wishes of its people because there was nothing the people could do anymore. The three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster civilizations had already reached this level, only they did not do it. One reason was their traditions and regulations, and another was so that the society would remain in a virtuous cycle. This was not their weakness.

Therefore, Han Xiao had never doubted that the three Universal Civilizations would flip the table if pushed too hard. To them, people dying was no big deal. They only were not willing to flip the table, not that they could not.

"Hehe, if it were in the past, maybe you're right. But now you've brought the Sanctum Revival to the association, along with the intimidation of the Virtual Mutiny Virus, I don't think the three Universal Civilizations will still be as daring… Anyway, I hid this technology to back the association up. You're the president now, so deal with it," Manison said unhappily. "The fundamentals of this technology are in my brain, so these people can't steal it. But they stole some related lab records and logs. Although there is no clear description of the technology in them, whether they can link the records to the Virtual Mutiny Virus or not, I don't know."

"…Tell me the truth, did you do it on purpose?"

"It's already happened. On purpose or not, does it matter?" Manison's tone was calm. "I hid this trump card mainly to prepare for the worst. Since the association wants balance, them finding out about us having this trump card is much better than finding out when we use it. At least it won't be the worst situation."

"… Really good job, and I thought you'd really respect the path I want to take as the president."

Han Xiao gave him a meaningful look, turned around, and left right away.

Manison watched Han Xiao disappear in his sights. His lips seemed to have moved faintly, but he then went back to focus on repairing his firewall.

…

As his consciousness returned to his office in Black Star Palace, Han Xiao opened his eyes.

"Mechanic Emperor… what an ass."

Regardless of whether the three Universal Civilizations stole it or Manison deliberately leaked it, there was quite a high chance the existence of the Virtual Mutiny Virus was going to be discovered by the three Universal Civilizations. This meant that the association had no choice but to deal with it.

Although the second set of Sanctum keys were collected now and he did have plans for an all-out war, he wanted it to come as late as possible. He thought the balance could last for a long time, but this sudden incident probably sped up its arrival tremendously.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

One way or another, it had already happened, and he had to prepare for it.

…

In the Joint Conference Room of the three Universal Civilizations…

"Oh? Mornisa did it, nice."

Seeing the report, Louis nodded with satisfaction.

"Nothing to be happy about. If all of our main artificial intelligences couldn't deal with just one Mechanic Emperor, that would be strange," the pope said calmly.

"You're right." Louis looked at the remote projections of the Beyond Grade A Mechanics in front of him and wondered, "Where's Mornisa? Why isn't she here?"

"She was heavily wounded by the Mechanic Emperor and is resting now. She doesn't have the energy to deal with other things," 'Defender' Romo said with a deep voice.

"Hmm, send her my regards then." Louis waved. "What did you guys get this time?"

"All data has been sent to the Science Institute. They're reorganizing and stitching the information. The results should come in very soon," Romo replied.

The data fragments they stole from Manison's database were not in order. It was a violent invasion, after all. Quite a large portion of the data was incomplete and had to be put together like puzzles. Only then would they know what data they had acquired.

Louis nodded. As he was just about to speak, an emergency report popped up on the virtual screen on his table. It was from the Science Institute.

"So soon?"

Louis raised his brows and looked at the report. Suddenly, his expression changed drastically.

The report consisted of the incomplete experiment records of Manison's research and developments of the Virtual Mutiny Virus. The Science Institute was still adding in more information as quickly as possible. However, just from the test results of these records, one could see that Manison had already achieved some results.

Marbruce and the pope saw his expression and turned to him.

"What is it?"

"… Take a look yourselves." Veins appeared on Louis's forehead as he sent the report to the two of them.

The two of them looked at it. Their expressions suddenly changed too, and rage appeared on their faces.

Romo and the other direct Beyond Grade As were curious.

What information did the Science Institute piece together from the data they collected that was able to make all three leaders so furious?

This time, Louis closed his eyes, calmed his mind, and looked at the curious Mechanics. He waved and turned off the remote projections. Only the three leaders were left in the room.

Seeing that the outsiders had left, Marbruce coldly said, "Mechanic Emperor never gave up and is still studying the Virtual Mutiny Virus, achieving some results even… I wonder if Black Star shattered the virus core back then just to put on a show for us."

"If not because we hacked into the Mechanic Emperor's database this time, god knows when we would've found out about this." The pope had barely suppressed his rage.

Louis looked at the two of them and said slowly, "The nature of the matter has changed. We have to prepare for the worst. Get ready for war."

Chapter 1299: Arriving Storm

"… These are the new members who'll join the association today. We'll be comrades on the same side from now on."

At the Beyond Grade A Association headquarters, Han Xiao introduced these newcomers to everyone present with a smile. They were Joey's group and the new batch of Holy Accord members.

After Manison got hacked by the three Universal Civilizations, he quickly arranged the time for them to join the army, and it was that day.

Hearing Han Xiao's introduction, the various Beyond Grade As present sized these newcomers up and looked surprised.

Although they already knew the Sanctum Revival's existence, they were still astonished when they saw a new batch of revivors.

Plus, not only were there revivors who were joining the association this time, but Black Star even attracted a few others who were avoiding the world previously to make the association stronger. From the way they looked at it, this was undoubtedly Black Star's measure against the three Universal Civilizations' plans, and they were excited by it.

At the same time, this proved that Black Star could use the Sanctum Revival more than once, which was what the majority of people present cared about and were pleased by.

"We're all friends now that you've joined the association. Please, sit," Kasuyi said with a smile.

Joey and the others sighed and sat in their seats. Although they had a bit of social anxiety, they still tried to chat with the other Beyond Grade As.

The Holy Accord members exchanged looks and chatted as if this was the first time they had met.

The people chatted with the newcomers for a while. The atmosphere was harmonious like a big family.

Han Xiao waited for a while. Seeing that everyone chatted about enough, he smiled and said, "Alright, now that you guys have gotten to know each other, other than welcoming the newcomers, there's actually another matter that needs to be discussed today."

Hearing this, the room immediately became quiet. Everyone turned around and looked at Han Xiao, waiting for their president to continue.

Seeing this, Han Xiao changed into a serious expression and said slowly, "Not long ago, the three Universal Civilizations worked together to hack into Mechanic Emperor's database and succeeded. The three Universal Civilizations are both testing and provoking us. Therefore, I'd like to hear everyone's suggestions today about how we should respond."

The people subconsciously glanced at Manison and saw that Manison was resting with his eyes closed.

"I know about this. I received the distress signal back then too," Kant said with a deep voice, "Manison is a member of the association, so we should stand up for him."

"That's right. Although Manison is despicable, dishonorable, wretched, petty, old, ugly, and shameless, he's one of us. He was attacked by the three Universal Civilizations for no reason, so the association can't act like it never happened," Sun Hunter said.

"I agree." Secret Master nodded.

Sun Hunter turned and glanced at him. "Which part?"

"… All parts." Secret Master's eyes twitched and felt a bit of his luck had disappeared.

Manison snorted, opened his eyes, and said, "Focus on the matter. Don't insult others."

"Come on, is telling the truth illegal?" Sun Hunter said with a surprised tone.

Manison took a deep breath and calmed his emotions down.

Calm down, calm down, no point getting angry…

Han Xiao gave Sun Hunter a look of approval and asked the others for suggestions.

More than ninety percent of the people agreed to stand up for Manison. It was not because they were good friends with old Manison, but it was not a personal matter. They hoped to receive the same treatment if something similar were to happen to them in the future.

"… Since the majority agrees, the association will condemn the three Universal Civilizations' actions tomorrow and demand that they give an explanation. At the same time, everyone, dispatch your armed forces. When necessary, we might have to take military action on the three Universal Civilizations."

Hearing this, the people were slightly stunned.

They thought just verbally condemning was about it, or a group of Mechanics causing trouble for the three Universal Civilizations' vassal organizations at most. Why did Black Star sound like he was about to start a war?

However, their surprise only lasted for a few seconds, and they did not oppose it.

With the Sanctum Revival, most people were quite confident. Starting a war was not impossible to do. Plus, most people felt that Black Star was just planning to make it an exercise to intimidate them. After all, the situation was balanced for the time being and did not look like a war was about to break out.

"Hmm. Also, to prevent things like this from happening again, I suggest having everyone's original body gather in the Flickering World and not give the three Universal Civilizations a chance to take us out one by one. Of course, this is not compulsory. If some people don't want to come, they can choose not to, but they'll have to deal with the consequences of that themselves…"

While saying that, Han Xiao glanced at Manison.

Manison closed his eyes again and acted like he did not hear it. He was definitely not going to show his well-hidden original body in front of others.

Most people had no problems with this. Quite a number of them had come to the Flickering World recently to begin with, operating their forces here, so they did not have to travel far. The Beyond Grade As in the other Star Fields also had no problems with staying there temporarily.

They discussed for a while more to confirm the arrangements before going offline as the meeting ended.

Very soon, Han Xiao, Kasuyi, and Ames were the only three left in the venue.

Han Xiao glanced at Ames and said, "Aren't you going offline? I have some private matters that I need to speak with old Kasu."

Ames shook her head, sighed, and said, "Aesop told me to tell you. He saw a confrontation that attracted the attention of the entire universe. The two sides confronting each other were the association and the three Universal Civilizations. The future he saw stopped there. He only knows that the results of it will change the fate of the entire universe. He wants to tell you to deal with it cautiously."

"The old man saw a prophecy again, huh?" Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, nodded, and said, "Got it, wait for me at home. I'll fetch you with the King after the meeting ends."

Ames smiled and went offline.

Now, only Kasuyi and Han Xiao were in the room.

Kasuyi heard the conversation from earlier and softly said, "Black Star, are we going to start a real fight with the three Universal Civilizations?"

"Very likely." Han Xiao casually explained the matter about the Virtual Mutiny Virus.

Kasuyi's expression changed uncontrollably, and he did not know what to say. After quite some time, he sighed and said, "The Mechanic Emperor is still too stubborn, but there's nothing we can do about it, since you aren't telling him that the Sanctum Revival can be used an infinite number of times… Without the Virtual Mutiny Virus, your plan could have been carried out steadily. This added deterrence will only make things worse and change the nature of the entire situation."

"Hehe, even if he knew the truth, he'd most likely think the Sanctum Revival and the Virtual Mutiny Virus are a perfect match." Han Xiao curled his lips. "Never mind him. Anyway, be prepared. Tell your Void Dukes to monitor the three Universal Civilizations' armies in the various big secondary dimensions. If they send troops to fight us, they'll definitely go all out."

"Understood."

Kasuyi nodded and went offline.

…

The confrontation between the Beyond Grade A Association and the three Universal Civilizations already lasted for quite some time, the galactic society already gradually got used to this uptight atmosphere.

However, on this day, the Beyond Grade A Association openly condemned the three Universal Civilizations for hacking the database of its member, Manison, and demanded an explanation. The Federation of Light retaliated and claimed that Manison had stolen their secrets multiple times. This was just a late debt collection and a punishment that should have happened long ago.

The galactic residents were already used to seeing conflicts like this and thought this was another joyous day of the two sides verbally fighting each other. However, what happened next made many people sense it was different this time.

According to the past experiences, the association and the three Universal Civilizations would condemn each other back and forth a few times, and this matter would be over without much happening. Even if there were any punishments, it would at most be like a new law to target the Beyond Grade A association.

However, this time, the galactic residents and the various organizations shockingly realized that the two sides seemed to have decided to do the real deal.

After the announcement was made, the three Universal Civilizations and the Beyond Grade A Association surprisingly both dispatched troops on a large scale. The three Universal Civilizations' fleets rode out from the Central Galaxy and stationed themselves at the various Star Fields, while the Beyond Grade A Association's people mainly gathered in the Flickering World.

A storm was brewing.

Even ordinary people could see that something was wrong. Although the three Universal Civilizations did not continue to make announcements after making the initial response, they were clearing sending the message that they would start a war any time.

Since the two sides confronted each other, most galactic residents were only watching a show, but now they were all nervous.

Most messages online of hoping the three Universal Civilizations could cleanse the Beyond Grade As were just people venting their emotions. When it seemed like it was really going to happen, many people panicked a little and were worried such a large-scale battle might affect them too.

Suddenly, the atmosphere of the entire galactic society became tense. Countless pairs of eyes paid close attention to the two sides.

…

"Weird, why are the three Universal Civilizations so daring all of a sudden?"

Inside the conference room of the Super Star Cluster Alliance, the various leaders were all surprised.

According to their analysis, due to all kinds of reasons, the three Universal Civilizations would not easily start a war, same for the association. Why did both of them suddenly become so headstrong?

If they assumed Manison was the fuse, they did not think it was that big of a deal. All that happened was some of the information in his database was stolen. Manison had not been killed or anything. Was there a need to escalate the situation this much?

"Did the three Universal Civilizations change their strategy and want to eliminate the problems no matter the cost?" someone pondered aloud.

"Probably not likely. Don't forget, we're still here. If the three Universal Civilizations and the association both get heavily damaged, won't that be giving us an opportunity to rise?" the Star Arc Civilization's leader said hesitantly.

Their existence was the exact reason a weak balance could be maintained. If not because both sides were worried about the Super Star Cluster Alliance, they might have acted long ago.

"What do we do?"

"Just watch. If they're really going to fight, it's a good thing for us…" the Star Arc Civilization leader said. "But we need to be careful about the three Universal Civilizations dragging us in. It won't be the first time they've done something like that. We'd best station heavy troops at our borders. Don't have to interfere with their war, just protect our territories."

The Super Star Cluster leaders discussed their options quietly. They all sounded excited. Although they had no idea why the three Universal Civilizations and the association both suddenly became so impulsive, it was not bad news for them.

…

Time passed by quickly in the intense atmosphere. Under the close attention of the galactic society, both sides dispatched their troops more and more frequently without hiding their movements at all. They set up their formations like playing chess but never clashed with each other as if they ignored each other's existence.

However, neither of the two sides made any announcements, which caused all kinds of rumors to spread, leading to panic everywhere.

The population flow of the various Star Fields showed the public's reaction. The galactic residents in the Flickering World left in large numbers, causing the stargates to jam. The number of people going to the Central Galaxy and some border Star Fields to take refuge increased tremendously day by day.

Under the eyes of the entire world, an enormous joint fleet of the three Universal Civilizations advanced into the Primeval Star River and right toward the Mechanical Race's territory.

At the same time, the three Universal Civilizations finally made a new joint announcement.

"Through the Science Institute's analysis of Mechanic Emperor's database, we have acquired solid evidence that proves the Mechanic Emperors has been privately studying the Virtual Mutiny Virus, hoping to replicate this possible source of a universal level disaster. He has already achieved results and could attempt to bring catastrophe to the galaxy.

"On behalf of the galactic society, the Federation of Light, the Crimson Dynasty, and the Arcane Church have made a joint warning to the Mechanic Emperor—give up the Virtual Mutiny Virus technology immediately and destroy all backup data under our supervision. We will protect the safety of the galactic society no matter the cost!"

On the day this announcement was made, the dark clouds of the Intelligent Plague once again shrouded galactic society and the hearts of countless galactic residents. Panic swept one Star System after another at an unbelievable speed.

The Virtual Mutiny Virus is still in this world‽

Someone produced this monstrous virus capable of threatening the entire universe again for his own interests‽

The galactic society exploded!

Along with shock and fear, there was incomparable rage.

The Mechanic Emperor deserves to die!

Chapter 1300: Storm

"Hehe, the three Universal Civilizations have really done it now. Looks like they've made up their minds…"

In the guest meeting room of Black Star Palace, more than a dozen Beyond Grade As gathered and looked at the virtual screen on the wall of the room that was playing the news about the three Universal Civilizations' announcement.

They were all looking worried except for Han Xiao, who was holding his chin and had a poker face.

Bang!

Someone suddenly slammed the table. The others looked over and saw Kant had a gloomy expression, and his fist was planted into the cracked table.

"Manison is forcing us to waste our one chance at the Sanctum Revival!"

The people present all had hostile expressions on their faces.

The two sides' military forces had made frequent movements. These were all core members of the association invited by Han Xiao to gather in Black Star Palace.

At the start, they thought this was another trick played by the three Universal Civilizations, till Han Xiao briefly explained what had happened when Manison was attacked. They were shocked both by the fact that Manison really produced the Virtual Mutiny Virus and Manison leaking the lab records deliberately.

With the Sanctum Revival backing them up, they were not afraid of fighting. However, being willing to fight and being forced to fight were two different things.

Initially, after the three Universal Civilizations invaded Manison's database, the association standing up for him would be normal. However, with the Virtual Mutiny Virus' appearance, the nature of the matter changed. The association became the side in the wrong. Furthermore, Manison most likely did it on purpose to drag them down.

At this time, they were all very unhappy with old Manison. After all, there was only one chance to use the Sanctum Revival, and no one wanted to use it too early.

"Black Star, what are we going to do? The three Universal Civilizations brought this matter up. Will the association still back Manison up?" Kasuyi asked. He did not react much to it as Han Xiao had told him long ago.

Han Xiao rubbed his chin and said with a deep voice, "Based on my speculation, after the three Universal Civilizations found out about the Virtual Mutiny Virus' existence, there were a few possible paths they'd take, and what they're doing now is one of them. After announcing it to the galactic civilization, they sent an army to surround the Mechanical Race's territory, threatening and trying to force Manison to give up the technology.

"If the association backs the Mechanic Emperor up and holds onto the virus technology, the three Universal Civilizations will only have to push the public opinion slightly, and the neutral image and reputation the association has built will collapse instantly. At the same time, an all-out war might erupt, and the three Universal Civilizations are probably ready for it."

"How about we give up Manison?" someone asked. "The situation is different now. I believe most members understand. After all, we really had no idea about the Virtual Mutiny Virus. The Mechanic Emperor did it on his own, so it's not our concern."

Han Xiao shook his head and said, "The three Universal Civilizations have already shifted the public opinion against us. They created a sense of fantasy and fanaticism the Supers have in us. At this point in time, if we back off like this, even if it is sensible and logical, it'll mean we have lowered our heads to the three Universal Civilizations. We'll very likely lose our special guiding position among the Supers, which will be very difficult to regain in the future… To the three Universal Civilizations, eradicating the Supers' admiration and fantasy for the association will be a good result."

"Is the association really going to take the blame for Manison? Why not insist that this is the three Universal Civilizations framing us and is nothing but a lie, or could we say they were the ones who created it first and Manison only stole it?" Sun Hunter widened his eyes.

Han Xiao cut him off and said, "They have a ton of evidence in their hands. It'll be tough to push it back to them, and it might make our situation even worse. Also don't forget, in many people's eyes, the civilizations can touch some things, but civilian organizations can't. Even if we claim the three Universal Civilizations created it first, they don't have to explain much. Plus, they can totally say that if not because the Mechanic Emperor had ulterior motives, why would he have stolen this technology? It's too easy to find such reasons."

Then, he paused before continuing. "The moment the Mechanic Emperor gave them this leverage, we were already in a dilemma. At this point, the matter has exceeded the verbal argument stage, and the public opinion is only an add-on. Either they step back, or we do; there's no way any of us can dodge the core of the issue by playing tricks. It all depends on if we protect Manison or not, or if we give them the technology… I'll say this, we are going to protect Manison, and we are also not going to give up the technology to them. At most, we'll make what we do sound better in words."

They exchanged looks.

"What do we need to do now?"

"I've already spoken to Manison about sending your troops in the Primeval Star River to the Mechanical Race territory to form a line of defense, stopping the three Universal Civilizations' joint fleet. As for yourselves, stay here for now. I'll go to the Primeval Star River with the King. If a fight breaks out, then I'll bring you guys over to help." Han Xiao shook his head.

Hearing this, the others had nothing to say and left the room with a lot of things on their minds. They needed some time to digest the sudden changes.

Han Xiao leaned back in his chair, took out his communicator, and looked at what was going on online.

The terror of the Virtual Mutiny Virus was carved deep in everyone's heart. The entire galactic society was in a panic. Almost all the messages were scolding Manison for how ambitious he was and how what he did threatened the universe once again.

After the virus incident, Manison's reputation had been poor. His goal of developing this technology was clearly to weaponize it. Almost all galactic residents were terrified and furious.

Even Han Xiao was dragged into it. His act of destroying the virus core was doubted by countless people. Many people felt that if Black Star still had the same mindset as before, he should once again destroy or give the virus technology to the three Universal Civilizations. Otherwise, what he did back then might be an act of destroying the technology on the surface to avoid the three Universal Civilizations' attention while working with Manison behind the curtains.

"Tsk…"

Han Xiao curled his lips and did not say anything. He then closed the tabs and called Manison.

Very soon, Manison appeared on the screen.

"Black Star, when will you be coming?" Manison cut to the chase.

"Wait for a while." Han Xiao said with a poker face, "Are you really not going to migrate the Mechanical Race?"

"No, leave them be." Manison was unconcerned.

"… Wait for me to go over then."

Han Xiao did not want to say anything else to Manison. He ended the call, stood up, and left the room.

Over the next few days, the explored universe remained stormy. The three Universal Civilizations' joint fleet advanced toward the Mechanical Race' territory without hiding their movements at all, while the troops the association had in the Primeval Star River also started to gather around the Mechanical Race's territory.

Fleets from Beyond Grade A organizations were stationed at half a day's distance from the Mechanical Race territory around it, forming a spherical defense formation, and blocked all routes toward the Mechanical Race territory, allowing no one to pass. They did not hide their intention. They were clearly blocking the three Universal Civilizations' joint fleet's path.

At the same time, responding to the three Universal Civilizations' announcement, the association also made an announcement to the galactic society.

"The association did not know about the Mechanic Emperor developing the Virtual Mutiny Virus before this and is now investigating it. As everyone knows, solving conflicts between Beyond Grade As and restraining the actions of Beyond Grade As are the purpose of the association's founding. If the Mechanic Emperor is found to possess the Virtual Mutiny Virus technology, the association will certainly take actions and ensure this technology won't damage the order of the galactic society.

"However, the association won't interfere with one's freedom to research and grow, nor does it agree with how all dangerous technology must be controlled by the three Universal Civilizations. If the Mechanic Emperor does indeed possess this dangerous technology, the association will restrain him and tell him to seal this technology up and never use it, ensuring the safety of the galactic society all the same.

"Also, the association strongly opposes the military actions the three Universal Civilizations are currently taking against Manison's people. This is an immoral act. The association hopes the three Universal Civilizations will remove their troops immediately and not escalate the issue. When the association completes the investigation, it will give the galactic society an answer. There's no need for the three Universal Civilizations to interfere."

As soon as this announcement was made, it shocked the galactic society once again.

Many people originally thought the association would back away this time for sure; they did not expect them to be this firm.

Although the Beyond Grade A Association said that they were investigating, their attitude of not backing down was clear. They directly expressed the fact that this was an internal matter, and they would not let the three Universal Civilizations interfere. Plus, their point was sensible…

The three Universal Civilizations can monitor things, so can we.

The galactic residents trusted the three Universal Civilizations more, but since the association claimed to ensure that the galactic society would not be damaged, though many had doubts, as onlookers who knew nothing about the truth, they could not accuse the association of having ulterior motives.

After all, the Beyond Grade A Association was no ordinary civilian organization, it had a certain authority. At the same time, the outside world could not find out if Manison's personal research was done with the association's support. Therefore, at least the reason the association gave made sense… As for whether their monitoring would really work, words could not prove it.

The Super Star Cluster Alliance that was watching earlier jumped out again at the sight of opportunity, supporting the association's decision. They questioned on what grounds could one guarantee that giving the technology to the three Universal Civilizations would be safe and that it was just an excuse to rob the technology from others.

It was not weird for them to do this. The Super Star Cluster Alliance was probably the last group that wanted to see the three Universal Civilizations have the Virtual Mutiny Virus technology. If not because they were not in the position to, they would have suggested to be the third party to 'monitor' this technology.

To countless galactic residents, the situation of the world changed way too rapidly. It felt like only yesterday when everything was peaceful, and suddenly, a war was about to break out.

When the intense atmosphere spread throughout the entire universe, the joint fleet of the three Universal Civilizations finally came into contact with the defense circle the Beyond Grade A Association had built up around the Mechanical Race territory.

Inside the bright night sky, the enormous joint fleet slowly advanced. The exterior defense circle outside the Mechanical Race's territory was already in sight.

The defense circle was formed by fleets, temporary fortresses, and portable satellite bases. From one look, it appeared to extend infinitely. Psionic protective shields were set up in a formation and formed an enormous protective shield, extending all the way out like a wall made of energy, dividing the two areas.

Inside the main fleet's command room, Fleet Commander Simon Tagman stood in front of the porthole and stared closely at the defense circle that was getting closer.

He was a high-level military commander of the Federation of Light who was appointed as the main commander of this joint fleet.

The aide-de-camp looked at the radar and whispered, "Commander Simon, we've already reached their defense circle. They're blocking the way. Should we stop?"

Without even turning around, Simon calmly said, "What's the order?"

"Surround the Mechanical Race's territory."

"Is this the Mechanical Race's territory?" Simon asked.

"N-no…"

"Then why stop?"

"Understood!" The aide-de-camp took a deep breath and ordered in the communication channel with a deep voice, "All ships, continue to advance and get ready for battle. If anyone tries to stop us, fire at will!"

The order was quickly passed down. Cannon barrels extended from the battleships of the joint fleet and aimed forward, ready to fire any time.

The front of the joint fleet gradually entered the attack range of the defense circle. The distance between the two sides kept reducing, and the atmosphere kept becoming more and more intense. Almost every crew member held their breath.

Ding!

At this time, a remote projection suddenly appeared in the command room. It was a military officer of the combat command department.

"Order from above, all fleets stop advancing immediately."

"Stop." Simon raised his hand.

The aide-de-camp immediately passed the order down.

Very soon, the joint fleet slowly stopped only a short distance from the defense circle. The battleships at the front could almost see the crews of the other side through the portholes.

Seeing this, the atmosphere in the command room relaxed a little. Everyone was relieved.

Seemingly not surprised at all, Simon looked at the remote projection of the military officer and asked, "Any other orders from above?"

"… Spread out, surround them, and standby. Wait for the results of the negotiation."

In the Mechanical Race's territory, Manison's Lord's Avatar looked at the remote surveillance screen and smiled.

"You guessed right. The three Universal Civilizations are not willing to start a war right away."

Han Xiao sat opposite him with his eyes narrowed and casually replied, "The three Universal Civilizations definitely did not send a fleet so openly here to start a fight. If they really wanted to attack the Mechanical Race territory, they would have used the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device long ago. Plus, your original isn't here, so attacking the Mechanical Race won't do much. This should be their last test."

This had already become the center of the storm, and the attention of the entire universe was focusing on the situation here. He had arrived not long ago. He and Manison were the only Beyond Grade As there at the moment.

"Although they've made up their minds, they're sadly not decisive enough." Manison shook his head.

Han Xiao glanced at him and said, "Things have become like this because of you. Don't you have anything to say?"

"… What are you trying to say? You want to get off the boat now?" Manison paused.

"Nothing, but now that I'm backing you up, at least act like the one who's being helped."

"Humph, what a strange thing to say. Do you like to see me put down my pride that much?" Manison was not in a bad mood now, so he did not mind it. "Alright, help me settle this matter, please."

Han Xiao's eyes moved subtly and glanced at the interface. He then grinned faintly for a short instant.

He slowly stood up.

"Let's go. It's time for me to meet my old boss."

Chapter 1301: Negotiation

At the Mechanical Race territory's defense circle, the three Universal Civilizations' joint fleet and the Beyond Grade A Association had been standing opposite each other for quite some time, and the atmosphere was very intense.

At the edge of their fleets, spaceships with symbols of differing galactic media groups were broadcasting the situation live. None of the sides banished the battlefield reporters.

As this place might become a battlefield, these media groups only sent unmanned spaceships to carry out remote broadcasting. This place had become the eye of the storm, and the entire universe's attention was focused there, so the audience count had already broken records.

"The three Universal Civilizations' fleet has been stopped. The two sides have not fired… though the reason is unknown, a battle did not break out. We sincerely hope things will come to change…"

In the broadcast channel of a galactic media, the host spoke with a serious expression. Countless viewers watched the images nervously and anxiously.

With all the comments online, the majority of people already knew that what was about to happen would be the turning point. If the two sides started a battle, it might lead to an all-out war between the three Universal Civilizations and the Beyond Grade A Association, and countless people were terrified of that.

At this time, two streams of light appeared in the broadcast, dashing quickly from inside the defense circle toward the middle area, showing themselves in front of everyone.

"The center of all this, the Mechanic Emperor has finally appeared. The person beside him is the Beyond Grade A Association's president, Black Star. Did he come personally to stop the three Universal Civilizations?"

Hearing the host's introduction, the eyes of the countless galactic residents focused on the two of them. Many felt complicated toward these two people who caused the situation of the entire universe to become like this.

Han Xiao stepped out of the association fleet's formation, came to between the two armies, and hovered in the center, instantly becoming the focus of everyone's attention. The battleships of both sides all focused their cameras on him and displayed his enlarged image on their screens.

He glanced at the enormous fleet of the three Universal Civilizations, opened the public channel, and said to everyone,

"You're neither fighting nor retreating. Bring out someone who's in charge. I believe no one wanted to see things escalate to this point. If we can come up with a plan we can all accept, no one will want to solve problems with violence."

As he said that, the battlefield became silent for some time. Then, three beams shot out from the main ship, forming the remote projections of the three Universal Civilizations in front of Han Xiao, entering the public channel at the same time.

As soon as the communication was picked up, Louis cut to the chase and said with a deep voice, "Black Star, are you going to hold on to the Virtual Mutiny Virus that might endanger the entire explored universe and protect the malicious Mechanic Emperor?"

Han Xiao shook his head. "The Virtual Mutiny Virus was destroyed long ago. The Mechanic Emperor only studied it and achieved some results. It's his innovation to begin with. Although this technology is dangerous, we have no obligation to submit it to the three Universal Civilizations, nor did it ever endanger the galactic society. How is it malicious? On the other hand, attempting to threaten the Mechanic Emperor to give up his technology by sending an army to surround the Mechanical Race territory isn't all that honorable."

"Judging from past experiences, the Mechanic Emperor's motive to study this technology is suspicious. Out of safety reasons, we need to obtain this technology, as well as control the Mechanic Emperor himself. This is all to protect the galactic society. That's where the duty of the three Universal Civilizations lies," Marbruce said with a serious expression.

With the same calm expression, Han Xiao said, "Back during the Intelligent Plague, multiple Beyond Grade A Mechanics worked together to defuse the disaster, which proved that the association is also protecting the safety of the universe. We will ensure that this technology won't endanger the galactic society all the same. This is the internal matter for the association to handle; we won't accept the three Universal Civilizations' interference."

The church's pope said seriously, "The Beyond Grade A Development Union is only a civilian organization. Its promise doesn't mean anything. The three Universal Civilizations have the authority to carry out needed measures and monitor anything that might endanger the galactic society. This is within the boundaries of the law. The Mechanic Emperor must submit the Virtual Mutiny Virus!"

"Impossible." Han Xiao rejected it instantly. "The association has already stated its stance in the announcement. Its members have the freedom to research what they want, and we won't accept forceful measures. The association will restrain the application range of the technology. We hope the three Universal Civilizations will retreat immediately!"

Louis paused and said with a louder and more serious voice, "We will pull our army back as soon as the Mechanic Emperor submits the technology. Before that, we won't terminate this operation for any reason. You have ten days. We hope the association will think carefully in this time and not make the wrong decision."

"There's no need to talk further then?"

"You have ten days."

Han Xiao nodded and said with a serious voice, "Since that's the case, I'll stay here from now on, and if you want to force the association to submit the technology, you'll have to get past me!"

Then, he crossed his legs and hovered in the center between the two armies. Although he was alone, it was like he had drawn an invisible line that extended out infinitely.

The three Universal Civilizations leaders gave him a deep look before their remote projections disappeared.

The two sides had spoken in the public channel, so everyone present had heard it, including the media.

The expressions of countless galactic residents changed.

"Does this mean the negotiation failed?"

"Neither side is willing to take a step back. Looks like they're really going to fight!"

"There's still ten days. I wonder if I have enough time to take refuge."

The galactic society was in fear.

Han Xiao looked around at the three Universal Civilizations' fleet. Seeing that they were still on standby, he shook his head.

As the president, he represented the association. There was no way he was going to step back and submit the technology. It was the same for the three Universal Civilizations; they were not going to retreat before achieving their goal.

"Ten days…" Han Xiao mumbled.

This was the time the three Universal Civilizations had given him. In ten days, if they still could not come to an agreement, a fight might really break out. The three Universal Civilizations probably made up their minds this time and were willing to accept the consequences of starting a war.

He glanced at the interface. In his mission list, a new mission was pinned to the top. It was the mission he had triggered from Manison. The requirement was to defuse the danger the Mechanical Race was in by any means necessary. As long as he could make the three Universal Civilizations retreat, the mission would be considered complete.

Maybe because Manison personally 'asked him to help', other than the high experience, the reward also included one chance to draw an ability from Manison.

Of course, Han Xiao was not going to let this opportunity slip.

He casually opened the forums. The stand he made earlier was also recorded by the players in the fleet.

Unlike the galactic residents who were panicking, the players were all looking forward to it. They were all excited about the current situation.

Beep beep…

This time, his communicator suddenly rang. It was surprisingly a call from Marbruce.

Han Xiao was not surprised at all. The open negotiation was more to express their stand to the outside world. The real negotiation still had to be carried out privately.

Picking up the communication, the three Universal Civilizations' leaders appeared on the screen inside the mechanical suit.

"Black Star, do you really want to start a war?" Marbruce questioned.

"I should be asking you guys that."

"Don't be overconfident just because you have the Sanctum Revival. You're leading the Beyond Grade As to their deaths," Louis said coldly.

"Isn't that exactly what you guys want to see? If not because you're worried about the damages a war might cause, why would you contact me privately now?"

"Hehe, we have already come to some results in our research. We know that using the Sanctum Revival will consume some special resources, and it's not free; you can't bluff us. Plus, these revivors have already used their one chance of revival. If a fight really breaks out, you guys will incur damages too. No one wants that," the pope said.

"What great ideas do you have then?" Han Xiao curled his lips.

"We want the Virtual Mutiny Virus and the related information of the Sanctum Revival. In exchange, not only will we pull away our army, but we'll also void the new law against the association and support your developments. We can even provide you with more than enough Universal Treasures and blueprints, and we can promise that no one in the Black Star Army will be on the cleanse list in the future. These deals will be done privately and not shared with the public. We can say we pulled out our army because we were intimidated by your strength, so your reputation will become even higher…"

"You're daydreaming, good-freaking-bye."

Before they could respond, Han Xiao hung up the communication right away.

This was the first time he had hung up on the call from the three Universal Civilizations' leaders. He would have never done it if it were in the past before the association and the three Universal Civilizations became complete oppositions. He felt great doing it.

…

"… Hmm, okay, understood."

After hearing the orders from above, Fleet Commander Simon put down the communicator, returned to the command table, and calmly ordered, "Pass down my orders. Engineering team, start to assemble the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device. Start preheating in twelve hours and connect with the other side."

"We're getting reinforcements?" the chief staff sergeant on the side asked.

"Hmm."

Simon turned around and looked outside the porthole at Han Xiao, who was sitting alone in the cosmic space. He said with a meaningful one, "Orders from above, we're going to receive the direct Beyond Grade As who will be sent here."

"How many?"

Hearing this, Simon looked at him.

"All of them."

…

In Black Star Palace's guest hall, a group of Beyond Grade As gathered and watched the news broadcast of what was happening at the Mechanical Race territory with varied expressions, discussing the matter softly.

"Black Star's stand is too strong. There won't be room for negotiation like this." Milizaus was worried.

While adjusting his gun, Sun Hunter said, "Bullsh*t negotiation, this fight is unavoidable. Black Star isn't just putting on a show by standing there. I'm guessing he's waiting for the three Universal Civilizations to send their direct members to fight him. Be it duels or fighting them all at once, he'll accept it. He's doing this on purpose to intimidate them."

"Can he do it alone?" Kant frowned. "If the three Universal Civilizations go all-out, Dark Lord and Golden Ring will definitely be there. Those who are stationed in the secondary dimension bases will most likely be called back too. No matter how strong Black Star is, he has limits. Plus, even God Chooser might go."

"Black Star should be able to deal with the others, but God Chooser…" Kasuyi hesitated. "If he uses the Arcane Church's National Treasure, Black Star might have problems."

Hila crossed her arms, put one leg on top the other, and said coldly, "You don't have to be concerned about Black Star. His skin is thick enough. Better think of the threat we're facing right now. The three Universal Civilizations' army have already locked down the Flickering World's entrance, the Dawn Star Cluster, so they could attack us any time. There are probably already at least ten thousand Super Long Range Planet Annihilation Weapons aimed at this place now."

"Ten thousand? You're underestimating the three Universal Civilizations way too much." Sun Hunter snorted.

Kasuyi shook his head. "We've done what we needed. We can only wait for the results at the Primeval Star River. The three Universal Civilizations won't fire at the other areas before they do anything to the Mechanical Race's territory at least."

The others sighed. Although they knew this would happen sooner or later, when it really did, they still were not confident about it.

No matter what, their opponents were the rulers of this universe. The fear in their hearts that had lasted for so long in the past could not be cleared this easily.

The situation turned way too quickly. Even many Beyond Grade As could not get used to it. However, the changes of time were always sudden. Rarely did it give people the time to adapt. They could only accept the reality.

Chapter 1302: Challenge

Many military base planets were stationed in the Dawn Star Cluster, filled with countless deep holes that had enormous caliber Super-Long-Range Psionic Planetary Obliteration Cannons that were aimed at the nearby Star Clusters—the Garu Star Cluster, Crown Star Cluster, and the Renault Star Cluster. These were all areas of the second exploration phase and were now prosperous areas with many Beyond Grade A Organizations stationed in them. Of the Planetary Obliteration Cannons, Black Star's territories had the highest number of them aimed at them.

The Dawn Star Cluster was the area the Crimson Dynasty had taken over the earliest. Many of the planets there were military restricted areas. In the past few decades, these planets had all been modified into weapons.

After the first Meeting of the Gods a few decades ago, the Crimson Dynasty had secretly started carrying out this project, planning for the future. What was happening today was exactly what they had been preparing for. If a fight broke out, this Star Cluster could immediately become the bridgehead of the war. At the same time, the regular route between the Flickering World and the explored universe would be sealed up.

Fleets belonging to the three Universal Civilizations stationed in the various places of the Dawn Star Cluster, while the three Universal Civilizations' temporary combat command center also moved from Planet Lighthouse to a military planet at the heart of the Dawn Star Cluster.

"Maintain the highest alert level in the next ten days. Once the joint fleet starts to fight on the Mechanical Race's territory, that'll be our signal to fire at all Beyond Grade A organizations, including the Black Star Army's territories."

Inside the temporary combat command center, Euwan Fabick looked around at the many military officers in the room with eyes as sharp as an eagle.

He was a high-level military officer of the Crimson Dynasty who had taken over the position as the Marshal of the dynasty's exploration army after Tarrokov retired. Due to all the things happening lately, the three Universal Civilizations classified the Flickering World as an independent key war zone, and he had become the commander of this war zone directly, in charge of the military operations of the three Universal Civilizations in the Flickering World.

"Understood," the others replied simultaneously.

Euwan turned to one of the military officers and said, "Due to shortage of manpower, the people above can't send direct Beyond Grade As here to help. How's the setup of the defense measures doing? After the battle starts, the Beyond Grade As will definitely try to assassinate the people in the command center. If we can't stop them from invading the Dawn Star Cluster's core, the situation is going to be very tough."

"The engineering team is setting up the defense measures as quickly as possible. They've also left traps and quick support routes. If the Beyond Grade As go too deep, there's a chance we can surround and eliminate them…"

"Give me a report later." Euwan raised his hand and stopped him. He then asked about the progress of other things.

Whether the three Universal Civilizations would end up fighting the association or not, this was not something he cared about. He only cared about his own duty, making sure the strategy could be carried out if a battle did start.

In some desolate universe belt in the Dawn Star Cluster, many hovering shrouding devices circled around a small planet and orbited in the exterior atmosphere, putting out illusions to shroud what was happening on the surface so that it would not be detected by others.

From the outside, this was just a desolate planet. However, the real look of the planet would only show when entering the atmosphere. This was a mechanical fortress that was armed to the teeth, filled with countless battleships and mechanical armies.

In the past few decades, the Black Star Army was not only operating its territory but also setting up many secret bases in other areas, and this was one of them.

At the top of a building, Aurora stood at the edge of the balcony looking at the enormous white mechanical ring far away. This was a new fixed directional teleportation technology Han Xiao had obtained from Jayz's treasure that could transport troops on a large scale. It was not yet activated.

Behind her was a huge crowd. Everyone's body was giving off a faint light. They were all Hero Spirits who had acquired a physical body.

The eight Hero Spirit Kings stood in one row in front of thousands of Calamity Grade Hero Spirits, followed by countless Grade B Hero Spirits.

As early as when Manison's database was attacked, Han Xiao had urgently recalled Aurora, who was traveling at the time, and given her a secret mission. She was to hide in one secret base and keep using her ability. Other than eating and sleeping, she spent all her time summoning Hero Spirits of the Underworld.

Aurora's life in this period of time was summoning Hero Spirit, resting, and recovering. Then she would continue summoning more Hero Spirits and repeat. By doing that every day to the limits of her stamina, she finally summoned so many Hero Spirits.

The amount of time these Hero Spirits with a physical body could exist relied on the speed their body was losing vitality. Basically, as long as they were not killed or Aurora did not take away their body, they could last for a very long time. That was especially so when they were in the standby mode as they were now. The speed they were losing vitality was negligible. This was how Aurora had accumulated such a huge army.

Aurora turned to look at the Hero Spirits and softly said, "Black Star said that you guys will have to make a big mess in the Dawn Star Cluster before the ten days are up. Destroy as many of the three Universal Civilizations' Planetary Obliteration weapons as possible."

Sorokin snorted. "He really likes to order people around."

After spending more than four decades as a Hero Spirit, he had accepted his fate and gotten used to his identity. However, he had never given up his hobby of making money. In order to satisfy that, he had found a way to change the societal environment of the Underworld.

As Hero Spirits basically had zero physical needs when they were in the spirit form, through observing over a very long time, Sorokin discovered what they all needed. Hence, he created a concept currency system based on 'Promises'. One promise meant one owed another person a favor, while the promises from Hero Spirits of different levels and identity represented different values.

When a Hero Spirit gave promises to one or more other Hero Spirits, it was the equivalent of printing money. Sorokin designed a special credibility system to prevent the Hero Spirits from giving out promises without restraint, which would have led to inflation, at the same time solving a series of problems associated with 'damaged promises'. Plus, the number of promises every Hero Spirit could create in a certain period was limited. Also, this kind of 'promises' currency was allowed to be sold to others, similar to giving others one's 'debts'.

Sorokin worked quite hard to promote this system. He even convinced Aurora and Onicelu to semi-relate the monetization of this currency with the chances of reviving and the duration of being revived. This way, the Underworld Hero Spirits who usually had nothing to do gradually accepted this system.

Having created a market, using the capitalist methods he was most proficient in, Sorokin harvested a ton of promises. Currently, the Hero Spirits of the Underworld owed him 0.37 Promises on average. He became the 'wealthiest' person in the Underworld… Although this did not mean much, seeing his 'wealth' increase was satisfying to him on its own.

This war made Sorokin see an opportunity to largely monopolize the promise currency. After all, if a war broke out, the Underworld Hero Spirits would definitely be revived frequently. Although they were summoned for a war, it was much better than staying in the Underworld and doing nothing.

As for the conflict between the association and the three Universal Civilizations, Sorokin was not interested. His position was no longer the same; it was not his problem to worry about anymore.

Aurora turned back and continued to look in front. Facing away from the many Hero Spirits, her expression became worried.

Both the three Universal Civilizations and the association had set up secret bases like this in the various key Star Fields. Once an all-out war erupted, tons of places would be drawing in blood, and she did not really want to see that.

"If a war really breaks out, I hope I can save more people with the Underworld…"

Back in the Mechanical Race's territory, the media and news groups were still broadcasting the situation. A lot of time had already passed after the failed negotiation. Han Xiao sat in the middle as if he was dividing the fleets of the two sides. None of them moved.

Looking at the broadcast that was like a still image, the countless galactic residents kept feeling more anxious.

More than half a day had already passed, yet neither side had made a move. Were they going to just keep looking at each other for ten days? If that was the case, their stand would not change even after ten days.

While many were feeling pessimistic, a change happened in the three Universal Civilizations' joint fleet. The Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device was suddenly activated. After rapidly spinning for a while, it released a bright light, and a small fleet arrived through teleportation.

"Reinforcements?"

Countless galactic residents were excited. Although they did not know what the three Universal Civilizations were doing, change was good.

Through the broadcast, countless people's eyes followed this small fleet as it passed through the fleet's formation and arrived at the main ship of the joint fleet.

At the same time, inside the command room in the main fleet, all crew members including Simon stood up to welcome the people who were arriving.

As footsteps approached, a group of people with varied appearances walked into the command room.

Seeing this, thrilled chatter sounded among the crews, naming these people like reading off a list.

"The Crimson Dynasty's 'Dark Lord' Clotti, 'Thunder' Guzar, 'Army Leader' Padro, 'Army Flag' Enid…

"The Federation of Light's 'Golden Ring' Oulou, 'Super Mentor' Verena, 'Defender' Romo…

"The Arcane Church's 'God Chooser' Wuornos, 'Mechanical Catastrophe' Francisco, 'Holy Disciple' Mornan… It's them!"

The people who had just arrived were indeed all the direct Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations. There were as many as dozens of them. They had all been urgently summoned.

Simon took a few steps forward, nodded at them, and said, "I won't say much. I believe you've already been given orders and know what to do."

Hearing this, they all turned to look outside the porthole and focused on Han Xiao.

Oulou grinned with a tint of cruelty.

"Don't worry. We're here now. He won't be arrogant for long."

"I'll leave Black Star to you guys." Simon nodded.

The fleet firing was the signal to start an all-out war. Before the ten days period ended, the three Universal Civilizations were not going to do that. However, since Black Star had come out on his own, they could test him. Therefore, the three Universal Civilizations had summoned their direct members and planned to pressure the association.

This time, Verena looked around at everyone and said slowly, "Black Star is very strong and difficult to deal with, but if we fight him together from the start, it won't look good. Only Clotti, Oulou, and Wuornos here are capable of fighting Black Star alone. Which of you will go first?"

Hearing this, everyone focused on the three of them. Most people were looking at Wuornos, who was known as the strongest.

Wuornos' eyes were closed, and he remained silent, not looking interested in this mission.

It was true. If not because the church pope had called him here, he would not have left the Temple of Ten Thousand Gods at all.

Seeing that he did not speak, the others turned to look at Clotti.

"You used to work with Black Star. You should know about his abilities more than us," Verena said.

Clotti frowned. "I don't know more than you do. He…"

This time, Oulou interrupted him.

"I'll deal with him. I've been wanting to fight Black Star for a long time. Maybe I can take him on the spot."

Seeing this, the others nodded and did not fight with him for the spot.

This time, Verena tapped her forehead with her finger. A pure white glow flew out and landed on Oulou.

Suddenly, Oulou felt the energy in his body start to boil. His ability strength kept increasing.

"Hehe, I can deal with Black Star without this enhancement."

Oulou was not very thankful.

"It's for just in case," Verena replied calmly.

She was the principal of the Federation of Light's Super Research Institution. She had a utility Esper Ability that leaned toward supporting others, enhancing the abilities of other Supers. She could also analyze the target's ability's growth path and design comprehensive training plans for them. This was why she was given the nickname of 'Super Mentor'.

A few minutes later, Han Xiao, who was resting in the battlefield, slowly opened his eyes.

In his sights, a familiar person stepped out of the three Universal Civilizations' fleet and hovered not far from him, giving off a powerful presence that was exclusive to peak Beyond Grade As.

"Oulou?" Han Xiao said softly in the public channel.

Oulou narrowed his eyes. "I heard that in order to make the association submit the technology, we'll have to get past you?"

"As long as you can defeat me, I can consider it," Han Xiao answered casually.

Hearing this, Oulou's eyes flickered, and he said with a deep voice, "Then you can start considering that option now!"

After that, his presence rapidly grew. Tons of golden rings appeared behind him, linking to a bright golden world, giving him seemingly infinite energy. It was indeed the 'Golden Treasure Ship' dimension he was known to have.

Seeing this, Han Xiao shook his head and slowly said, "Do you want to consider joining the association to enjoy the Sanctum Revival chance? You won't get killed for nothing that way."

Chapter 1303: Thrashing

While Han Xiao and Oulou were looking at each other, the galactic residents who were watching the broadcast all heard their short conversation in the public channel and were excited.

"Heard that? As long as they can defeat Black Star, he'll consider compromising."

"This is an opportunity! If Black Star keeps his promise, defeating him will avoid the all-out war."

"Come on, the three Universal Civilizations, the peace of the universe relies on you guys!"

"I'm not sure about this. Can the three Universal Civilizations really deal with him? Plus, his attributes on his Wayne Card are way too high now. I don't think Oulou is his match."

"Is this really the time to talk about cards? We can't know who will win till they fight!"

"Speaking of which, if they could decide this with a game of cards, it would be much easier…"

Countless galactic residents were looking forward to it.

It did not matter if Black Star was telling the truth or not, they could only put their hopes on this statement. No one wanted a war; any change was welcome.

At this time, in the eyes of the many galactic residents, Black Star seemed to have become the big villain, and defeating him would protect the peace of the world. Countless people cheered for the three Universal Civilizations in their hearts and hoped to see Black Star defeated the next second.

Inside the three Universal Civilizations' joint fleet's main ship, the other direct Beyond Grade As were all in the command room watching the two of them.

"Do you guys think Oulou can beat Black Star?" someone asked.

"He has less than a fifty-percent chance. If Black Star was that easy to deal with, the people above wouldn't have sent us all." Verena shook her head.

"Then why did we let him go alone? Although ganging up on him isn't good, losing a duel will be embarrassing too, won't it?" Guzar wondered.

"We never expected Oulou to win," Francisco said. "Given Oulou's strength and Verena's enhancement, he's more than capable of matching up to Black Star. This was mainly a test."

Verena nodded and explained, "That's right. It's already been decades since Black Star last fought. With his growth speed, the data from the past is outdated. Oulou will be able to force out Black Star's full strength to collect information for us, which will help in making plans. We have ten days anyway, so there's no need to hurry. Intelligence is crucial in combat."

The others nodded with agreement.

Having made his name in the universe decades prior, Black Star was already recognized as extremely strong among the Beyond Grade As. Not many people dared underestimate him.

Oulou was a peak Beyond Grade A among the top tier in the universe, one of their strongest. Letting him be the first to test Black Star was already an act of taking Black Star seriously enough.

While the many direct Beyond Grade As had their own thoughts, Han Xiao and Oulou who were in the middle of the battlefield suddenly moved like lightning!

Oulou's eyes turned bright as he activated the Golden Treasure Ship dimension. The next moment, countless golden beams of light shot out from the rings behind him like a fountain.

Unaffected, Han Xiao's body shook. Mechanical Force lightning bolts spread instantly, and the mechanical army he hid in his body using [Compressed Orb Innovation—Armed Body] shot out, instantly turning into an enormous mechanical army. The mechanical army set up thick psionic shields in front of Han Xiao, forming a barrier.

Thunderous golden light beams bombarded the psionic barrier. Golden light dust splashed everywhere, and blue-purple electronic bolts danced.

Seeing this, Oulou immediately summoned more golden rings and shot out burning golden light beams nonstop at Han Xiao's mechanical army, as if he had infinite energy.

His Esper Ability allows him to link with the Golden Treasure Ship dimension and use its energy. He's another one with infinite mana who excels in large scale attacks, using his infinite energy to exhaust the enemy time after time. The Golden Treasure Ship is a special secondary dimension. The nature of its energy is very destructive, and it also has other utility functions.

Oulou's information flashed past Han Xiao's mind as he opened up the secondary dimensional army box, and more mechanical troops swarmed out.

The psionic barrier became many times thicker instantly. No matter how powerful Oulou's attacks were, the guarding troops in front of Han Xiao stood firmly. Without the need to dodge any attacks, Han Xiao summoned his Divine Mechanical Throne and sat on it to command his troops.

At the same time, the long-range troops in the mechanical army retaliated. Under the lead of the Apostle Weapons, the melee combat troops also charged toward Oulou from various directions.

The two sides entered an intense battle, dishing out countless attacks at each other without restraint. The battlefield was filled with all kinds of explosions and beams.

The three Universal Civilizations' joint fleet had to move back a certain distance and activate their shields to avoid being accidentally damaged.

Sitting on the Divine Mechanical Throne, Han Xiao looked at Oulou.

Although having infinite mana was one of the special traits of Beyond Grade As, from the way he looked at it, this ability had a weakness that was not really a weakness—no matter how much energy these people had, their power output was still limited. Oulou's Energy Rank determined his damage output.

Oulou's Energy Rank was undoubtedly at the top tier, comparable with Kasuyi. After receiving Verena's enhancements, his Energy Rank even increased by a portion once again. However, compared to Han Xiao's Energy Rank now, it still came up short.

After spending decades keeping a low profile and growing stronger, the bonuses he received from his talents were massive. His combat capability was astonishing and had the upper hand without even having to use any Character Summon Cards. This was the difference in raw strength.

Han Xiao only took out ten or so Apostle Weapons that chased after Oulou, and Oulou was already having quite a difficult time. With Han Xiao's Mechanical Force bonuses, the combat capability of his Apostle Weapons was already steadily at the Beyond Grade A level. They could even go a few rounds with high level Beyond Grade As.

There was no need for flashy plays with such a huge advantage!

One word could describe the situation of this battle.

One-sided!

"This guy is no match for me. His defeat is only a matter of time… Hehe, all these talents I've put in so much effort to obtain would be for nothing if I couldn't easily beat guys like you."

Watching the battle for a while, Han Xiao grinned, shook his head, and looked at the interface casually.

Not long after Oulou challenged him, the Beyond Grade A Challenge Mission appeared once again. Clearly, this challenge received enough attention to trigger a mission.

The mission requirements and the rewards were still the same, requiring him to last for a certain amount of time, and the best reward was still a Character Summon Card and one of Oulou's abilities or talents.

"How I love duels. They're really doing me a big favor."

Han Xiao laughed in his mind.

While he relaxed on his throne and patiently commanded the army, his talents were activated one after another, continuously increasing his status, and the battle became easier and easier.

Meanwhile, Oulou had a more and more difficult time.

In the eyes of others, the mechanical army was like a swarm of bees surrounding Oulou and attacking him. While the golden light beams that Oulou used with no restraint could wipe out piles of the mechanical army from time to time, the empty areas were filled up very quickly by other mechanical soldiers. Plus, the broken machines also very quickly reassembled and returned to the battlefield right after.

Oulou looked like an insect trapped by a spider's web who could only struggle meaninglessly, breaking through the siege time after time, then getting surrounded again every time.

Oulou's expression had already changed. It was grave.

It was not that he had never fought with a peak Beyond Grade A Mechanic, but his attacks would have usually already overwhelmed the opponent's mechanical army. However, Black Star's mechanical army never showed any signs of defeat or flaws, wrapping around him like he could not tear it open no matter what.

These ten or so Apostle Weapons were especially strong, making him not only feel quite tired but also unable to let his guard down at all. Any flaw at this point might be fatal for him.

Protracted battles were originally his expertise, but he was losing this one.

Seeing that the situation was not going well, Oulou could not help but to look at Black Star, who was behind the mechanical army, seemingly having some ideas. Coincidentally, his eyes met with Han Xiao's eyes that had a tint of anticipation.

In just one look, Oulou's heart shivered, and he immediately gave up the thought of charging toward Han Xiao's original body.

… I almost forgot, this guy isn't an ordinary Mechanic. If I really go so close to him, who knows who'll be beating up whom?

Not being able to find a solution, Oulou became more and more irritated. He had no choice but to continue the bombardment. More and more wounds appeared on his body as time passed.

The battle lasted for quite some time, and it remained simple all the time.

Then, suddenly, Oulou's energy exploded. Golden energy formed a tsunami and blew away the mechanical soldiers around, helping him to get out of the encirclement once again.

However, instead of charging toward Han Xiao, he fled in the opposite direction instead and rushed into the formation of the three Universal Civilizations' joint fleet. Using the battleships as cover, he quickly left the battlefield.

Seeing this, Han Xiao made the mechanical troops stop and did not chase into the joint fleet.

Watching Oulou flee into the main ship, only then did Han Xiao speak in the public channel with a slight mocking tone.

"Is that it?"

Right after he said that, Han Xiao waved and retrieved the mechanical soldiers from the field, as if what he had done was nothing worth mentioning.

Then, he sat back on his Divine Mechanical Throne, held his chin with his hand, and looked at the three Universal Civilizations' fleet.

"Next, and please let someone who can warm me up come."

Seeing this, the many galactic residents who originally had high hopes for Oulou felt like their tinder of hope was instantly extinguished.

"H-he lost just like that?"

"Black Star didn't move from the start to the end, right?"

"Was it too easy for him…"

Countless galactic residents felt a sense of suffocation in their chests.

They thought they would see a close battle; never did they expect to see Oulou lose so easily. Oulou was incompetent, and their passion was wasted.

Most people could not understand the details of the battle. They only knew that Black Star sat on his seat without moving an inch, and Oulou was beaten so badly he had to flee. The two of them had no physical contact at all. It was embarrassing beyond words.

They did not know how strong Beyond Grade As were and could only judge from what they saw. Hence, a question popped up in the minds of many galactic residents…

Is Oulou too weak, or is Black Star too strong?

…

In the main ship of the three Universal Civilizations joint fleet, the direct Beyond Grade As who saw this were all silent. Doubt and shock flickered in their eyes.

As Beyond Grade As, they were the only ones who could see the details of this battle that looked like it was completely one-sided, and they were terrified.

The strength of Black Star's Mechanical Force had increased the performance of his mechanical army to a higher level. His Energy Rank crushed Oulou's!

"How can the difference be this huge‽"

Verena widened her eyes with disbelief.

She knew that Oulou's chance of winning was not high, but never did she expect Black Star to win this easily.

Originally, they all hoped Oulou could force Black Star to use all his strength so that they could collect some intelligence. To their absolute surprise, Oulou could not even complete the mission of testing Black Star and was thrashed by Black Star head-on, unable to make Black Star use even one of his trump cards.

Oulou was someone who had top tier strength, not just some nobody. Yet, he lost so pathetically and did not gain an upper hand at any point of the battle at all.

How strong is Black Star now‽

"… He wasn't this strong before," Clotti said with a grave expression. "The only explanation for this is that he became stronger in the past few decades again and kept it a secret."

"This won't be easy," Guzar said with a serious expression. "Even you probably won't be a match for Black Star."

Clotti remained silent and did not refute it. He had no confidence either.

If not because he knew Oulou's personality well, he would have suspected that Oulou was acting.

"We still underestimated this guy. His feathers have matured…"

Clotti exhaled slowly with a heavy heart.

At this time, the hatch opened, and Oulou walked in.

As he was really afraid that Black Star might kill him, he had fled when things were not going well. He was not heavily injured, but he looked confused and could not accept how easily he had lost.

Who am I? Where am I? What am I doing?

The others glanced at him with complicated looks and did not know what to say.

Brother, you asked for this. Thanks for being so brave…

Chapter 1304: Something New

Beep beep…

At this time, Verena's coded communicator rang. The face of the federation's president, Louis, appeared on the screen with an unsatisfied expression.

The leaders of the three Universal Civilizations were watching the broadcast too and were just about as unsatisfied as they could be about the battle earlier.

"What are you doing? I told you guys to go there to help, not to get beat up!"

"Sorry, we wanted to test Black Star's strength, but he's much stronger than the intelligence says…" Verena explained.

"… Don't be so careless again. Oulou losing this easily isn't good for the federation's reputation. I don't want to see it happen again," Louis suppressed the shock and rage in his heart.

"Okay."

Verena hung up the communication and sighed.

They had only lost one battle, and their bosses were already scolding them. Usually, these upper echelons would not be as impatient as this, but they were probably shocked by that battle too and could not keep it in any longer, so they quickly hinted for these direct members to not hold back.

She knew very well why the upper echelons summoned all the direct members here. They thought that with so many of them working together, they could at least suppress Black Star by outnumbering him. At the start, Verena was filled with confidence, but not anymore.

The upper echelons had this idea based on the records of Black Star's strength. However, the last public battle Black Star was in was decades ago when he fought Manison. Back then, the two of them had fought intensely, and Black Star had quite a hard time defeating Mechanic Emperor's Lord's Avatar.

Hence, in the eyes of the three Universal Civilizations, Black Star was a bit stronger than Manison at his peak, but not a lot stronger. Therefore, the three Universal Civilizations felt that as long as they sent all their direct members, it would be more than enough to teach Black Star a lesson. After all, they had three peak Beyond Grade As, and God's Chosen was acknowledged by all as the strongest who could defeat even Mechanic Emperor. There was no reason they would fail.

However, the strength Black Star had just displayed refreshed the three Universal Civilizations' knowledge. Oulou, whose strength was also in the top tier, lost so embarrassingly, and Black Star did not even use his full strength.

Although they knew that Black Star had remained low profile for decades and that their intelligence was already outdated, the difference was way too huge!

"… What now?"

The people suppressed their emotions and exchanged looks.

Being shocked was one thing, but they still had to execute the mission given to them.

Verena pondered for a while and said, "The target's strength is beyond expectations. Dueling will do nothing. Looks like we have no choice but to fight him in groups. Let's all discuss how we should deal with him."

They started discussing it as if they were facing a terrifying enemy.

They were all intimidated by Han Xiao's strength. Even though they were going to fight him together, they did not dare strike carelessly before coming up with a reliable plan.

Wuornos stood at the edge of the crowd and did not participate in the discussion. He looked through the porthole at Han Xiao, who was hovering in the cosmic space. His eyes kept flickering, and he mumbled in his mind, 11,000 Energy Rank minimum, at least one God's Trait Transformation route fully completed… Worthy target to turn.

…

Inside the Mechanical Race's main ship, the many crew members were thrilled by the results of this one-sided battle and started cheering.

In front of the porthole, Manison looked at Han Xiao's back in silence. Although his avatar was expressionless, a tsunami was roaring in his mind.

How is this guy so strong‽

Manison was naturally shocked. His impression of Han Xiao also remained in the last time they fought. It had been a very long time since he saw Black Star fight anyone.

Although he knew he was probably no match for Black Star, he never thought the difference would be so huge. Even if he had to fight Oulou, he could not have done it so easily and casually. It would be an extremely intense and suspenseful battle.

Black Star is becoming more and more unfathomable. How the hell does he become stronger so quickly?

Having realized that Black Star was already so much ahead of him and that he could no longer figure out Han Xiao's limits, Manison could not help but feel complicated and a little sour.

However, after being down for a few seconds, Manison let it go and sighed.

Maybe only someone like this was capable enough of leading the Beyond Grade As into a higher level… Having a leader like this was a blessing for the Beyond Grade As of this era.

The only thing Black Star lacked was probably accumulation…

Manison's eyes spun, and he made up his mind.

He was not a petty man. If Black Star had needs, he did not mind lending his machines to Black Star.

With Black Star's strength and my inventory, he'll probably have no match in the universe.

…

"I knew it. The three Universal Civilizations are overconfident. How can they possibly bring out someone who can fight Black Star?"

The four old hermits including Joey were watching the broadcast and looked relieved.

They had fought Black Star only about a year ago and were the ones who knew Black Star's strength the best in the universe. Back then, their confidence was absolutely crushed and still had yet to recover; they felt shivers every time they saw Black Star.

Earlier, when they saw the three Universal Civilizations only send Oulou to fight Black Star, they were surprised. They thought the three Universal Civilizations had hidden some direct members who were as strong as Black Star, and that made them uneasy.

However, when they saw the one-sided battle, Joey and the others knew that they were overthinking it and worrying for nothing.

"The three Universal Civilizations' intelligence is way too outdated. One peak Beyond Grade A is probably nothing to Black Star." Joey shook his head.

"They'll have to fight as more than one if they want to win, just like what we did…"

Joey felt a little awkward. "Black Star seemed relaxed when fighting the four of us too. God knows what his limit is."

"… Do you guys think he expected this long ago, which is why he kept a low profile for decades?"

"Who knows?"

The few of them softly gossiped.

…

After defeating Oulou, the three Universal Civilizations seemed to be shocked and did not immediately send someone new in right after. Han Xiao sat on his throne and waited patiently.

"Looks like the three Universal Civilizations' expectation of my strength was not high enough."

Seeing the three Universal Civilizations fleet that was not making a move, Han Xiao curled his lips.

In the past few decades, he had kept a low profile and quietly accumulated his strength. Only the Holy Accord, Joey's group, and Kasuyi had seen his strength; the outside world almost knew nothing about it.

The main reason was that there was not really a chance for him to fight publicly. The Beyond Grade A circle was quite small, and there were only a few he could fight.

More than a year ago when he beat up Joey and the others, Han Xiao had gained a rough estimate about his own strength. It would take at least a dozen high-level Beyond Grade As to cause any threat to him.

For now, not only were his growth talents growing steadily, but he had also even obtained [The Ancient Ones] and his first Unique Talent, and he had acquired some new technology from SWY-001. His strength had grown even higher, and the number of Beyond Grade As it would take to cause any threat to him increased once again.

Fighting Oulou was nothing but an appetizer to him. He had gone there with the mindset of starting a 'slaughter', showing the outside world the strength that fitted the identity of the leader of the Beyond Grade As while getting some talents. Stepping up on his personal behalf at such an important occasion, he was certain there would be opportunities for him to fight.

Seeing that the three Universal Civilizations were not making a move, Han Xiao opened the interface. The Challenge Mission triggered by Oulou was already shown as completed.

Since he could not leave at this point and could not acquire some luck, Han Xiao chose to conclude it on the spot.

[Beyond Grade A Challenge Mission—'Golden Ring' Oulou] completed!

You have completed all the mission requirements. You have received 86 Billion EXP!

You have received [Character Summon Card – 'Golden Ring' Oulou]!

Character Summon Card – 'Golden Ring' Oulou: [Golden Treasure Ship—Ram]—Condense the energy of the Golden Treasure Ship dimension in your body and carry out a long-distance charging attack. You're immune to any Crowd Control abilities during the charge. Deals a high amount of melee combat damage. Usages: 0/3

"Aiyo, a distance closing ability, nice."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Sadly, Oulou did not use this ability earlier, or he would have had the chance to do some stretching.

"If there's a chance in the future, I shall try to see if I can get some taunt-type ability. I feel like this is what my combat style needs…"

If he could just yell, "Come here, ya coward!" and the enemy actively went to him, it would be amazing.

Shaking his head, he put these thoughts behind and looked at the rest of the notification.

You have received a reward: Draw one of Oulou's Abilities/Talents.

Note: Oulou is an Esper, so part of the abilities/talents are adjusted according to your class.

Randomizing… complete!

Please select one from the five options below as the reward.

[Energy Control Precision] - Talent: Tremendously increase your ability to control energy, +10% Energy Resistance.

[Secondary Dimension Affinity] - Talent: Increases the chance of you building a connection with some secondary dimensions, grants you comprehensive bonuses when using the power of a secondary dimension.

[Liveliness Increase] - Ability: By stimulating your cells, temporarily increase the activity of your cells. +10% – 20% Health, Energy, and Stamina; +50% – 100% basic recovery speed of Health, Energy, Stamina. Duration: 15 minutes.

[Exquisite Taste] - Talent: +15%. You gain the Favorability of some people more easily.

[Phase Blink] - Ability: Using the secondary dimension, move by phasing and temporarily dodge most attacks. Cooldown: 6 minutes.

Han Xiao tutted. "My luck is ordinary as always without touching Feidin."

After all, due to the difference in class, most of the core abilities of Espers were unobtainable. A surprise like with Gaud would not happen every time.

Looking through, Han Xiao made a decision very quickly.

You have received the talent [Secondary Dimension Affinity]!

He had a link with the Void Dimension and the Underworld, and his Racial Talent was also related to the Void Dimension, so choosing this talent would indirectly enhance his Racial Talent. As for the other options, they were either too ordinary, or he already had something similar.

Comparatively, the ability of this Character Summon Card was quite good. After all, it gave immunity to Crowd Control abilities, which might be amazing in some scenarios.

After concluding the reward, seeing that the three Universal Civilizations still did not make any move, Han Xiao started looking at the forums.

More than half a day passed like this. When only eight and a half days were left till the end of the three Universal Civilizations' ultimatum deadline, they finally struck the second time.

A total of thirteen direct Beyond Grade As stepped up and walked out. Only then did Han Xiao close the forums and size them up. He saw that Clotti and Oulou among them, clearly the leaders.

This was a horrifying enough team. In a direct head-on battle, other than God's Chosen who no one knew what his limits were, no one else in the universe could match up to it. Plus, there were no actors among these people; they had the same goal and would not hold back at all.

"Yo, no more duels?" Han Xiao said with a mocking tone.

Oulou looked ashamed. He had already adjusted back to normal after the humiliating loss, and he could not have been more embarrassed.

This time, Clotti slowly said, "Black Star, you are indeed strong. However, since you stepped up to take challenges, you won't mind us fighting you in a group, will you?"

"Whatever. No matter how many Beyond Grade As you send, as long as you can defeat me." Han Xiao did not mind.

Clotti nodded. He suddenly changed the topic and said, "His Excellency told me to ask you a question… Gaud, you killed him, didn't you?"

As he said that, the other direct members were surprised. Even the many onlookers were stunned.

The Gaud incident was huge back then, and many people still had an impression of it. Now that it was brought up, many people were reminded of it once more.

"Oh? I'm warning you. We might be enemies, but I won't just let you frame me like this," Han Xiao said with a poker face.

Clotti added with a deep voice, "Originally, we didn't suspect you because you were the dynasty's ally. However, there were way too many suspicious parts about that incident back then. In recent years, you've become more and more lawless, so our suspicion of you has grown as well. You had plenty of reasons to attack Gaud… Sorokin might not be the culprit, just someone you framed!"

Han Xiao waved, interrupted him, and said casually, "What you say means nothing without evidence. I've never even thought of killing Gaud."

"You think you can clear your suspicion?"

"Hehe, I'm not guilty."

Han Xiao did not mind it.

Of course, I never thought of killing Gaud. I only sealed him up. He's still alive, so this isn't a lie.

Plus, other than him, probably no one else knew about the fact that Gaud was EsGod. He never regretted capturing that guy; it was only a pity no one knew his contribution.

While speaking, Han Xiao stood up from his throne. The gates of the secondary dimensional army boxes opened behind him.

Even Han Xiao did not dare act overconfident facing this situation. None of these thirteen direct members were ordinary. The three Universal Civilizations had probably given each of them Universal Treasures, so they might have some trump cards. Plus, when fighting together, their strength would not just add up but multiply.

However, taking the opponents seriously was one thing, but he was not going to say it out loud.

"Thirteen Beyond Grade As… it's at least enough for me to warm up a little."

As he said that, the swarm of mechanical army appeared once again. This time, they gathered around Han Xiao and quickly assembled into a Mechanical Deity.

Seeing this, Clotti and the others spread out and formed an encirclement. Their energy presence became unrestrained and clashed with Han Xiao's energy presence. The energy readings in the area rocketed, and the spacetime stability started to fluctuate.

In this extremely tense moment, another Mechanical Deity suddenly appeared in the Mechanical Race's fleet. It was Manison, and he instantly attracted everyone's attention.

The next moment, Manison suddenly threw out the Emperor Mechanic's Sacred Trident at Han Xiao, the rest of the Universal Treasures on the body of his Mechanical Deity also detached and flew toward Han Xiao.

Han Xiao caught the Emperor Mechanic's Sacred Trident that was covered in electronic sparks. The various Mechanical Deity exclusive weapons of Manison also attached to his Mechanical Deity's body, assembling perfectly. The controls of these equipment were transferred to Han Xiao, and his Mechanical Deity looked more magnificent right away.

He turned around and looked at Manison. He then heard Manison speaking in their channel.

"Since they're fighting you as more than one, I'll lend you my weapons."

"… I don't need it, but thanks."

Han Xiao weighed the Emperor Mechanic's Sacred Trident and felt complicated.

Old Manison had always taken the secrecy of his technology extremely importantly and treated these Universal Treasures almost like his wives.

I could only secretly steal them, but now he's willing to lend them to me… Damn, I'm touched.

Han Xiao turned and looked at Clotti and the others. Psionic energy spun around the blade of the trident, leaving ripple-like afterimages as Han Xiao swung it.

"Old Manison, since you're so generous this time, let me show you something new."

As he said that, blood-colored energy erupted and entangled around the Mechanical Deity's body. Its appearance changed subtly.

It was as if these streams of blood energy were forming flesh on the Mechanical Deity's body!

A strange energy ripple spread, giving the Beyond Grade As even greater pressure.

Clotti, the others, and Manison all looked with surprise at Han Xiao, whose appearance was changing rapidly.

"This guy's Mechanical Deity… why does it look different from the others'?"

Chapter 1305: Intense Battle

In the blink of an eye, the black Mechanical Deity's appearance changed. Flesh grew out from the gaps of the mechanical parts like roots of a plant rapidly digging into the ground. The Mechanical Deity's body seemed to have become the bones, wrapped in firm and strong flesh tissues. It turned from a mechanical giant to a biochemical prosthetic giant.

During the shapeshift, the energy presence Han Xiao was releasing was also enhanced. The radars of all the battleships around were shocking record-breaking individual energy readings.

At the same time, the blood-red energy and the golden Mechanical Force electronic arcs entangled each other, releasing from the Mechanical Deity's body like water vapor. It was very flashy. The mechanical army around reflected the light from it and painted the battlefield gold and red.

Clotti and the others looked at this in dismay. They felt a sense of pressure, and fear surfaced in their hearts uncontrollably, awakening memories that had been buried for a very long time…

This feeling was like the life hierarchy pressure they had experienced before when they were young, and it had been a very long time since they felt it after becoming Beyond Grade As!

"What the hell is that? I've never seen a Mechanical Deity like this!" Oulou's expression changed drastically.

Clotti's expression was grave. "I've never seen other Mechanics use this. This is probably Black Star's own innovation. It has some similarities with the Polar Channel Flow, so it should be some kind of burst ability… It doesn't look simple. Stay alert!"

Manison's eyes were opening wide, and his heart was filled with shock.

"What ability is this?"

As a senior Mechanic, he was shocked to realize he could not figure it out right away, and he was filled with questions.

This doesn't look like a Mechanic's ability!

What has Black Star been studying?

However, as he looked closer, Manison discovered something.

There are signs of the Felon technology… Did Black Star reverse engineer the Felons‽

Manison was astounded.

While everyone was shocked, the spacetime suddenly shook, and a ring of energy suddenly exploded at where the Mechanical Deity was standing. The next moment, the Mechanical Deity's enormous body disappeared. Dragging a chain of electronic tracks behind, it came right before Clotti and the others. Its dash was almost as quick as teleportation, and its size did not make it slower at all.

Wrapped with blue psionic energy, the tip of a trident instantly appeared in front of Clotti's eyes!

Getta Hadoken—Vortex Blade!

In the blink of the eye, Clotti took a deep breath, absorbed the dark energy that was everywhere in the universe, and released it at the blade of the trident like a tsunami.

Boom!

The next moment, a ring-shaped shockwave exploded from the point of impact!

Clotti's body shot out like a cannonball, turning into a stream of light, and penetrated battleships one after another.

In just one move, the Crimson Dynasty's National Pillar, Dark Lord, was blown away!

The many direct Beyond Grade As reacted instantly. Not having the leisure to be shocked, they immediately worked together and attacked Han Xiao. The battle broke out in a flash!

At the same time, Clotti's serious toned voice sounded in their team channel.

"Don't fight him head-on!"

Clotti finally stopped himself from flying backward and charged back toward the battlefield, covered in a crystal yellow prism-shaped shield that was now filled with cracks.

This shield was not his ability but a protective Universal Treasure with an extremely high defense that was triggered. Since the three Universal Civilizations had sent them to fight Black Star, they were not going to be petty with their Universal Treasures. They had given several Universal Treasures to each direct member.

Although he was not injured, this attack from Han Xiao still shocked Clotti.

While the defense capability of this protection type Universal Treasure was not invincible like the Spacetime Amber, it was still exceptional. If the attack damage did not reach a certain standard, it could almost block all damage. Even he had to charge his attack for some time to penetrate it. It was a complete surprise to Clotti how Han Xiao casually broke it with one attack.

Hearing Clotti's words, the direct member Beyond Grade As spread out and moved swiftly in the battlefield. The Mechanics brought out their armies, and the Mages pulled out their summoned creature armies too, covering the skies and restraining Han Xiao. At the same time, Han Xiao's mechanical army arrived and joined the battle.

Both sides used the Human Wave Tactic, and the battle instantly became a huge brawl.

Turning into a Mechanical Deity, Han Xiao swung the Mechanic Emperor's Sacred Trident speedily and slashed his way in the crowd. Everything his attacks landed on was either heavily damaged or broken instantly. The blade of the trident shattered piles and piles of enemies. He looked invincible.

His ranged weapons were also firing nonstop, chasing the direct member Beyond Grade As everywhere. His body was also covered in electromagnetic and space fields, so anything that got close was either immobilized or shattered.

This form of Mechanical Deity was what Han Xiao had invented from imitating SWY-001. Its name was [Mechanical Deity—Semi-living Body]. It was a special shapeshifting technology he innovated by using SWY-001 as the foundation and adding in more technology. It was an upgraded version of the Mechanical Deity, and all of its performance parameters were superior compared to the normal version.

The prerequisite was not only [Polar Channel Flow—Blood Rage] but also Hila's death energy and Aurora's life energy. In the past few years, through using the Gaud Character Summon Card's [Energy Analysis], he had studied the principles and nature of these two special types of energy. He had achieved some results and fused them into this technology. Only then was he able to turn blood energy back to flesh and tissue. At the same time, he did indeed use some of the Felon technology's concepts, successfully fusing the Super cells and the machines together, which made the flesh tissues increase the energy output tremendously.

It was only 'semi' because the functions of the flesh tissues were not complete. His ideal goal was to achieve the level of SWY-001, meaning the flesh tissues could both increase energy output and provide energy, balanced and whole like an independent living body.

Unfortunately, Han Xiao could not completely duplicate this mechanism. The flesh cells that covered the Mechanical Deity could only increase the Mechanical Deity's energy output but not provide energy, which meant that the Mechanical Deity's energy consumption increased but its maximum energy remained the same, so the balance was broken. He did not know if the reason was because the flesh tissues came from only one person or not, he just could not reach a balance like SWY-001 could. This led to the energy consumption of [Mechanical Deity—Semi-living Body] being extremely outrageous; even peak Beyond Grade As could barely afford it.

However, Han Xiao was already at the top of the Void Race system and had linked with the Void Dimension. He could use the Void energy like Kasuyi could. Even without getting beat up, he had almost an infinite amount of mana, so this was not a problem for him at all.

Han Xiao's burst strength was too incredible, chasing the direct Beyond Grade As all around the battlefield. However, after their initial shock, Clotti and the others gradually adapted to this amount of pressure. The two sides fought intensely.

Clotti and Oulou were both top tier peak Beyond Grade As whose Energy Rank was above 90,000, and they had received a lot of enhancements. Although they were no match for Han Xiao alone, as they fought together, their combined strength multiplied.

Both their Esper Abilities were AOE types that were amazing at this type of large scale battle. Plus, mana was also no issue for them. With all kinds of Universal Treasures, they took care of more than half of Han Xiao's attacks.

Furthermore, Clotti and Oulou had a group of teammates who were quite strong too. They were not the only two who had above a 70,000 Energy Rank; those stationed in the secondary dimension bases were mostly elites, only they did not appear in public often.

Buzz!

Enormous electromagnetic bolts formed dancing lightning chains crisscrossing between the mechanical army, causing tremendous damage. Covered in bright blue lightning arcs, Guzar stirred up a lightning storm like the god of thunder. Every time he raised his hand, electromagnetic cannons were released and landed on Han Xiao's protective shield, causing countless explosions.

He was someone from the same generation as Clotti. Although his potential was not as high as Clotti's, he was still a very powerful Beyond Grade A. If not, he would not have been sent by the dynasty to defend a secondary dimension outpost.

'Holy Disciple' Mornan, who was wearing a monk outfit, teleported continuously within the mechanical army with the help of some kind of teleportation type Universal Treasure. His fists and legs struck at an ordinary speed, as if they were hitting a transparent barrier. The particles in large portions of the cosmic space resonated, dealing continuous large area vibration damage to Han Xiao's mechanical army. Although he was a Pugilist, the many Universal Treasures he had made up for what he lacked.

'Army Leader' Padro summoned countless creatures and magic colossuses nonstop, fighting with Han Xiao's mechanical army. There were also many boss level units that attempted to retrain Han Xiao by any means necessary without having a care about their casualties. At the same time, 'Army Flag' Enid activated her abilities all the time, providing all kinds of enhancements to her allies present.

The thirteen direct Beyond Grade As were not only powerful but their coordination was amazing too. Along with the Universal Treasures they had, they could match up to Han Xiao, even enduring the pressure of dozens of Apostle Weapons.

With the Universal Treasures he had built in the past years, Han Xiao did not show signs of defeat even when facing such a luxurious team.

Once again blowing Clotti away, Han Xiao looked around the battlefield and pondered.

The situation was in a stalemate, but he did not feel pressure at all, which was mainly because the enemies posed a limited threat to him. Although he could not break away from these people for the time being, he was not in a dangerous situation.

He had the absolute upper hand in terms of individual strength. Any time he had the opportunity to get into a one versus one battle, he would crush the opponent. Be it Clotti or Oulou, no one could stop his powerful attacks. However, when that happened, the others always came to restrain him and defuse their teammate's danger.

"I need to aim for the weak spot and find a breakthrough."

The essence of fighting a group was to target and chase after one person. Without hesitation, Han Xiao changed his attack target and charged toward a comparatively weaker direct Beyond Grade A.

The others saw and hastily came to focus fire on Han Xiao. Han Xiao bathed in attacks and ignored them. His Sacred Trident swung heavily up and down. Every attack seemed like it could shatter space itself.

Boom!

The enormous trident blade slashed down once again, painting a blood rose in midair. This direct member Beyond Grade A was sent out flying, heavily injured.

As Han Xiao wanted to end him, the other dozen Beyond Grade As ignored the damage they took and held him back with their lives while a traction beam shot out from the three Universal Civilizations joint fleet's main ship and took the wounded away.

The next moment, three more direct Beyond Grade As flew out of the main ship and joined the battle. Han Xiao's opponents increased to fifteen. The situation went back to a stalemate, and the pressure he faced increased again.

Han Xiao's eyes gleamed.

He understood what the three Universal Civilizations were planning. They brought a group of direct members here. Anyone who was heavily injured by him would be pulled back and healed up, and more would be sent into the battlefield. Using the advantage of their fleet not being attacked, they could give their direct Beyond Grade A members time to recover.

After all, Han Xiao was alone and could not take a break, while the three Universal Civilizations had dozens of direct members. They made up their mind to exhaust Han Xiao by any means.

They wanted both to win and not suffer any casualties.

"Tsk, dirty enough."

Han Xiao curled his lips and did not say anything. After all, nowhere was there a rule that said the three Universal Civilizations could not do this.

"Since you all want to do it like this, let's see who can last longer."

He shook his head, got rid of these thoughts, and focused on the battle.

The two sides fought intensely for six days and six nights.

…

The battlefield had shifted multiple times. Everywhere was filled with machinery fragments and carcasses of summoned creatures. The size of the armies on both sides had shrunk tremendously. Be it Han Xiao's mechanical army or the direct Beyond Grade As' all kinds of armies, they all suffered severe damage.

The Mechanical Deity that Han Xiao turned into was still fighting intensely with Clotti and the others. However, comparatively, Han Xiao was still very energetic, while many of his opponents were already showing signs of being exhausted.

The number of direct Beyond Grade As in the battlefield had increased to twenty-one. Having fought with everything they had for six days consecutively, most people were exhausted, and their status dropped unavoidably. Even though some of them exchanged shifts more than a dozen times, they could not take it much longer.

The entire process was broadcast live by the media.

Not many galactic residents could keep watching in front of the screen all the time. However, whenever they turned to this channel, the intense fight was still going on.

God knew how many people were praying night day for Black Star to be defeated. However, despite facing such a grand team, Black Star was still as strong as he was at the start, not showing any signs of defeat at all. The feelings of many galactic residents changed from shock to despair, then numbness, watching the intense battle on the screen with an empty mind.

What monster is Black Star? Doesn't he get tired‽

Seeing that there was no hope the war could be avoided, many galactic residents became irritated and started to condemn Han Xiao. It was as if strength became a sin. They found a way to vent all their rage, panic, and dissatisfaction at Han Xiao, like the roars of the powerless.

While the three Universal Civilizations' soldiers present at the scene's morale kept dropping in the past few days. They were dumbfounded by Black Star's strength.

Their high-level combatants put down their pride and used such an unethical strategy just to outnumber Black Star. Changing shifts to fight him was already embarrassing enough, yet not only could they not take Black Star down, but some of them even got killed.

They were still getting thrashed!

The Beyond Grade As who were watching from various channels were even more shocked. They knew how difficult this was more than the others, and as if this was the first time they met Han Xiao, they were all astonished.

Although we knew our president was strong all along, isn't this too strong‽

In the entire history of Supers, there did not seem to be anyone who ever achieved something like this. The many Beyond Grade As were astounded.

It seemed to them that the strength Black Star was displaying probably exceeded any Beyond Grade A ever recorded in the history of the explored universe. He was on an entirely new level.

"What the f*ck? Is old Black still a human‽"

"I finally understand the meaning of the version name… Is this the definition of the Age of Black Star?"

"Who's next!"

Compared to others, the players were the most excited. Having watched a six-day-long action movie, their passion was boiling.

No matter how the others responded, the battle still carried on.

Clank!

The blade of the trident slashed down time after time chasing after a direct Beyond Grade A, shattering his shield and spilling blood.

Just as Han Xiao was about to give him the last hit as usual, Clotti and Oulou stood before him. Dark energy and golden energy gushed out and clashed with the trident!

Boom!

A blinding explosion erupted. Clotti and Oulou were pushed back afar as blood poured out from their mouths. Their injuries got heavier once again.

At the same time, the already heavily damaged Sacred Trident finally reached its limits and shattered into fragments.

Han Xiao looked at his empty hands and then looked around. All the direct Beyond Grade As who were surrounding him were wounded and looked visibly exhausted.

"Looks like you guys can't last much longer."

Han Xiao clenched his fist and pulled out a melee mechanical weapon that looked like a spear. It was black and gold, and its tip was pyramid shaped, like the spear of a cavalry. This was also a Universal Treasure. It came from Jayz' technology treasure.

Clotti coughed a few times, spitting out a cloud of blood. He forced himself to stay alert and said with a deep voice, "You don't have many troops left either."

"I have enough. On the other hand, Oulou and you seem to have reached your limits. The others can swap with the rest, but not the two of you. Can you still fight?"

Han Xiao did not mind it.

Clotti remained silent. He could not disagree.

The other direct members could swap with the others and rest. However, without Clotti or Oulou, their team had no chance of fighting Black Star; the others would only be crushed.

Therefore, for the past six days, the two of them did not rest either and were covered in wounds. Although they were not short on energy, their wounds were getting more severe. They were close to their limits.

It would be great if God's Chosen was willing to step in. Sadly, he had been watching on the side for the past six days and never did anything, as if he was really there just to watch.

There were only two days left till the end of the ten-day warning period the three Universal Civilizations gave. They probably could not complete the mission given to them anymore…

When Clotti was about to give everything he had left, a sigh suddenly sounded in their team channel.

A person flew out from the main ship of the three Universal Civilizations joint fleet and entered the battlefield.

The others turned to look at him and were shocked. It was Wuornos, who had remained silent till then.

Ignoring his teammates, Wuornos looked at Han Xiao, sighed with resignation, and said, "Black Star, although we've only met once, I actually have quite the respect for you and don't want to fight you. Unfortunately… I'm a direct member of the Arcane Church, and I can't disobey orders."

After that, ignoring everyone else's reactions, Wuornos raised his hand, aimed his finger in Han Xiao's direction, and tapped softly.

As an invisible energy was released from his fingers, a pale-golden light suddenly flew out from inside the Mechanical Deity's body and entered Wuornos's body.

At this instant, an enormous shadow of the Mechanical Deity came out of his body from his back.

The next moment, this Mechanical Deity detached from his body and quickly materialized. It had Wuornos's face, but its appearance was extremely similar to Han Xiao's Mechanical Deity, as if they were twins!

Chapter 1306: God's Chosen and the Incredible Church National Treasure

In the torn-up battlefield, the second living Mechanical Deity appeared. The weapons and equipment it had were almost exactly the same as Han Xiao's Mechanical Deity, like a carbon copy of him.

This replica Mechanical Deity had a poker face and stood opposite Han Xiao. Powerful energy was released from its body continuously.

This startled countless galactic residents, and their shocked eyes all focused on Wuornos.

"Another new Beyond Grade A? I don't seem to recall seeing this person before."

"What ability is this? Seems strong…"

"I know this guy! He's the Arcane Church's Grand Priest!"

Countless galactic residents opened their eyes wide. The extinguished hope in their hearts was rekindled.

Among the Beyond Grade As, Wuornos was an oddity. He rarely fought others or appeared in public, nor did the Arcane Church promote him. His presence in the outside world was not high at all. Without deliberately searching for his information, ordinary people would not even know he existed in the universe. However, in the Beyond Grade A circle, he was recognized by all as the strongest.

Seeing Wuornos arrive, Oulou heaved a sigh of relief but was also a little unhappy.

"You've finally decided to come. I thought you'd just watch till the end."

Tsk, we've been exhausting ourselves and fighting Han Xiao for six days and six nights. Did you deliberately only now join us to 'turn the tide' alone?

Wuornos looked around at the many direct members, sighed, and said, "You guys have fought hard. I'll take it from here. Go and rest."

"You still want to fight him alone?" Clotti frowned.

"I don't like to bully the few." Wuornos shook his head.

"You think we like it?" Clotti frowned. "This is an order from above. If you join the fight, we'll have the highest chances of taking down Black Star. Aren't you too cocky to want to fight him alone now?"

Wuornos glanced at him and calmly said, "Earlier, I was given an absolute order to help, but I told them I won't join the fight unless I'm fighting alone. They agreed. If you have objections, you can convey them to the Crimson Dynasty's Ruler. If you guys don't need help, I'll be going back to the ship."

Clotti frowned, opened the channel, and shared a few words with the dynasty's upper echelons. He then gave Wuornos a deep look, turned around, and flew back to the main ship without saying a word.

The others also received orders from above, glanced at Wuornos with complicated looks, and left the battlefield.

Suddenly, other than the wreckages everywhere, Han Xiao and Wuornos were the only two people left on the battlefield.

Han Xiao had been watching on the side. Seeing that the other direct members had left, his eyes gleamed, and he said, "Your ability is interesting."

Wuornos did not respond to this. He changed the topic and said slowly, "I've been observing you for the past seven days. You're probably already half a step into the higher territory. I'm not someone who likes to fight. If possible, I really wouldn't want to fight you, but…"

This time, Han Xiao waved his hand and interrupted him.

"We don't know each other. You don't have to explain anything to me. Many people have been saying you're recognized as the strongest Beyond Grade A. I've always wanted to see how strong you are personally."

He turned to look at the other living body Mechanical Deity, narrowed his eyes, and said, "I have to say, with this ability, you can indeed be considered the 'strongest'. However, a fake will always be just that, a fake."

When Wuornos used his ability earlier, a notification had popped up on Han Xiao's interface too. It showed that he was affected by an ability called [God Embodiment—Granted]. Although the ability worked, it did not deal any damage to him or any debuffs.

Planning ahead, before the Mechanical Race territory was surrounded, he had already expected that he might have to fight Wuornos. Hence, he had asked about the detailed intelligence of this person from Kasuyi and the others, finding out that 'granting Gods' was one of Wuornos' abilities. He could materialize the concept of some 'Gods' into powerful physical forms, which were called 'God Embodiments'.

The God Embodiments were independent from their original body, usually called by the name of the original God. They had the various abilities the original 'God' conceptually had but not all of them. The number of abilities and their power were not only related to Wuornos' strength but also the number of believers that worshipped this 'God' and the depth of their faith.

However, the targets Wuornos could grant also included anything that was deified. Therefore, peak Beyond Grade As who were going through the God's Trait Transformation were also included. When the target of the granting was not a 'concept' but something with physical form, the God Embodiment would then be able to inherit the target's most strength and abilities, even without believers of faith.

According to the upper echelons of the association, if they were to fight Wuornos, they would have to first face a mirrored version of 'themselves' while at the same time fight with Wuornos' other God Embodiments. This was one of the reasons he was recognized by all as the strongest; he would become stronger against stronger opponents.

Furthermore, what was more disgustingly strong was that, if a God Embodiment that had a physical original body was destroyed, the damage would be reflected back to its original body. This meant that when peak Beyond Grade As killed their mirrored 'self', they would suffer damage too.

A few Ancient Ones shared a secret. Very long ago, Wuornos' success rate of granting Gods was limited, and it did not work every time.

However, Wuornos' ability was nothing short of a perfect fit with the Arcane Church. After being given many Universal Treasures related to his ability by the Arcane Church and forming strong Soul Links with them, the success rate of his granting ability was fixed at a hundred percent. In the players' terms, this basically meant that the judgement process was skipped.

The Universal Treasures given to him also included a core treasure seen by the Arcane Church as their 'National Treasure'. It could be said to be the foundation of how the Arcane Church united all the religions in galactic society. Wuornos matched with it perfectly, as if he was born for it.

The only good news was that when the interface showed he was 'Granted' one time, it also showed that he received a prolonged immunity to it. This meant that Wuornos could not continuously 'Grant' the same target in a short time. Plus, the time the God Embodiments could exist also had limits.

Even with Han Xiao's knowledge, he had to say that Wuornos' ability was extremely powerful, almost like a cheat, like himself!

Scary, this ability is somewhat like a weird version of the Character Summon Cards…

Han Xiao was surprised.

Seems like we're both professional cheaters… Our battle will be legendary!

As all kinds of information flashed past his mind, Han Xiao's movements were no slower. He gathered the remainder of the mechanical army and launched attacks at Wuornos.

At the same time, controlling the Mechanical Deity, he charged forward and struck with his spear.

At this time, another mechanical spear stopped in the path of Han Xiao's spear, the tips of the spears clashed.

Bang!

A powerful psionic shockwave erupted, the two spears stacked together and stopped each other.

"Your opponent is me."

The fake Mechanical Deity with Wuornos' face spoke coldly.

"Yo, you can even speak."

Han Xiao's eyes gleamed. He suddenly twisted the handle of the spear. The spear started spinning rapidly. Tremendous energy erupted and instantly pushed the other spear away. Then, like a drill, it penetrated into the fake Mechanical Deity's chest. Compressed psionic energy gushed out from the tip of the spear, launching flesh and metal everywhere.

However, like it had no sense of pain, the fake Mechanical Deity instantly retaliated, swinging its heavy spear forward. Seeing this, Han Xiao pulled back his spear and blocked it. Blinding electronic arcs exploded from the point of contact, and the powerful force pushed Han Xiao back.

Han Xiao looked up and saw that the fake Mechanical Deity had a gory wound on its chest that almost went all the way through his body. However, the next moment, the flesh and machines near the wound started to move and slowly grew back.

Han Xiao tutted. "Tsk, as expected, it's as difficult to kill as me."

His own extraordinary regenerative ability was also duplicated by this God Embodiment. The fake Mechanical Deity had an Indestructible Body. Only a few abilities were not duplicated. Although its strength was a lot weaker than him, from the way it looked, it definitely had an Energy Rank above ten thousand. It was stronger than top-tier Beyond Grade As like Clotti and Oulou, definitely capable of fighting him.

At the same time, the Apostle Weapons who were all wounded started to focus fire at Wuornos's original body, and attacks rained like a storm.

Wuornos calmly put his hands together like he was praying. Colorful spiritual lights appeared on his body and rapidly expanded, turning into bright symbols, forming an enormous protective shield, and protecting him from the rain of attacks.

He separated his hands. Eight faint-gold spiritual lights appeared and jumped into his mouth.

The next moment, eight God Embodiments with varied appearances detached from Wuornos' body, all giving off the presence of powerful Beyond Grade As. They charged toward the mechanical troops around and displayed their strength.

"I'll have to worship these again when I get back."

Wuornos shook his head. Having summoned eight God Embodiments at once, he felt a little heartache.

A few days ago, when he got urgently summoned, he had harvested the 'deifications' of about ten God sculptures from the Temple of Ten Thousand Gods and stored them in the church's 'National Treasure' in his body. When he had to fight, he could summon the God Embodiments any time. If there was no need to fight, he could put the 'deifications' back.

He was the only one who knew that every time he summoned the God Embodiments from the God sculptures in the Temple of Ten Thousand Gods, it would consume the 'deifications' in these God sculptures that took a long time to accumulate, and he would not be able to summon another God Embodiment from the same sculpture again in a short time. The Gold sculptures' 'deifications' would only recover through praying and worshipping for a very long time. Only then would he be able to summon God Embodiments from them again.

The strength of these God Embodiments also relied on how many 'deifications' their sculptures had, and accumulating 'deifications' was extremely troublesome and time consuming.

To him, the Temple of Ten Thousand Gods he was stationed at was his weapon inventory, and the God sculptures were his ammo… However, he liked to think of the Temple of Ten Thousand Gods more as a farm, every God sculpture as a crop that needed to be taken care of every day. Unless absolutely necessary, he did not want to harvest any crops.

Knowing himself well, he knew he could not easily grant eight God Embodiments at once easily. However, the Church National Treasure already fused with him perfectly. Even if he did not use it actively, the passive bonuses it gave him still increased the strength of his ability to an unbelievable height.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, suddenly charged forward with his body, and knocked the fake Mechanical Deity away. Drill-shaped machinery shot out from his waist and bit onto the fake Mechanical Deity's waist like charge cabins. The Psionic Deterioration modules were activated immediately, absorbing the fake Mechanical Deity's energy.

As the fake Mechanical Deity was restrained, Han Xiao suddenly turned and swung his spear toward Wuornos. He planned to target him first.

Seeing this, Wuornos released two more God Embodiments. This time, these two God Embodiments did not materialize but melted and fused with Wuornos as if he was possessed.

His energy presence suddenly rocketed. He raised his energy-covered arms in front of him, not dodging the attack at all.

The next moment, the heavy spear swept onto him like a truck ramming toward an ant.

Clank!

An enormous shockwave exploded. However, the result was completely different from when Clotti got sent flying.

Wuornos' hands remained in the same position; his body did not even move back a single inch. Instead, the enormous mechanical spear was stopped. It was as if the ant had stopped an entire truck.

Wuornos glanced at Han Xiao and did not say anything. He only put down his hands and slowly backed off, as if he did not take the attack earlier seriously at all and was not worried about Han Xiao continuing to attack him.

"It's tough to beat, as expected of the National Treasure of the church…"

Han Xiao frowned.

According to the description of someone who knew about the church's National Treasure, it had the trait of 'Unbreakable' and extremely high resistance, which were given to Wuornos too.

God only knew what percentage of Wuornos' strength came from the church's National Treasure. Fighting with him was not just that but also fighting with the pinnacle technology of a Universal Civilization!

Therefore, when Beyond Grade As were compared with each other, they rarely ever considered Wuornos because it would simply be unfair!

At this time, the fake Mechanical Deity got rid of his restraints and pounced at Han Xiao again, dragging his Mechanical Deity back.

Having fought for six days and six nights, Han Xiao was not at his peak. His mechanical army had suffered heavy casualties; most of it had been sent into the Dimension Factory for repairs. At this point, only about twenty percent of his army still had combat capabilities. Plus, all of them had gone through a few times of Waste Modifications. In the face of Wuornos' many God Embodiments, the battle was getting tough.

Dealing with the fake Mechanical Deity's attacks, Han Xiao glanced at the worsening situation on the battlefield and narrowed his eyes.

"Wuornos indeed deserves the praise. Looks like it's going to be a tough fight… Luckily, I have more things up my sleeve!"

…

In the three Universal Civilizations' main ship, Clotti and the other direct Beyond Grade As had already finished attending to their wounds. They were all gathered at the bridge watching the intense fight between Black Star and Wuornos.

Seeing how Wuornos could match up with Black Star who fought all of them alone, they all felt bitter.

"How many years has it been since we saw God's Chosen fight? He's still extraordinarily strong." Guzar sighed.

"Humph, if I had a Universal Treasure as strong as the church's National Treasure, I could be that strong." Oulou's tone was sour.

"That's given that the Federation of Light can build one like it." Francisco shrugged.

"Who you looking down at?" Verena snorted.

They chatted casually, slightly flushing away the heavy atmosphere.

Oulou turned around, realized that Clotti was not speaking, and said, "We fought Black Star for six days and nights, exhausting him. Now that Wuornos has come out to fight him alone, maybe he just wants to have the fruit of victory for himself. If he defeats Black Star, not only will he gain all the reputation, we'll even be his steppingstone. Aren't you angry about that?"

Clotti glanced at him and said with a poker face, "I don't care about these trivialities, as long as the mission given to us is completed. As for who defeats Black Star in the end, it doesn't matter."

"Tsk. If words get out that Wuornos defeated someone we couldn't even defeat together, we'll be humiliated. You might not care about face, but I do!" Oulou clenched his teeth.

Clotti gave him a weird look and said, "You fled with your tail tucked between your legs after fighting Black Star alone. Your face is already non-existent. What are you talking about?"

"… F*ck!"

Oulou wanted to argue, but a change suddenly occurred!

Suddenly, an even stronger energy presence suddenly exploded from Black Star. His energy readings rocketed visibly, breaking the record every second!

Black Star's Mechanical Deity's strength soared. The next second, the enormous fake Mechanical Deity was thrown out into the formation of the three Universal Civilizations' fleet, toppling rows of battleships!

As if they were on steroids, the Apostle Weapons and the mechanical troops' power suddenly shot up. The God Embodiments that were originally overwhelming them suddenly could barely fight back, and their wounds grew rapidly.

Then, Han Xiao turned around and slashed down with his spear. The one God Embodiment he attacked instantly shattered and turned into light particles, as if it suddenly evaporated!

"Hmm‽" Wuornos' calm expression disappeared immediately.

The sudden change startled Clotti, Oulou, and the other direct Beyond Grade As. Their sights were instantly attracted by Han Xiao. Everyone opened their eyes the widest, their faces filled with shock.

He became stronger‽

He clearly held back earlier!

At this point, they shockingly realized one thing, and shivers shot up their spines.

"We fought with all we had for six days and six nights, yet we couldn't even make him go all out‽"

Chapter 1307: Defeat

Boom!

Wild thunder raged like dragons, dancing around Han Xiao.

The mechanical spear turned into an enormous bolt of lightning and struck again, targeting another red God Embodiment.

Restrained by the Apostle Weapons, this red God Embodiment could not dodge the attack in time. It hastily went into a defensive stance and knocked the side of the shield with its hammer. The shield instantly lit up and released an energy shield that enlarged thousands of times, blocking in front of the spear.

Bang!

The spear crashed onto the shield. The shield that looked indestructible shattered instantly like a fragile piece of paper. A shockwave expanded in a flash and triggered a loud explosion in everyone's mind like the sound of glass shattering.

With an enormous bolt of lightning, a light beam-like shockwave released from the tip of the spear. With this one attack, half of this God Embodiment's body was instantly shattered!

At this time, Wuornos teleported from afar, focused his strength at his elbow and deviated the direction of the spear, dodging the second round of damage. He then dragged the heavily damaged God Embodiment aside, saving it at the last point.

Wuornos sized Han Xiao up once again. Feeling the even stronger energy presence of the Mechanical Deity, complicated feelings flashed past his eyes.

"Is this your full strength? Looks like I still underestimated you… No, I should say you hid your strength too well, just like the rumors. No one really knows just how many trump cards you have and where your limit is."

"Why have I never heard of this rumor?" Han Xiao replied casually.

While he had been fighting with the three Universal Civilizations, he had been suppressing the impulse to use his Character Summon Cards, all to make sure he could use them if Wuornos showed up.

Wuornos could summon Gods, but he had Character Summon Cards too.

He had activated double Mechanical Sense and double the Ancient Ones, instantly entering into his explosive state.

If he had activated the Character Summon Cards earlier, the three Universal Civilizations' direct members probably would not have lasted as long as six days. Even if they could, there would have been many more of them dead in his hands.

"A hundred years is just a blink of an eye to Beyond Grade As; it's no more than a child's age. Yet, at such a young age, you've obtained such extraordinary strength… There has never been anyone in recorded history who was as talented as you are. I can hardly imagine just how bright your future is."

Wuornos sighed, took out his last few God Embodiments, and sent them into the battlefield to fight the mechanical army.

He had brought more than a dozen God Embodiments this time. Initially, he did not want to use the rest of them, but the situation now did not allow him to do that.

"Just a few? They're probably far from enough to defeat me." Han Xiao raised his brows.

These God Embodiments had varied abilities. Although they all had high level Beyond Grade A's strength, they had a common weakness too—they were comparatively more fragile.

His strength in the explosive state exceeded the knowledge of ordinary people. He could easily crush high-level Beyond Grade As. As long as these God Embodiments did not have any special defense, dodge, or regenerative abilities, he could shatter them in seconds. It was much easier than dealing with those direct Beyond Grade As with multiple Universal Treasures.

"Try me."

Wuornos held his hands together. His body suddenly expanded and enlarged, turning into a giant. Earlier, his size compared to Han Xiao's Mechanical Deity was like an ant and a mountain. Now, he was the same size as Han Xiao's Mechanical Deity.

Despite how large he became, the Grand Priest robe on his body was not torn but expanded with his body. Magic circuits that filled all of its surface started lighting up. Clearly, it was Universal Treasure-level enchanted equipment; only then did he not have to go nude in front of the entire universe.

This guy can grow bigger?

Han Xiao's eyes gleamed. This was not mentioned in the intelligence he had.

As if he saw Han Xiao's doubts, Wuornos slowly explained, "My God's Trait Transformation has already reached the maximum. My Giant blood is at its peak. This is my first time using this ability."

Having trained in the Arcane Church for many years, as the church's National Treasure and his own ability were related to divinity, his God's Trait Transformation progressed countless times faster than the other peak Beyond Grade As. He had completed both God's Trait Transformation routes long ago, but he had never told anyone.

Wuornos had the Giant bloodline, so the God's Trait Transformation on his race's side tremendously enhanced his Giant blood, turning it into the most optimized form. It was as if all the pros of the Race Evolution were gathered into one.

"Your luck is really incredible. Not only is your ability a perfect fit, but you even received the support of the church." Han Xiao frowned.

This b*stard was probably a protagonist-type character who most likely had Advanced Luck Glow, only he kept a low profile for countless years and hid his true strength. It was like he was the monk who swept the floors of a temple.

He looked at Wuornos's empty hands and said, "Are you planning to keep fighting me with your fists?"

Hearing this, Wuornos remained silent for a while, sighed, and said, "… You have already sealed up my weapon."

Han Xiao was stunned for a second, then it occurred to him.

Damn, the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter is this b*stard's equipment!

Specifically, Wuornos only shared the right to use it; the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter still belonged to the Arcane Church. Sadly, it was sealed up by the Spacetime Amber.

It made sense. This Universal Treasure also matched Wuornos' ability perfectly. It would not be weird for the church to let him use it… only he did not have the chance to use it now.

At this time, the fake Mechanical Deity finally returned to the battlefield after being blasted away in the fleet's formation. It pounced at Han Xiao fearlessly, clearly very headstrong.

Han Xiao turned around. The mechanical spear shapeshifted rapidly as if it had turned into a whip. He swung it backward, stirring up bright lightning bolts everywhere.

In the explosive state, the speed of strength of the Mechanical Deity increased tremendously. This attack was as fast as lightning; it instantly swept onto the fake Mechanical Deity's waist, almost cutting it half, sending it away flying and rolling once again.

A scorching wave of energy came from behind. Han Xiao turned around and placed his spear horizontally, stopping Wuornos' fist.

Boom!

A shockwave erupted!

The strength of both sides clashed. Han Xiao's thrusters operated at the maximum power output, gaining the upper hand and slowly pushing into Wuornos.

"The giant blood is quite strong indeed. Your strength is comparable to a Pugilist." Han Xiao snorted.

"And you."

Wuornos suddenly retracted his fist. The next second, afterimages of his fists filled Han Xiao's sights.

Not willing to take a step back, Han Xiao spun his spear and blocked each attack accurately. Shockwaves exploded in the cosmic space continuously.

This time, the fake Mechanical Deity returned and joined the battle again, then got blown away once more before charging back to the battle time and again.

Wuornos had the church's National Treasure to protect his body, while the fake Mechanical Deity inherited his own super strong regenerative abilities. Currently, the only breakthrough point in the battlefield was the other God Embodiments, which was what Han Xiao was planning to target exactly. Only, he was stopped by the two giants and had no choice but to endure their attacks to eliminate the God Embodiments.

As the battle reached this stage, there were no more shortcuts to be found, only head-on combat. The battle had already reached the climax.

Watching the live footage, the hearts of countless galactic residents rose to their throats as they watched the screen with all their attention.

"What a powerful Beyond Grade A, he must be the ace of the three Universal Civilizations!"

"God bless, please let Black Star be defeated… This is probably our last hope."

The galactic residents secretly prayed.

Meanwhile, the players were thrilled, completely the opposite of the galactic residents.

"Aiyo, I know this. The boss has entered stage two!"

"Clear the minions before fighting the boss, Old Black knows his dungeons."

"Anyone betting? I'm betting 30,000 Enas on Old Black, anyone?"

The many army players discussed the fight with excitement. The forums were already filled with the videos of those who were at the scene. The edited footage and recordings of Han Xiao's battle in the past few days had filled up more than ten pages, like it was an incredible VFX movie.

In the main ship of the three Universal Civilizations' fleet, the many direct Beyond Grade As looked outside the porthole with bitter expressions.

"I never thought Black Star held back against us… If he'd used this power earlier, many people in this room would probably not be breathing now." Verena smiled bitterly.

Hearing this, many Beyond Grade As glanced at her and felt complicated.

Originally, they thought they could at the very least match up to Black Star together. However, the truth was, that was only what they thought. Not only were they exhausted from fighting Black Star, they even had to appreciate Black Star for not going all out…

Having realized that, their mood became even heavier, and their confidence was severely damaged.

Having held back for a very long time, Oulou finally squeezed two words out between his teeth.

"Two monsters!"

Even as a peak Beyond Grade A, Oulou had to admit that these two people were terrifyingly strong. Not only was Black Star crazily powerful, but Wuornos was much stronger than many years ago. The two of them had surpassed the others and were on a completely different level from them.

This time, Guzar frowned and said, "There's only two days left till the warning period ends. Are we really going to let them fight one on one and watch?"

Hearing this, Clotti said seriously, "Of course not! When the warning period is about to end, we'll all strike together. Just ignore Wuornos, we must defeat Black Star no matter what, so get to recovering as fast as possible. If Wuornos still can't settle the battle by tomorrow, we'll have to fight again."

The others nodded solemnly.

Time passed quickly. Under countless pairs of eyes, Han Xiao already fought intensely with Wuornos for more than a day, the situation was already becoming clear.

Han Xiao finally eliminated all the God Embodiments except for the fake Mechanical Deity, and he paid a ton of mechanical troops as the price for that.

Although he was restrained by Wuornos and the fake Mechanical Deity, in his explosive state, his attributes were clearly superior. He continuously broke through the two of them, ignoring his injuries and eliminating the God Embodiments one after another, causing the strength difference between two sides to increase as time went on, making the situation easier and easier for him.

The last few God Embodiments were not even killed by him personally but by the mechanical troops and the Apostle Weapons. The remaining mechanical troops were already free to surround Wuornos and the fake Mechanical Deity, the only ones left.

Clank!

The two of them clashed once again. Wuornos moved back a certain distance, casually blasting away an Apostle Weapon, and suddenly sighed.

"You have killed all the God Embodiments I've brought here today, looks like I can't do much more."

"What, is that it?"

Han Xiao slapped the fake Mechanical Deity away once again and snorted.

"… We're the only two left. We won't be able to decide a winner if we continue." Wuornos shook his head.

"There's only one day left anyway, doesn't matter to me."

Han Xiao did not mind it.

Although he had killed all the God Embodiments, he could neither penetrate the church's National Treasure nor eliminate the fake Mechanical Deity, and Wuornos could not threaten his life either.

Conservatively, he could still fight Wuornos for half a month or so without resting.

"If that's the case, we'll call it here," Wuornos said softly.

"You think you can make the call?" Han Xiao curled his lips.

Wuornos glanced at him and softly giggled. His enormous body shrank back to his original size, and he opened the public channel.

"I'm no match for you. I admit my loss."

Han Xiao was stunned. He did not expect Wuornos to do this.

Admitting loss in front of the public went against the direct Beyond Grade As' goal of fighting for the three Universal Civilizations. Plus, no one showed any signs of defeat at this point; it was a tie at most. Why did he admit defeat?

Wuornos snapped his finger. The fake Mechanical Deity suddenly stopped and then exploded from the inside. He got rid of this God Embodiment on the spot.

Han Xiao frowned, raised his hand, and made the mechanical army stop attacking.

"…What are you doing?"

Wuornos disconnected from the public channel, looked at Han Xiao with a meaningful expression, and said, "Black Star, you're the most talented Super to have ever existed. You have the highest possibility of opening the gate to that next territory. Like I said in the beginning, I don't want to be your enemy."

"What is the meaning of this? Aren't you afraid of the Arcane Church having problems with you because you admitted your loss in front of the public?" Han Xiao frowned even harder.

"I've already done what I can. As for my goal… maybe you'll find out one day."

Wuornos gave him a strange smile, turned around, and flew toward the three Universal Civilizations' fleet.

Han Xiao made the mechanical army open a path and did not stop him. He silently stared at Wuornos' shrinking back view and realized that he had no understanding of Wuornos' personality and mindset.

In Han Xiao's previous life, both Dark Lord and Oulou died in the World Tree War; only Wuornos never even participated in it. Han Xiao would never believe for a second that the Arcane Church did not give him any orders. He had no way of knowing what this guy was really thinking.

… Never mind, I can't guess what he's thinking. I got the mission reward, anyway.

Han Xiao exhaled, opened the interface, and looked at it with a satisfied smile.

The Beyond Grade A Challenge Mission for Wuornos was shown as 'completed'.

He retrieved the mechanical army, deactivated the Mechanical Deity, sat on a new Divine Mechanical Throne, looked at the three Universal Civilizations' fleet, and said in the public channel, "Who's next?"

As he said that, the entire channel went dead silent.

As soon as Wuornos returned to the main ship, the many direct Beyond Grade A surrounded him with rather hostile looks.

"How could you admit loss publicly‽" Clotti questioned loudly.

"I couldn't win, so of course, I admitted my loss," Wuornos replied casually.

"You think we're all blind?" Verena said with an angry tone. "You showed no signs of defeat at all. You could've totally fought Black Star for much longer!"

Wuornos glanced at her and coldly said, "Then what? Keep fighting like this till the end of the warning period? I seem to recall I said I was going to fight Black Star alone, but you guys were going to ignore my request and were planning to fight him together, weren't you?"

Hearing this, they immediately did not know what to say.

"I can guess what you guys are planning to do with my eyes closed."

Seeing this, Wuornos shook his head, pushed his way through the crowd, and left.

He did not want to participate in the battle to begin with. Originally, he wanted to watch till the end. However, the church had given him an absolute order, and he had no choice but to fight.

However, Wuornos did not plan to defeat Black Star. What he really wanted was to see and experience Black Star's true strength, do his best to fight him to the extent that it was enough to give the church some results.

He was not lying about respecting Black Star, but he did not admit loss because of that. It was because of another reason.

Wuornos did not want to stop the three Universal Civilizations and the Beyond Grade A Association from starting a war; he wished to see it happen instead!

This was his core motive!

For many years, Wuornos had been stuck at an invisible ceiling. He realized that no matter what, his strength could barely grow anymore. It was as if there was some kind of higher power that prevented him from stepping into that higher territory of power.

He believed that only competition and pressure could breed the strong. Back during the exploration era, Supers slaughtered each other every second. Only then were the Beyond Grade As born. When the first Primordial One appeared, like a signal, more and more Beyond Grade As appeared one after another.

From the way he looked at it, the evolution of individual greatness might require an extremely talented pioneer to break that ceiling. Only then would the others be able to follow and enjoy the benefits.

This was how Black Star, whose growth rate broke every record, had entered his sights. Black Star was the person who had the highest possibility of becoming that pioneer in his eyes.

Wuornos did not like the peaceful atmosphere of the Beyond Grade A Association; he liked to see Beyond Grade As fight everyday more, breeding stronger individuals. Hence, the three Universal Civilizations targeting the association matched with his goal.

In this respect, Wuornos had the same fanaticism as EsGod, only he took a different path. Compared to EsGod's selfish style, Wuornos hoped to see the entire universe's strong individuals working hard.

After all, given the mechanics of his ability, the stronger individuals there were in the universe, the stronger his peak strength would be.

All kinds of thoughts flashed past his thoughts, Wuornos closed his eyes and thought, I'll give you this reputation today. Let me see how far you can go.

At the same time, the image of Wuornos admitting loss was broadcast to countless people.

At this moment, the hope that had just been rekindled was completely extinguished.

All the galactic residents who were hoping to see Black Star defeated collapsed onto their seats and looked hopeless.

Not a single person in the entire three Universal Civilizations could defeat Black Star. Even by shamelessly fighting him in groups, they still lost.

Embarrassing!

Before long, the countless galactic residents turned from pessimistic to nervous. They knew that today was the last day of the warning period given by the three Universal Civilizations. If neither side decided to take a step back, a war was most likely going to break out!

Seeing that there was no hope, many galactic residents suddenly stopped worrying. They started to vent their rage born from powerlessness and fear online, as well as the hatred toward Black Star for not 'losing like they wanted'.

Suddenly, support for the three Universal Civilizations grew tremendously once again. No longer were they hoping to stop the war; they went in the complete opposite direction, almost supportive of starting a war. They only had one core reason… for the three Universal Civilizations to crush the Beyond Grade A Association and clear the unstable factor of the galactic society!

Chapter 1308: Change

The loss of hope, increase of fear and panic were always accompanied by rage. Wuornos' act of admitting defeat caused public opinion to explode.

They had been looking forward to the three Universal Civilizations sending someone to break Black Star's arrogance. However, reality shattered their illusion. No one could defeat Black Star. The many galactic residents were both afraid and angry, then their humiliation turned into rage.

Okay, you're strong as a person, no one in the three Universal Civilizations can match up to you. But we still have fleets; we still have armies! I don't believe we can't deal with you!

Since the three Universal Civilizations had lost in terms of individual power, tons of galactic residents turned to believe in the three Universal Civilizations' collective strength. They found a new excuse to convince themselves and took it as a new source of confidence.

It was already the last day of the warning period. The public opinion had become extreme in supporting the three Universal Civilizations to wipe out the association.

"The Beyond Grade A Association is nothing but a civilian organization. How dare they fight with the three Universal Civilizations? It's clearly a criminal act. Think about it, the government wants to control you, and if you don't obey, isn't that violating the law? What, just because you founded a civilian organization, you can ignore the law? What makes you think you can do that? Just because you are strong‽"

"All things aside, the Beyond Grade As have always been unstable factors. They enjoy the privileges but don't take the laws of the galaxy seriously. They should either all be monitored by civilizations or killed! That way, they won't endanger society; today will be a lesson!"

"Hehe, Beyond Grade As are just representatives of the Supers. All Supers should be monitored and controlled; only then can order be maintained. Just think about how many crimes are related to the Supers. Without them, society would be a much better place!"

Ever since the appearance of the Sanctum Revival, the three Universal Civilizations had been guiding the public opinion and deliberately inciting the conflicting emotions between the ordinary people and the Supers. This had lasted for more than a year. These suppressed emotions kept getting tighter. At this turning point, the dissatisfaction the tons of civilians had toward the Supers finally erupted.

Countless galactic residents vented their rage without restrain, hoping all the Beyond Grade As and Super would just die.

Although this was very extreme, it was the true feelings of some galactic residents. Their genes dictated the fact that they would be ordinary their entire life, which was more depressing and impossible to cross than the difference between the rich and the poor. Almost all of them had a certain amount of hatred and frustration toward their destiny. When given the chance, most people would not mind expressing their hatred toward Supers.

However, the raging comments online meant absolutely nothing to Han Xiao; it had zero impact on what he was going to do.

Han Xiao sat in the middle of the battlefield and looked at the three Universal Civilizations' joint fleet. After Wuornos admitted his defeat, the other direct members seemed to have gone silent. Shockingly, they did not meaninglessly fight him again on this last day of the warning period.

"Looks like they've finally got a grip of the situation."

Han Xiao let out a deep breath.

All things considered, this was quite a successful decision. After keeping a low profile for many years, he had shocked the world once again and showed the universe his overwhelming strength, not only giving the association members confidence but also affecting the enemies' morale.

At this time, the mechanical suit's communicator rang. It was a call from Manison.

"… Your growth always exceeds my expectations."

Manison felt complicated. He was shocked by Han Xiao's strength and could not help but feel sour.

"It's alright, nothing extraordinary." Han Xiao took a humble approach.

Uh huh, still as shameless as always.

Manison was speechless for a moment. He then adjusted his emotions and said curiously, "Your Mechanical Deity is a little different. Is it new technology? There seem to be signs of the Felon technology in it."

"Uh huh, I did use some of the Felon technology." Han Xiao nodded and admitted it.

Manison fell silent.

Ah, another trump card got stolen by Black Star…

My heart hurts!

He wanted to get angry, but to his complete despair, he realized he was used to his abilities being stolen…

Taking a deep breath, Manison stabilized his mood and said with a low voice, "What's the principle of this technology? Can you share it with me?"

"Sure, I can, but you won't be able to learn it…" Han Xiao shrugged. "This technology was tailor made for me. You need to have an extremely strong physique to learn it, but you're too fragile."

"…"

Isn't it normal for Mechanics to have a fragile body? You're the only exception.

Manison pressed on his heart, calmed himself down, and did not want to continue discussing this subject.

He then changed the topic and said with a serious tone, "Today is the last day of the warning period. I'm ready for a war. How are things on your side?"

Han Xiao nodded. "The association's members are already stationed at the key strategic areas of the various Star Fields. Some people might have already started making moves."

"War is a shortcut toward peace. After today, let's hope the generations will extend in our hands." Manison sighed.

Han Xiao curled his lips.

After a few words, Manison was about to hang up the communication when he suddenly thought of something.

"Erm… my spear broke, but the other Universal Treasures I lent to you didn't. You put them all away. When will you be returning them to me?"

"Hey, come on, what's our relationship? Would I just take your Universal Treasure like that? What kind of person do you think I am?" Han Xiao complained.

Manison snorted instantly.

You don't do anything that's related to being a person, yet you ask me what kind of person you are?

You're not a person at all!

"Just tell me when you'll return them."

"When I'm done… ahem, after the three Universal Civilizations' fleet retreats, I'll give them back to you when I have the time."

Excuse me, you were going to say you'll return them after you're done studying them, weren't you!

Manison snorted and turned off the communication.

His temper was already depleted by Han Xiao, and after knowing him for so many years, he was mentally prepared for this long ago.

Just what I expected from you, Black Star!

Han Xiao turned off the communication. Seeing that the three Universal Civilizations were not making any moves, he opened the interface and looked at the mission reward.

Fighting the direct members of the three Universal Civilizations did not trigger individual Challenge Missions but instead triggered the sparring kind of mission like when he sparred with Joey and his friends. The mission reward relied on how long he lasted. The highest Mission Rating gave seven Character Summon Cards and five chances to draw abilities or talents from a target of his choice.

As for the duel with Wuornos, it triggered the regular Beyond Grade A Challenge Mission. The rewards were one Character Summon Card and one chance to draw his ability or talent.

"Looks like I won in the end."

Han Xiao felt much better.

With a war around the corner, he was quite tempted. However, after thinking about it, he still suppressed his impulses.

His goal of intimidating the enemies was already achieved. If a war were to break out the next day and the three Universal Civilizations' joint fleet attacked, all the direct members would most likely strike too. Of course, Han Xiao would not be facing them alone. Therefore, he was not in a hurry to accept the mission rewards.

"If only I could make the three Universal Civilizations take a step back…"

Han Xiao shook his head and thought of an idea he had some time ago. He caressed the communicator, hesitating on whether or not to call the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations and tell them about the World Tree Civilization, shifting the conflict away.

The most ideal situation would, of course, be the three Universal Civilizations believing what he said, temporarily lowering their hostility and working together with him against the external enemy. Although this would cause the World Tree war to arrive in advance, it would save a huge portion of the explored universe's strength… However, given the current uptight situation and the relationship between the two sides, he felt there was an extremely low chance the three Universal Civilizations' leaders would believe him. They would most likely think it was an excuse to avoid admitting defeat or a made-up reason for both sides to take a step back.

If he could not convince the three Universal Civilizations' leaders, a war would still break out, and the three Universal Civilizations would very likely secretly investigate the authenticity of the information about the World Tree Civilization. Not only would the explored universe lose a ton of military power, but the World Tree war would still arrive in advance, meaning the three Universal Civilizations would have close to no time to recover before facing such a powerful enemy. Therefore, Han Xiao was hesitating. It was almost impossible for him to predict the butterfly effects this move might cause.

"Sigh, tough."

…

In the online chat room of the Beyond Grade A Association, the remote projections of a group of Beyond Grade As gathered. Shock still remained on some of their faces.

"Even Wuornos can't defeat Black Star… It's hard to believe how strong he's become after not showing his strength for just a few decades."

"Black Star is really an unbelievable guy. I thought he would lose this time. Who could've predicted he would actually hold on?"

"Fighting the three Universal Civilizations alone, suppressing all direct members. I would never have believed this is true if I didn't see it with my own eyes!"

The many Beyond Grade As discussed excitedly.

They had watched the broadcast of Black Star fighting the three Universal Civilizations' direct members alone from the start to the end, feeling more astonished each day. After Wuornos admitted his defeat, all of them were dumbfounded.

Even Wuornos, who was recognized by all as the strongest cheater, could not defeat Han Xiao, astounded the entire Beyond Grade A circle. In their eyes, this crown no longer belonged to Wuornos and was shifted to Black Star's head… Not only was he the president of the Beyond Grade A Association, but he was also undoubtedly the strongest Beyond Grade A, which made his position as the president even more deserved.

"Seeing how strong Black Star is, I'm less concerned." Kasuyi relaxed.

Many people nodded and smiled.

The three Universal Civilizations had tons of trump cards. Many association members had been worried that something might happen to Black Star, which would lead to no one being able to use the Sanctum Revival, and that would be very unfortunate for them. Seeing that Black Star was unbelievably strong, many people were relieved.

Kasuyi looked around, wiped the smile off his face, and said with a serious tone, "Alright, don't get too relaxed. Today is the last day of the warning period. Everyone, be ready and standby. Wait for Black Star to teleport us over for war!"

Hearing this, the expressions of the others also became serious.

Sun Hunter pulled the bolt of his gun, snorted, and said, "Finally, my big cannon is thirsting for blood!"

…

In the three Universal Civilizations' joint conference room, Marbruce, Louis, and the church pope looked at the screen. Their expressions were furious.

Marbruce hit the table heavily and said with a tone filled with dissatisfaction, "Ridiculous! All of our direct members can't even take down one Black Star. How are we going to deal with the other Beyond Grade As?"

"Their loss has embarrassed the entire civilization! We've become stepping stones for Black Star's reputation!" Louis was furious.

"We can't really blame them. Black Star is illogically strong."

The pope frowned tightly. He was very unhappy with Wuornos' act of admitting defeat, but what was done was done. There was no use in blaming Wuornos now. He was a little bit regretful of forcing Wuornos to leave the Temple of Ten Thousand Gods to participate in this.

Looking at Black Star, who sat in the middle of two sides, the three of them suddenly felt powerless, angry, and frustrated.

In terms of individual strength, they really had no ways of dealing with Black Star. Even the three of them were out of ideas.

"The only way to deal with him now is through armies and war weapons…" Louis looked at the other two with a serious expression. "Once the warning period ends, we'll start a war instantly. Are you two absolutely sure about this?"

"This day would've come sooner or later. I only regret how late we made up our minds to do this. We've let the Beyond Grade As roam and grow freely for too long. That's how they've turned into such huge threats," the pope said slowly.

"We're already here. There's no way we're going to go back on our word." Marbruce nodded.

"Okay. Pass the order down to your armies at the various locations to execute as planned…"

Before he finished, the sound of an urgent alert from a communicator suddenly rang in the room.

Louis stopped and looked at Marbruce. It came from his communicator.

Marbruce took out the communicator and looked at it. It was an urgent report from the dynasty's main artificial intelligence, Heroic Soul.

The reports of the various departments were all analyzed by the main artificial intelligence, then given to different departments to take care of depending on their priority level. Given how the main artificial intelligence sent this to him even during his meeting with the other two leaders, it meant that from the main artificial intelligence's judgement, this message was extremely urgent.

"What report is th… hmm?"

Marbruce's expression changed drastically the moment he saw the title of the report. He then finished reading it in silence.

He pondered for about half a minute before turning to look at the other two.

"You guys might need to take a look at this…"

…

On this last day of the warning period, the timer passed in an extremely uneasy atmosphere. Seconds felt like years to all the soldiers present and countless galactic residents watching the broadcast.

As the last moment of the warning period got closer, the fleets of the three Universal Civilizations and the Beyond Grade A Association started to fidget. The atmosphere kept getting more and more intense.

In the Black Star Army's fleet, the tons of army players were filled with anticipation.

"It's here! It's here! War!"

"I've seen more than enough cutscenes. The main storyline is finally about to begin."

"For the army!"

The army players could not wait for the two sides to start fighting.

One reason was that they loved to see a chaotic world and hoped to participate in the main storyline. Another reason was that many people saw the comments online too and realized that there were so many people insulting, condemning, and scolding them, the 'Immortals'.

Of course, many players were quite enraged by that.

However, at the same time, they also had a deeper understanding of the 'Calamity of the Supers' mission name, as well as the conflict between the ordinary and the Supers.

As Supers, the players who had a lot of interest in the storyline were exhilarated. They felt like the curtains of the new era were unfolding right in front of their eyes.

"All crews, prepare for combat!"

The voice of the commander spread in the battleships. Countless warriors tightened their body and looked at the clock.

In this apprehensive wait, time passed seconds by seconds as it got closer to the end of the warning period. The hearts of the soldiers of both sides and countless galactic residents were all at their throat.

In this extremely intense atmosphere, the three Universal Civilizations' joint fleet suddenly moved.

Without any warning, the entire joint fleet suddenly moved back, leaving the conflict area batch by batch.

This stunned the Beyond Grade A Association's armies and all the galactic residents. They were lost.

The warning period is almost here. Why did the three Universal Civilizations suddenly retreat? Plus, without saying anything?

Didn't they firmly say they'll never give in? Why did they go back on their word all of a sudden‽

On the quantum network, the comments calling for the three Universal Civilizations to wipe out the association suddenly went silent. As they realized that things did not go as they imagined, they suddenly did not know what to do.

Is it because Black Star defeated all direct Beyond Grade As single-handedly and the three Universal Civilizations are afraid?

It was difficult for them not to think this.

At the same time, a similar speculation also appeared in many people's minds.

"Could it be that the three Universal Civilizations only wanted to intimidate the association, scare them, and pressure them into compromising to begin with? And once they realized this method is useless against the association, they could not continue the show and retreated like a coward on the last day of the warning period that was claimed by themselves!"

Many galactic residents did not know what to say and felt very complicated.

We all supported you guys in wiping out the Beyond Grade A Association and defusing the source of the instability of the galactic society, yet you guys are afraid?

Although not starting a war was fortunate, many people felt embarrassed. Their all-out support for the three Universal Civilizations now felt like a slap to the face, by the three Universal Civilizations themselves.

Han Xiao was also confused by the three Universal Civilizations' neat retreat too.

After a bit of hesitation, Han Xiao actively called the dynasty ruler. However, it was not picked up, which made him wonder even more.

"They're retreating just like that? Doesn't fit them at all. The three Universal Civilizations shouldn't be this cowardly… or did something happen?"

…

A few days ago, at the dynasty's Science Institute, the team members of the wormhole analysis team all gathered in the activity room, watching the fight between Black Star and Clotti's group on the screen with worried expressions.

In the past few days, they had stopped all projects on hand and focused on the developments of this event. This was closely related to their everyday life.

In the crowd, someone softly whispered, "Looks like a war is going to break out…"

Sighs sounded in the room one after another, filled with worries.

All the researchers present opposed starting a war. One reason was that they were worried that their project would be stopped once again when the war started, meaning they would have nothing to do. Another was because as people with virtue, they intuitively opposed wars.

"Only if someone could stop this war…" someone softly mumbled.

Hearing this, the project director's eyes suddenly gleamed. He clenched his teeth, turned around, walked out of the activity room, and returned to his office.

He searched through the database and brought up a special wormhole detection report that he did not have time to submit lately due to how much attention he paid to the recent events.

"I hope this works…"

The project director swallowed his saliva and modified this report, changing the 'suspected existence of an unknown advanced civilization' included in the report conclusion into 'confirmed existence of an unknown Universal Civilization'.

After doing all this, the project director did not send it to the audit department but directly skipped this procedure and submitted it to the dynasty's main artificial intelligence's database. He knew that skipping the fixed procedures would definitely get him into trouble.

"No idea if this will work…" the project director mumbled with a worried expression.

In order to stop the possible universal war that might break out, he was willing to do whatever he could in his power.

He was not sure if this trick would work, but he felt that if everyone only watched and did nothing, no change would come.

Chapter 1309: A Gamble

The three Universal Civilizations' sudden retreat right before the warning period ended completely shocked the entire galactic civilization. Everyone was lost.

The comments supporting the war on the quantum network disappeared, and all kinds of sarcastic comments started to appear instead.

"Yo, weren't the three Universal Civilizations unshakably firm? What happened?"

"Tsk, looks like that's what the three Universal Civilizations are. Their dominance is only an act."

"Y'all still supporting the war? Why don't you take a look at how much the three Universal Civilizations care about you people?"

Public opinion shifted once again. Looking at these sarcastic comments, the tons of galactic residents were frustrated but had nothing to say.

These sarcastic comments came not just from some Supers who could finally vent their emotions but also from some organizations that were secretly inciting the public opinion. The Super Star Cluster Alliance had always been keeping a low profile, and once they saw the chance, they immediately jumped out to display their traditional skill, sh*t-stirring.

Compared to the galactic residents, the players were even more dumbfounded.

"Is that it?"

"I watched ten days of cutscenes, and now you're saying there won't be a war‽"

"What happened to full-out war‽ Coward!"

Under the fearful sights of the other crews, the many army players yelled, shouted, stomped the floor, and bashed their chests, hating the fact that a war did not break out.

The three Universal Civilizations' joint fleet turned into closely packed streams of hyperdrive lights and retreated hastily. Seeing this, Manison flew out from the fleet, stood beside Han Xiao, and watched the three Universal Civilizations leave.

"That's weird. They just left without saying anything?" Manison was confused.

Han Xiao caressed his chin and mumbled, "There's definitely something wrong with this. The three Universal Civilizations did not bring this many forces here just to put up a show to intimidate us. It's absolutely certain they were really prepared to start a war. However, they are now retreating even when it means they're going back on their word, knowing this will cause their reputation to plummet. Something huge must have happened."

"Hmm… or maybe they really got scared?" Manison said, the shook his head, knowing clearly that the possibility of that was extremely low. "Maybe the three Universal Civilizations thought it through and believe that having an all-out war with the association has more cons than pros? So, they changed their mind… Does that mean the strategic goal of leaking the virus technology worked out?"

"No idea. The three Universal Civilizations should give a response to the galactic society, so let's just see what they have to say. I'll try to find out some inside information too… or maybe the three Universal Civilizations will actively contact me after some time."

Han Xiao's eyes flashed.

Hearing this, Manison turned to look at him.

"Do you know something?"

"Just some guesses that can't be confirmed without enough information."

Han Xiao shook his head.

At this time, the communicator rang. It was from the communication channel of the Beyond Grade A Association.

"Black Star, what's going on over there? Do the three Universal Civilizations not want to fight anymore?"

"What do they mean by this?"

"Are we going to continue our plan?"

As soon as the call was picked up, the many Beyond Grade As started questioning continuously.

The many association members were confused too. They were all mentally prepared for a bloody war, yet their opponents fled at the last second. It felt like they had bought a sports car and were just about to test it when they saw a cop car beside them, leaving them no choice but to suppress their urges.

"Standby for now. We'll have to see what the three Universal Civilizations are going to do next. But don't let your guard down. It might be a trick. If they really are going to attack, they might use the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device to launch surprise attacks on key strategic locations directly…"

Han Xiao said a few words, telling the association members to stay on alert, and then hung up the call.

The three Universal Civilizations surrounding the Mechanical Race territory was only a signal; attacking this place was actually not useful at all except for declaring war. He still could not find out what the three Universal Civilizations were planning at this point… Retreating on the surface but charging back later using the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device was possible, so he had to consider it.

Seeing that Han Xiao had finished the call, Manison said, "What now? The three Universal Civilizations retreated, so should we dismiss the troops here?"

Han Xiao thought about it but shook his head. "Don't dismiss them. Shrink the defense circle, and continue to guard the Mechanical Race territory. Only dismiss the troops when the three Universal Civilizations' joint fleet is confirmed to have left this Star Cluster. I need to make a trip back."

Manison nodded, flew back to the main ship, and sent down the orders.

Han Xiao changed into the King and disappeared.

Swoosh!

The next second, he returned to a secret army base. This was a hideout for some officers who were not participating in battles.

Some army officers and the many members of the Floating Dragon sat in the room, including Ames who was there in case of anything. They were all watching the news broadcast.

Seeing Han Xiao suddenly appearing, the sights of the various officers all focused on him. The admiration and respect in their eyes were not just a little bit stronger than before; it was as if they were looking at a god.

Ames crossed her legs, leaned slightly forward, and pressed her elbows on her knees and her hands under her chin. She tilted her head slightly, letting her soft hair down, and said with a faint smile and a joking tone, "You've been very manly the past few days."

"Don't you know best how manly I am?" Han Xiao raised his brow.

Ames smiled and said, "You should have a lot of things to deal with. What are you doing here?"

"Just came to take a look and make sure everything's okay here."

Han Xiao casually made up an excuse, looked around at the officers, and accurately stopped at Feidin. He immediately smiled, took a few big steps forward, and rubbed him.

With a speechless face, Feidin did not resist at all.

Seeing this, Aesop coughed and said, "You defeated all the three Universal Civilizations' direct members, and even Wuornos could not defeat you. So, they definitely gave up fighting you with individual strength. I don't know if this is part of the reason the three Universal Civilizations retreated, but they don't seem to want to start a war anymore. What are you going to do next?"

Hearing this, Han Xiao said with a serious tone, "I'll first have to figure out what happened. Anyway, don't celebrate yet. If I guessed correctly, things might get even worse from now on."

…

The ten-day confrontation between the three Universal Civilizations and the association attracted the attention of the entire universe, but not many expected it to end as it did. After the joint fleet retreated, the three Universal Civilizations went completely silent. Not only did they pull back some of the armies they had sent earlier, but they did not even publicly explain the reason for their retreat yet. The public opinions got more and more intense; all kinds of speculations surfaced one after another.

Originally, they all thought this would be the fuse of an all-out war. However, the three Universal Civilizations extinguished this war at the last second, so this confrontation elevated Black Star's reputation. He was now firmly recognized as the strongest Beyond Grade A. If one had to define who the winner was, only Black Star could be considered.

Some were glad that a war did not break out; some furiously condemned the three Universal Civilizations for being cowards; some laughed at the galactic residents for thinking their opinions actually mattered. There were all kinds of opinions, but they all shared one thing in common. They were all curious as to what made the three Universal Civilizations choose to take a step back.

Due to the three Universal Civilizations' silence, no one knew the answer to this question. Even the Beyond Grade A Association did not make an announcement; they were watching silently too. Countless people were intrigued.

…

The three Universal Civilizations' Joint Conference Room…

"… We've already checked the authenticity of this report multiple times. Through the wormhole detection needles, we did indeed discover signs of activity of an unknown civilization. The data itself is completely legit. Only the conclusion is not fully definitive."

The remote projection of the dynasty's upper echelon in charge of the scientific research stood in front of the three leaders and reported with a serious tone.

"So, we can't confirm that this unknown civilization is a Universal Civilization for the time being?" Marbruce confirmed.

"That… is right. However, they definitely are an advanced civilization. The extensive data collected by the multifunctional spacetime detection needles we have been frequently sending over proves their advanced technology level."

"… Got it. Continue to collect data while keeping yourselves hidden. I need to know the details of this civilization."

After a few more words, Marbruce ended the communication. The other two civilizations' leaders and him were the only ones left in the room.

"Looks like our decision to retreat back then was correct," the pope said with a deep voice.

"Hmm, or we'd be beleaguered by now. This report came way too timely," Louis added, a little relieved.

On the last day of the confrontation, they were originally going to strike as planned, but this wormhole report from the dynasty's Science Institute had shaken their decision.

The three Universal Civilizations had always been exploring the unknown areas of the universe; this wormhole report claimed to have discovered an unknown Universal Civilization, which would be an enormous threat if true. In this respect, the three Universal Civilizations were very experienced. Once an outside enemy appeared, they had to carefully deal with internal conflicts. This was clearly not a good time to deal with the unbalance of individual strength.

Back then, there was not a lot of time for the three of them to discuss matters. In the end, they decided not to take the risk. They stopped their plan and chose to step back from the association. In turn, they spent tons of resources authenticating this wormhole report. They knew their priorities.

This set of wormhole data was one of the things EsGod had left behind. As EsGod had been sealed for many years, it had become an unimportant project long ago. However, with this astonishing discovery, it became a top-priority project. Its progress was directly monitored by the three Universal Civilizations' leaders.

The final results were, although the conclusion of this wormhole report was slightly exaggerated, the data was completely legit. An unknown advanced civilization was indeed discovered, only it was not confirmed to be a Universal Civilization.

If it was true… this would be a priceless 'exaggerated' conclusion.

Marbruce knocked the table and slowly said, "The priority now is to collect information about this unknown civilization and confirm their strength, societal structure, attitude toward outsiders, and so on. Everything else can be put aside for now."

Louis and the pope nodded.

The three Universal Civilizations had a strategic plan for this kind of situation. No way were they going to directly make contact or start a war. Once they discovered an advanced civilization in the unexplored universe, their top priority was to carefully collect intelligence without exposing their presence. Afterward, only then would they choose different approaches depending on the strength, culture, and many other factors of this civilization.

Although the explored universe had entered the galactic society era, from the entire unexplored universe's perspective, it was still in the 'exploration era'. Discovering the enemy before being discovered was an enormous advantage, so of course, they were going to use it to its fullest potential.

"Don't forget to carry out measures against all possible scenarios before exploring further," the pope said.

"I know." Marbruce nodded.

The measures the three of them were speaking of were mainly preparing for war, as well as preparing to send strategic annihilation weapons toward this unknown civilization's territory through the wormhole. In extreme situations, they would not mind directly destroying its territory, turning it into a desolate universe belt, wiping out all lives of this unknown civilization, not showing any mercy at all.

"This matter is extremely important. If a war really breaks out, the Beyond Grade A Association will be a powerful force too. Should we tell them about it now?"

Louis brought up this sensitive question and asked the two of them for their opinions.

Though the existence of Beyond Grade As threatened their rule, they were also a powerful force against outside enemies. Since the situation had changed, their mindset changed too. There was no such thing as an eternal enemy in their eyes.

The pope pondered for a moment, waved, and expressed his opinion.

"Let's just be cautious. We haven't figured out the state of this unknown civilization; there's no need to tell it to the association now. Think about it. If we can coexist with this unknown civilization that happens to be a Universal Civilization, once they take in the galactic society system, the association will have another choice of becoming allies with them, which will impact the structure of the galaxy… We can't guarantee the association's loyalty, so we should keep it a secret for the time being."

"Make sense." Marbruce nodded. "Let's not announce this publicly for now. We'll secretly investigate the situation, then consider whether or not to publicize it depending on the situation. It won't be too late to tell the association about it when we need their help."

From the way the three of them looked at it, there was clearly no need to immediately tell the other organizations about this for now. They were all unstable factors, and who knew what trouble they would cause?

"Since that's the case, let's put aside our conflict with the association first," Louis suggested. "Calm these Beyond Grade As down, don't let them cause any trouble, and make peace with them temporarily… This is their goal too. Find a reason to agree with their goal, relay our intention of stopping the conflict, and make the association think we decided to compromise."

The other two nodded in agreement. Although they could not deal with the association, as long as the Beyond Grade As did not cause troubles, it was enough for them.

At this time, Marbruce suddenly thought of something.

If I remember correctly, Black Star has this set of wormhole data left behind by EsGod too. I seem to recall he even specifically asked the dynasty about our progress of studying this set of data…

Now that I think about it, does Black Star know something?

As this thought flashed past his mind, Marbruce shook his head.

He felt the possibility of this was very limited. Compared to asking Black Star, it was better to obtain intelligence through investigating themselves.

Furthermore, they had just agreed not to leak this secret to the outside world. Therefore, even if Black Star might know something about it, he did not plan to ask him. After all, Black Star was the leader of the organization opposing the three Universal Civilizations for now, so they were no longer allies.

…

In a certain Black Star Army base, an enormous star map hovered in the room. On it were marks of the movements of the three Universal Civilizations' various armies, drawing out many arrows.

Han Xiao stood before the star map and carefully looked at it.

Quite some days had already passed since the three Universal Civilizations retreated from the Mechanical Race territory. In the past few days, the three Universal Civilizations' armies' movements had been very abnormal. Originally, they were stationed at the various Star Fields, prepared to deal with the Beyond Grade A Association at any time. However, now, they were all recalled back to the Central Galaxy, as if they had no intention of starting a war at all.

If that was all, he would not be so troubled. The weirdest part was that the three Universal Civilizations had remained silent all this time, neither making any announcement nor contacting him to relay their intentions. It was extremely odd, as if they had no time to deal with him.

He had been trying to find out what was going on behind the curtains. However, the three Universal Civilizations kept their secret extremely well hidden this time, and he did not discover anything at all.

"Did I really guess right?" Han Xiao murmured.

What could make the three Universal Civilizations change their decision last minute?

At this point in time, there were not many possible scenarios. However, the butterfly effects he caused had changed countless things. One of them was that EsGod had given the dynasty the key toward the World Tree Civilization's territory long ago, which was an unstable factor.

From his perspective, the most likely situation was that the three Universal Civilizations had discovered the World Tree Civilization. Due to the existence of an external enemy, the three Universal Civilizations retreated so quickly without any warning.

"If that's really the case, the three Universal Civilizations will definitely investigate the wormhole thoroughly. They might tell me about it, but they might also keep it a secret… Given the three Universal Civilizations' way of doing things and my current position, the latter is more likely."

Han Xiao frowned, bit his nails, and did not feel good about this.

If the three Universal Civilizations chose to keep it a secret and secretly explored further, given how ignorant they were about the World Tree Civilization, the risk of them being exposed was extremely high.

If making contact was already unavoidably brought forward, him continuing to hide the information about the World Tree would increase the risks. Now might be the best time to share what he knew.

However, he might have guessed wrong. If the three Universal Civilizations retreated not because they discovered the World Tree Civilization, it would be horrible.

"So, this is a gamble. It all depends on whether I'm willing to take the risk…"

Han Xiao's expression changed rapidly.

Di di di…

At this time, his communicator rang.

He took it out. It was surprisingly a call from a dynasty emissary.

"Greetings, Your Excellency Black Star."

As soon as the communication was picked up, the dynasty emissary nodded in a friendly way, looking quite respectful.

Han Xiao sized him up and cut to the chase. "Finally decided to explain what you guys did?"

"That's humorous of you. I'm here to negotiate with you on behalf of the three Universal Civilizations this time. We are willing to accept the association's proposal. We will allow you to restrain the Virtual Mutiny Virus technology on your own…"

The dynasty emissary said a ton of things. At its core, what he meant was that the three Universal Civilizations were willing to take a step back. They no longer required Manison to submit the virus technology and trusted the association's integrity, allowing it to control this kind of high-risk technology. In short, they would no longer interfere.

"Oh?" Han Xiao raised his brows. "Since you guys have accepted that the association's promise is effective, you're recognizing the association's correctness. What about the trade laws against the association?"

"They won't be removed for the time being, but it can be discussed." The dynasty emissary smiled.

Looking at his emotionless smile, Han Xiao acutely sensed the strange attitude of the three Universal Civilizations. He was filled with conflict.

His intuition felt stronger. He felt he might really have guessed the truth.

After a few seconds of silence, Han Xiao took a deep breath.

I'll take the bet!

As he made up his mind, Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and slowly said, "I've received your message. Please relay this message to Marbruce."

"What is it?"

"… From how strangely you guys are acting, it looks like you guys have finally deciphered the wormhole data left by EsGod, right?"

Chapter 1310: Truth

One hour later, Han Xiao's remote projection entered the three Universal Civilizations' leaders' joint conference room, and he immediately saw three old men staring dead at him with grave faces.

"Yo, you're all here."

Han Xiao was not in a hurry at all and greeted them casually. This was the first time he had been called into a meeting like this since the two sides' relationship reached the freezing point.

"Black Star! What the hell do you know!"

Marbruce was in no mood to chitchat at all and cut to the chase.

An hour ago, when the three of them were waiting for the dynasty emissary to report Black Star's stand toward the three Universal Civilizations' proposal of peace to see if they could calm the association down, to their absolute dismay, what they received was the news that Black Star shockingly immediately called out the secret of the wormhole.

The three of them were all completely dumbfounded.

Where did Black Star find out about the fact that they had decrypted the secret of the wormhole? Who leaked the information? Was there a mole?

If not, how did Black Star find out? Did he know about the wormhole data's secret all along?

There were so many unanswered questions!

Marbruce, Louis, and the pope were anxious.

Since Black Star had specifically told the emissary to relay this message to them, it did not matter how he got such surprising information. The matter was of the utmost importance and had to be taken extremely seriously. The three of them held an emergency meeting where they decided to speak to Black Star, hence this meeting.

"I know lots of things."

Han Xiao looked around and deliberately gave them a meaningful expression while feeling relaxed inside.

He was also unsure what was going on, so he did not directly reveal the World Tree Civilization's name but instead pointed it out ambiguously.

Nonetheless, since he had been called to this meeting, Han Xiao knew he had won the bet and indeed guessed the truth. He was glad he did not make things worse.

"You mentioned the wormhole data left by EsGod. How much do you know about it?" Louis asked with a deep voice.

Han Xiao arranged his emotions, glanced at him, and said casually, "You guys discovered a civilization on the other side of the wormhole, right?"

The three of them exchanged looks with extremely serious expressions.

Marbruce frowned and asked, "Where did you get that information from?"

"I know what you guys want to ask me…" Han Xiao raised his brows. "No, I didn't steal your internal information."

Hearing this, their expressions became even more grave.

By saying that his source of information did not come from the three Universal Civilizations, Black Star was basically saying that he had uncovered the wormhole's secret long ago and had information about it the three of them did not possess.

Marbruce took a deep breath, put down his pride, and said solemnly with even a slightly respectful tone, "I'm sure you know the nature of this matter. We hope you can tell us the truth. This is absolutely crucial to the entire universe."

"Sure." Han Xiao nodded. Since this had happened, there was no point hiding what he knew. It was time to tell them the truth. He had to make sure that the three Universal Civilizations were aware of how dangerous the World Tree was.

"… This wormhole leads to the territory of a civilization called the World Tree Civilization. That's an extremely powerful civilization that loves war and expanding their territory. Decades ago, due to some reasons, EsGod sent a doppelganger to attack me, which led to his doppelganger falling into a wormhole and coincidentally discovering the World Tree Civilization. After that, EsGod sent his men to steal this wormhole data to figure out a way to pinpoint the World Tree Civilization's coordinates. Some things happened, and I became the only person who knows about this…"

Of course, Han Xiao hid the fact that some of this information came from his previous life and described the matter in another way, emphasizing how powerful the World Tree Civilization was. He basically shared almost everything he knew about the World Tree Civilization.

The three of them listened till the end with frowns on their faces, full of doubts.

Marbruce asked, "Did EsGod tell you all this? Putting aside why EsGod told only you about this, why do you know this much about the World Tree Civilization? This is far from what EsGod could've found out in one trip."

"I understand your doubts." Han Xiao nodded. This was not a matter to be taken lightly. If he made EsGod the reason for everything, all they had to do was question EsGod, and his lies would be discovered.

Without an incomparably solid source of information, there was no way the three Universal Civilizations were going to believe all this.

However, he had come up with a reason long ago that just so happened to explain why he knew so much about the World Tree Civilization.

"Actually… I have something left behind by a certain civilization that was wiped out by the World Tree Civilization. It contains a ton of information. What I know about the World Tree Civilization mostly comes from that."

As he said that, Han Xiao summoned the remote projection of SWY-001 and displayed the information he had prepared beforehand on the screen.

The expressions on their faces changed as they hastily browsed the information. The more they looked at it, the more shocked they became.

SWY-001's memory module recorded the tragic state of the Karma Republic when it was being invaded as well as the World Tree Civilization's unique and extremely strong way of war. Furthermore, it also showed that the World Tree Civilization was a Universal Civilization that was almost impossible to coexist with. Everything proved that what Han Xiao said was true.

Without this big treasure, even if Han Xiao could explain the source of this information, it would not be convincing enough.

Man did this thing come at a good time… Han Xiao thought in his mind.

There was nothing he could say but… Damn, Feidin!

The three of them spent some time reading all the information, and shock still lingered in their eyes.

"Devouring everything in their way, the World Tree Civilization is really the enemy of all intelligent civilizations. To think there's such a hunter like this in the universe…" Louis mumbled. "Luckily, we sealed EsGod long ago. If he'd led the World Tree Civilization here…"

Suddenly, before he finished his sentence, his expression froze.

At this moment, Marbruce recalled that sealing EsGod up was something Black Star strongly proposed and made happen. The fact that they were still not discovered by the World Tree now was all thanks to Black Star.

Back then, Black Star insisted on sealing EsGod up no matter what. Was he already secretly trying to protect the explored universe from being invaded‽

Marbruce's heart skipped a beat. He looked up at Han Xiao and could not help but ask, "Was this the reason you insisted on asking us to capture EsGod back then?"

Han Xiao tutted and asked back, "Why else would I? You really think I had so much hatred against him that I had to kill him?"

Marbruce's expression changed slightly. He looked at Han Xiao and could not help but feel a bit of admiration and appreciation toward him. The doubt in his heart instantly lessened.

If not for Black Star, this galactic society would have already been invaded. Technically speaking, the entire universe owed him a favor.

However, Black Star did not share this at all and silently hid this honorable achievement, letting it collect dust in history. No one knew about this colossal contribution he made.

How noble!

Han Xiao's image immediately got taller in Marbruce's heart.

Suddenly, the pope said, "Black Star, since you knew about the threat of the World Tree Civilization and had all this information long ago, why didn't you share it till now?"

Han Xiao shook his head.

"I know you guys all too well. If you guys had found out there is a powerful unknown civilization in the unexplored universe, would you guys ignore its existence? Sharing it with you would only lead to making contact even earlier. It was best to keep this a secret. In fact, if not because you guys had made results studying the wormhole data, I wouldn't have said all this even now."

The three of them had nothing to say.

Indeed, even if they did not know about it, if they found out the threat of the World Tree, the three of them were fully certain there was absolutely no way they were going to simply ignore it. They would definitely want to strike first and attempt to take the World Tree Civilization by surprise; never would they have acted the same way they were now.

Attempting to find out more about the World Tree would mean they would be at risk of being exposed too. Despite that, based on their positions, striking first was a certainty. Otherwise, they would simply be relying on fate and waiting to be attacked.

Being aware of such a powerful enemy existing in the unknown universe would make the three of them sleepless, worrying about one day being discovered and invaded every second. That would be no way of living, so of course, actively erasing this threat was more in line with the three Universal Civilizations' needs.

If both sides were unaware of each other's existence, they could still coexist like two parallel lines. However, once one discovered the other, the two sides would rapidly collided

"I have to admit that makes sense…" Louis sighed. "But isn't that betting on the enemies not discovering us first too?"

Han Xiao shook his head and did not reply.

He was confident in this because he knew exactly when the World Tree would be invading, only there was no need to explain that. Plus, it would neither be easy to explain nor be convincing enough.

At this time, the pope frowned and said, "But how can we be certain that the information from this object is true and not made up?"

"Are you doubting me?" Han Xiao glanced at him.

"I'm just being careful. It's not personal." The pope waved his hand.

Louis thought about it and added, "Indeed, the source of your information is very convincing, but its authenticity is still unclear… We're not doubting you, but we can't fully trust this information. Although it looks very real, who knows if this information was made up in the first place? We can't just assume…"

"Black Star, we'll carefully refer to this information you have provided, but we'll still have to see the results of our reconnaissance," Marbruce said.

Damn, you three are troublesome!

Han Xiao curled his lips but was not surprised.

It was normal for the three Universal Civilizations to be careful from their perspective. After all, there was indeed the possibility of this information being made up, just like what happened to the Kunde Race. Who knew if this information might be 'bait' too?

Han Xiao caressed his chin and slowly said, "This civilization relic still has vital signs. It's only asleep. If we wake it up, we should be able to get more information."

He had a mission on him to awaken SWY-001, but he did not complete it all this time because he did not want to deal with the possible trouble. However, now that he was sure that the three Universal Civilizations had made contact with the World Tree in advance, he no longer minded waking up SWY-001. Instead, it might even be helpful to do it.

"Alright, I'll leave it to you then. This is very important… By the way, you'll help us, right?"

Marbruce nodded. He suddenly paused and realized that the association and them were still on opposite sides.

The other two realized this too and looked a little uncomfortable.

The situation had changed, and they needed the association now. However, not long ago, they were attempting to wipe the association out, yet now they were asking for their help. The three of them felt awkward and even slightly embarrassed.

However, the three of them only felt awkward for a few seconds before quickly adjusting their mood, looking at Han Xiao with passionate eyes.

Han Xiao glanced at the three of them and smiled.

"The World Tree Civilization can't coexist with us. We're all on the same boat here, so working together is the only choice."

"… It's great you can understand that."

The three of them felt relieved. They needed to unite all forces at this point, and they were really afraid the association might do something irrational.

Seeing that Black Star easily looked past their conflict, the three of them could not help but think back to their conflict with the association in the past years. They felt complicated.

Black Star had always been trying to reach a balance and peaceful coexistence; never did he trigger any conflict.

In the past, the three of them thought the association was delaying the time to accumulate more strength. However, in hindsight, the three of them shockingly realized there seemed to be another explanation to Black Star's actions… Was he trying to save the explored universe's forces?

Due to many reasons, the three of them kept oppressing and targeting the association, and Black Star had been trying to maintain a fragile balance. While the three of them were busy dealing with internal problems, Black Star was very likely making preparations against the external enemy, the World Tree Civilization.

Unfortunately, the leakage of the Virtual Mutiny Virus had led them to make up their minds on starting a full-blown war…

"We almost walked down a path with no return!"

Appalled, their backs were covered in cold sweat. They were glad.

Luckily, they stepped back at the last minute. If they had started a war, Black Star's efforts to maintain the explored universe's forces would have been wasted.

Having thought of this, the three of them looked at Han Xiao again with very complicated emotions in their eyes. There was shame and regret, as well as appreciation and admiration.

We misunderstood him…

Knowing Black Star's real motive, it was as if this was the first time they had met him.

Black Star's image became alive in their minds. It was as if the three of them saw the back of a man walking alone in the world, carrying heavy responsibilities no one knew about, attempting to defuse conflicts, yet no one understood his true motives…

Black Star… your contributions to this universe have been more than noble.

This thought flashed past Marbruce's mind, along with the same thought Urranrell once had.

If only Black Star was a direct member of the dynasty…

The problems they had with Black Star evaporated. At this point, the three of them knew that continuing their internal conflict was idiotic. They knew that Black Star had already displayed his compassion; it was time they showed theirs.

The three of them looked at each other and understood what one another meant. They slowly nodded.

Marbruce coughed, looked at Han Xiao seriously, and said with a solemn tone, "Black Star, on behalf of the three Universal Civilizations, I officially invite you to be the Special Safety Consultant again. What do you say?"

Chapter 1311: Negotiation and the New Stage

Looking at the solemn expressions of the three of them, Han Xiao raised his hand and shook his index finger.

"You don't want to?" Marbruce's expression became nervous.

"No, I mean it's… not enough."

Han Xiao looked calm but tutted in his mind.

You guys really are incomparable in terms of being shameless. Only not long ago you were still targeting the Beyond Grade As with all your forces, now you changed your attitude right away and want to work with us? Although your motive is right, do you guys think the Beyond Grade As are tools at your disposal anytime?

Ever since the new law was made, the association had suffered severe losses. Even though they were on the same boat now, since the World Tree had yet to attack, there was no way the association was going to help the three Universal Civilizations without anything in return.

Considering the association members' interests was part of his duty too; he was not going to let the three Universal Civilizations 'morally kidnap' him.

"What's your suggestion then?"

The three of them narrowed their eyes and leaned forward slightly.

No matter how much they admired Han Xiao's contribution, when it came to matters like this, they were not going to agree to everything Han Xiao said.

Maybe, with respect to the fact that they were on the same boat and that Black Star actively shared the information about the World Tree, they could consider compromising. However, if the terms were too over the line, the three of them were still not going to agree with it.

Han Xiao nodded and said, "Though we're working together for the big picture's sake, I hope you can understand that I'm the association's president, which means I have to give my members an explanation… The trade sanctions have caused severe losses for the Beyond Grade A members of the association, so firstly, they have to go. Furthermore, their losses have to be made up for. What do you guys think?"

"Sure." The three of them nodded. This was already within their expectations.

Han Xiao then continued, "Also, the association requires compensation for the time wasted and the emotional damage caused, in the form of resources. In our future partnership, the three Universal Civilizations will also have to continue providing us with resources. Although we have a common enemy, you guys are the rulers of the explored universe, which means we're protecting your territories for you. We won't be working for free."

The three of them pondered for a moment and agreed as well. "That's not a problem. The exact numbers can be discussed."

Han Xiao paused before slowly saying, "Lastly, the three Universal Civilizations have to approve the Beyond Grade A association's authority. It shall no longer be a civilian organization but an official Super organization. This means that our independence and the sanctity of our territory will be recognized. We'll be allowed to openly share all Super knowledges, and our political position will be on the same level as the advanced civilizations, having the same rights. All of this will also be written into galactical law… Furthermore, at the edge of the explored universe, the association shall be given a territory, of which it has the full rights of governing."

Hearing this, the three of them frowned in their minds.

One of the most crucial reasons they could openly suppress the Beyond Grade A Association was that it was still a civilian organization that was not protected by galactical law, including the Peace Treaty. Never had any civilian organization been treated the same way as advanced civilizations, not even the powerful Beyond Grade A organizations. This request meant they had to make the first exception in history.

Plus, this was not just a verbal agreement but had to be added into the laws. By doing this, the Beyond Grade A Association would be attempting to become the true authorized and official Super Organization. Once they approved that, the association's rocketing reputation would be able to almost monopolize all the Supers. Plus, if the association was protected by the law, tons of methods they could use against them before would no longer be effective. It would be very troublesome.

At the same time, by asking for a territory it had the full rights to govern, it would almost be like forming a civilization on its own. Furthermore, asking for it to be located at the edge of the explored universe was most likely because it would allow the association to retreat away anytime, preventing the possible cleansing that might happen again in the future.

Han Xiao waited for a while. Seeing that the three of them looked like they were contemplating, he tutted and added, "Don't take it the wrong way. This is a request made with the association's safety in mind. I believe the three Universal Civilizations are willing to satisfy the association's wish of keeping itself safe, right?"

The three of them exchanged looks and quickly exchanged opinions in their private channel.

After not long, Marbruce tapped the table and said, "If the information regarding the World Tree is true, we'll agree with this condition. At the same time, if a war against them breaks out, the association will need to contribute all of its forces. We'll confirm the detailed terms later."

"Good then. When you guys fulfil your side of the agreement, we'll have more bases to work together."

Han Xiao nodded. He was crystal clear in his mind that this was an exchange of interests and gamble of risks.

Even with the knowledge of an exterior enemy existing, life had to go on. The three Universal Civilizations would undoubtedly plan for what to do after the exterior enemy was banished. Then, they would still have to solve the problem of too many Beyond Grade As existing. Agreeing with this term would make their future cleansing plans tougher.

However, due to the pressure of an exterior enemy, the three Universal Civilizations had no choice but to compromise to a certain extent. If they disagreed with this request, their motive would be too obvious. Even if the association still worked with them, they would not be trusted. This request was one they could not reject despite knowing the consequences.

Furthermore, it was completely unexpected for Black Star to know about this, which disrupted their plans. Satisfying Black Star was even more important than keeping the association steady.

The three of them pondered for some time and agreed in the end. Other than this being a compromise, they were also betting on another possibility—rather than doing the cleansing themselves, they were hoping for the exterior enemy to reduce the number of Beyond Grade As. This was a more suitable path.

The Beyond Grade A Association suffering heavy casualties in the war against the exterior enemy was the most ideal result for them, much better than internal conflicts. Not only would it temporarily solve the problem of individual strength being out of balance, but it would also get the most value of these Beyond Grade As' deaths. This way, the side effects of agreeing with Black Star's request would be reduced. They would have more than enough time to consider what to do before the individual strength in the universe next went out of balance.

Han Xiao knew what the three Universal Civilizations were thinking too, but causing heavy casualties to the Beyond Grade A Association was also one of his goals.

The core reason for that was that Sanctum Revival could be carried out an infinite number of times. He claimed it was a one-time thing; when he exposed the truth, only then would his goal of making the three Universal Civilizations fearful be achieved.

In order for the Beyond Grade As to die, there were only two ways—internal conflict and external war. It was not he could make them collectively commit suicide.

Comparatively, of course, fighting an exterior war would maximize the profits. No keys would be wasted, no internal losses would be incurred, and the effects of the Sanctum Revival could be shown.

The three Universal Civilizations only had to see the effects of the Sanctum Revival to know just how important and extremely threatening it was to them. He intended on fighting the World Tree Civilization and intimidating the three Universal Civilizations at the same time, killing two birds with one stone.

Also, he planned to add some Sanctum key materials in the compensation list. Given the rich inventory of the three Universal Civilizations, they definitely had them.

This was basically the equivalent of using their raw materials to make 'weapons' that would be used against them, which was nice.

Making contact with the World Tree was already a certainty, so Han Xiao changed his plan to maximize the profits. Of course, the three of them did not know that; they probably still mistakenly thought he was ensuring their safety.

With varied plans in their minds, the two sides reached a temporary agreement.

"Also, about the World Tree Civilization, don't announce it yet. The fewer people who know about it, the better, or it would cause chaos," Marbruce said.

"I know, of course." Han Xiao nodded.

In the World Tree war in his previous life, the ones who fought were only the advanced civilizations, the armed force, and the Supers. The civilians were all protected and had limited use. It was not the time to announce it publicly yet; the public knowing about it would only add trouble.

Han Xiao paused. "By the way, since you guys invited me to be the Special Safety Consultant, I'll have to monitor this matter too. I'll need you guys to share your exploration report of the World Tree Civilization."

"No problem."

Marbruce agreed very quickly this time. After all, they had even less information than Black Star.

Han Xiao received the research report of the wormhole data from the dynasty's Science Institute right away and started reading it on the spot.

He agreed to come back to being the Special Safety Consultant because he wanted to monitor the three Universal Civilizations' exploration progress and acquire firsthand information. Currently, he was the only outsider who had the right to interfere with the three Universal Civilizations' exploration of the World Tree Civilization.

Quickly looking through it, Han Xiao's eyes locked onto the first report. On the 'Confirmed existence of a Universal Civilization' conclusion, there was a question mark beside. He then looked back at the data and realized that this conclusion was not really accurate.

"Hmm? What's with the researcher who wrote this conclusion? This data isn't sufficient to prove it's a Universal Civilization. Though he guessed it right, it's too assumptive." Han Xiao raised his brows.

"Which is why I fired him. It's too careless." Marbruce nodded.

Han Xiao had a guess.

Did this guy do it on purpose? He sighed in his mind. Even insignificant people can change the world.

Han Xiao arranged his emotions and jokingly said, "No matter what, that guy made a huge contribution. Don't wrong him."

Marbruce glanced at him and did not reply.

Seeing this, Han Xiao smiled, skipped this topic, and got back to business.

"Based on the current progress, I have a few suggestions…"

…

This meeting lasted many hours. After achieving the 'remain in close contact' agreement, only then did Han Xiao deactivate the remote projection.

As Han Xiao's sight returned to his office, he exhaled deeply, rubbed his cheeks, and mumbled, "Luckily, at least the internal war has been avoided for the time being…"

He knew the three Universal Civilizations were certainly not going to completely let go of their hostility toward the Beyond Grade As. However, at this point, they surely knew their priorities. As long as an agreement was made, they would forget yesterday's matters and make up. As long as there was a need, the relationship between the two sides did not matter, and an exterior threat was exactly what created that need.

The two sides did not turn from enemies to friends, only temporary partners at most, working together to solve the main and shared problem.

From today onward, we'll step into a new stage of fighting the exterior enemy together. It's time to prepare for war against the World Tree Civilization.

This matter had been troubling him for close to a century, and it was finally time to face it.

Chapter 1312: Awaken

One day later, on Planet Apostle, Han Xiao and Aurora walked into the research lab, stopped before SWY-001, and looked up at this enormous mechanical body.

Aurora turned and looked at Han Xiao. "Are you sure about waking this big guy up?"

"Hmm." Han Xiao nodded.

"Why the sudden change of mind?" Aurora asked.

"I've already finished studying it. There's nothing valuable left in it. It's time to wake it up and see if we can communicate."

Han Xiao made up a random reason.

"Alright then, whatever you say." Aurora rubbed her hands and said with anticipation, "Shall I start now?"

Han Xiao nodded, snapped his finger, and Mechanical Force flowed out. Mechanical soldiers appeared one after another, holding their weapons up in battle stances. At the same time, all the devices used to restrict SWY-001's movements also started to operate at maximum power output.

Seeing this, Aurora extended her arms with her palms up; life energy appeared and flowed into SWY-001. In her senses, SWY-001's almost extinguished tinder of life started to quickly come alive.

Even without the life energy Esper ability, Han Xiao could sense an enormous energy presence slowly awakening. In his senses, SWY-001's cells started generating Mechanical Force, and the countless slumbering mechanical modules inside its body gradually started to operate.

SWY-001's broken mechanical body started regenerating at a visible speed. The mechanical devices used to restrain him started to break down as if they were going to become materials for SWY-001 to recover its own body.

Ka la ka la…

Mechanical parts awakening could be heard in SWY-001's body. The core reactor activated along with a deep and weird roar, like the sound of a beast awakening.

Aurora cautiously moved back a bit while Han Xiao moved forward and stood in front of her, staring closely at the various parameter changes SWY-001 was going through during the awakening.

Suddenly, an enormous Mechanical Force exploded on the mechanical body and instantly flowed through its entire body. SWY-001's eyelids flickered, and its eyes slowly opened. There was no color in its eyes, as if it had slept for too long and its mind was blurry, trying to recall who it was.

After staying frozen for a very long time, it finally recalibrated its consciousness and started moving its body. SWY-001 looked around, looked down at Han Xiao who was also giving off a powerful energy presence, opened its mouth, and sent out deafening sound waves as if it was speaking.

"What is he saying?" Aurora asked.

Without even turning around, Han Xiao casually explained, "This is the language of his civilization. He's asking who we are and where this place is."

He obtained a lot of information from SWY-001's memory file, which naturally included the various languages of the Karma Republic.

Han Xiao was relieved about this too. Luckily, SWY-001's consciousness was still intact. Otherwise, he probably would have had no choice but to use the Sanctums.

As he was just about to speak with SWY-001, a change suddenly occurred.

Boom!

Boundless Mechanical Force exploded. The restraining devices instantly shattered and were devoured by SWY-001. Its enormous mechanical body dashed like a giant beast, instantly shattering the wall of the lab and backing away. At the same time, the shattered parts rapidly turned into all kinds of weapon modules that attached to its body and started firing at Han Xiao.

Beams shot out one after another at Han Xiao. Without even moving, the mechanical troops around him summoned shields and blocked the attacks.

"He's running away."

"It's normal given he's just woken up. Plus, he can't run," Han Xiao said casually.

The last thing SWY-001 remembered was being defeated by the World Tree Civilization, so he probably thought he had been captured by them.

Having expected this possibility, Han Xiao had disassembled SWY-001's many weapon modules long ago and stationed tons of mechanical life soldiers nearby.

The two of them entered space through the hole SWY-001 created and immediately saw what seemed to be an infinite number of mechanical troops surrounding this SWY-001 in the middle, who was about to attempt to escape.

At this time, dozens of Apostle Weapons suddenly stepped forward. Han Xiao's Mechanical Force landed on their bodies from some distance away, and these Apostle Weapons charged toward SWY-001, quickly gaining the upper hand.

After the fight with the three Universal Civilizations ended, Han Xiao had the Dimension Factory repair damaged soldiers every hour of the day, prioritizing the Apostle Weapons. The Apostle Weapons had almost fully recovered.

With the muscles on his body bulking, blood gushed out, weaving into flesh. The mechanical soldiers around swarmed toward him, and the evolved version of the Mechanical Deity instantly appeared.

He did not hold back and charged forward, pouncing at SWY-001 and beating him up fiercely. It was like two gigantic mechanical beasts fighting.

Han Xiao had the upper hand in all of his attributes, while SWY-001's modules were disassembled, and it was far from its peak state. It was completely overwhelmed and no match for Han Xiao.

Since he fought the direct members of the three Universal Civilizations, Han Xiao had concluded the missions from then and received 520 billion EXP, eight Character Summon Cards, and six new skills.

Among them, two were normal talents, two were high-level talents, one was a rare ability, and one was a Molding Talent, which came from Wuornos. The Molding Talent's name was [Divinity Enhancement]. The effects increased the strength of some of his abilities and tremendously enhanced the bonuses of the various God's Trait Transformation levels while enhancing the bonuses of talents related to religion, including [Key of Adeptus Mechanicus].

These missions also brought him three Universe Legendary Points. They were [Strongest Beyond Grade A], [Creator of the Most Legendary Battle], and [The Three Universal Civilizations' Source of Fear].

Other than that, he also completed Manison's request mission by forcing the three Universal Civilizations' fleet to retreat, so he got one of Manison's skills too. It seemed like all the luck from Feidin was concentrated into this draw. He once again obtained one of old Manison's Unique Talents. Its name was [Ultimate Mechanical Force—Manison]. It enhanced the Mechanical Force itself, tremendously increasing his Machinery Affinity and the strength of his Mechanical Force. It also increased the attributes of his Mechanical Force and his maximum energy.

Though the talent was great, having already obtained three of Manison's Unique Talents, he felt more and more like the Mechanic Emperor himself.

All these bonuses gave him a total 2,740-Ona increase in his Energy Rank. Bringing his Energy Rank up by such a considerable amount even at his current level, the impact on his combat capability was visible. Compared to back then, he was much stronger. The battle with the three Universal Civilizations became the nutrients for his growth.

Peak-state Han Xiao versus SWY-001, who did not even have a complete body—there was no suspense to the battle at all. The best method of convincing someone was usually with his fists. After a beating, SWY-001 was finally forced to speak calmly.

While beating SWY-001 up, Han Xiao sent messages at the same time to explain the current situation.

"Stop resisting. This is not the World Tree Civilization; we're another advanced civilization. You dropped into our territory and were found by me…"

After explaining repeatedly, along with the very convincing fists of his, SWY-001 finally stopped resisting and communicated back, though still doubtful.

In the quantum network, the data exchange between the two parties was completed in a blink of the eye. SWY-001 knew that Han Xiao had looked at his memory module, and he also saw some information about the galactic society. He believed Han Xiao for the most part but still said in a panicky tone, "I can't stay here. My civilization is waiting for me…"

His voice was like a mixture of the voices of countless people, strangely ethereal. His memories remained at when he was attacked and collapsed, so did not see the Karma Republic destroyed.

Han Xiao shook his head and said, "I've tested your age. You've already drifted in the universe for a very long time. In the terms of our time, what happened to your civilization was 600 years ago. Your civilization is long gone."

SWY-001 froze as if he was lost.

Protecting his civilization till his death was the top priority written into him, as well as the reason he was born in the first place.

"I need to confirm," SWY-001 replied.

"If you're willing to provide the coordinates, we can help you check it… but we need your help too. It's an equal trade."

"Help?"

"We're facing the same threat; you're the only survivor we know, so we need your help… Your civilization is destroyed, but if you want revenge, we can work together," Han Xiao explained.

SWY-001 thought about it for a while then nodded in the end. He did not have much of a choice anyway, since he could not defeat Han Xiao. "… If that is true, I'll help you."

Plus, in his fundamental logic, there was code for revenge too—while keeping himself alive, he should take revenge against the World Tree Civilization if his civilization was destroyed. Furthermore, if his civilization was really wiped out, he would have nowhere to go anyway, so fighting alongside another civilization against the World Tree Civilization matched his goal.

"I'll arrange to have you meet the rulers of this territory after some time then. I need you to convince them of some things and help them to see the threat of the World Tree Civilization."

Han Xiao paused for a moment.

"I gave you a name, but you probably wouldn't like it. What do you want me to call you?"

"… Just call me Herberlon."

The communication between the two of them happened very quickly. Herberlon no longer resisted, letting the several Apostle Weapons take him away. There were still a lot of things he had to learn about galactic society, but Han Xiao was not going to let him connect to the internet freely; he had sealed it up using his Virtual Technology.

Only then did Han Xiao deactivate the Mechanical Deity and relax.

"That went smoother than expected… Hmm, probably thanks to my strength."

If he was not able to control Herberlon, Herberlon would have definitely run away seeking the answers on his own. However, with his strength, this problem was solved easily. The method was simple, brutal, but effective. No way would Herberlon be so easily convinced had Han Xiao not defeated him.

Han Xiao opened the interface; [Visitor from Afar] was already shown as complete. The rating depended on how much SWY-001 had recovered, so the rating was very high. Although he disassembled a ton of his mechanical parts, because of Aurora, the rating increased tremendously.

The reward of this mission itself was not high; the most useful reward was only a Herberlon Character Summon Card. The key to this mission was the unknown impact waking Herberlon up would cause to the current situation of the explored universe.

While Han Xiao was concluding the reward, Aurora slowly flew over to him with her face filled with curiosity. He did not know what Han Xiao talked to Herberlon about, nor did she know where Herberlon came from.

"What did you just say to him? What's with this big guy?"

"He comes from a lost civilization, a wanderer who lost his home. As for the details, it's a secret. I have plans for him."

"Tsk, fine."

Knowing Han Xiao did not want her to ask more, Aurora curled her limps and snorted.

Aurora then said, "By the way, what are the Underworld Hero Spirits I revived going to do? They're still standing by; do you want me to revert them back to their spirit forms?"

"No need, keep them this way as a secret army. They'll be of use one day."

"Is it to guard against the three Universal Civilizations?" Aurora asked subtly. The outside world did not know what was going on between the association and the three Universal Civilizations now.

"It's part of the reason but not the main one." Han Xiao shook his head. "I've already spoken to the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations. If things go well, the two sides are probably going to call it a truce."

Shocked, Aurora said, "What? What agreement did you guys make that the three Universal Civilizations are even willing to take a step back‽"

"It's a secret for now, so I can't tell you… but I'll host a plenary after some time to explain the detailed terms. You'll know then."

…

More than half a month passed quickly. With concentrated attention of the galactic society, the three Universal Civilizations and the Beyond Grade A Association seemed to have really stopped fighting and were minding their own business.

As all kinds of speculations were blooming, the three Universal Civilizations who had remained silent for more than half a month finally made a joint announcement, causing an earthquake in the entire galactic society.

The three Universal Civilizations claimed that when the situation was spiraling out of control, they decided to take a step back, with the safety of the galactic society in mind. After thorough consideration, in the end, they decided not to burn the galactic society with the flames of war.

At the same time, they stated they had agreed with the association and came up with reasonable measures to deal with the virus… As for what exactly that was, not a single thing was mentioned.

As for the Beyond Grade A Association, they gave the three Universal Civilizations face and agreed with this claim, stating it was the truth and that there was no conspiracy.

At least on the surface, the reason the three Universal Civilizations made this huge military move was the Virtual Mutiny Virus. As long as this problem was 'solved', it made sense for them to retreat, despite the claims being quite ambiguous to say the least. They just called it confidential, and there was nothing the galactic residents could do about it.

However, what caused an uproar among the galactic residents was the second half of the three Universal Civilizations' joint announcement—they shockingly removed the trade sanctions against the association all of the sudden!

Everyone was dumbfounded. They were almost at war not long ago, yet they were making peace with each other? What in the world happened‽

Had the three Universal Civilizations given up dealing with the imbalance of individual strength? What agreements did the two sides make? Were the three Universal Civilizations so afraid they dared not strike?

Many people subconsciously thought of how Black Star single-handedly defeated all of the three Universal Civilizations' direct members. Although they knew very well the three Universal Civilizations most likely did not retreat because of how unbelievably strong Black Star was, they could not help themselves from thinking in this direction… Were the three Universal Civilizations really afraid?

Seeing how the three Universal Civilizations and the Beyond Grade A Association quickly turned from aiming at each other's throat to peace, countless members of the public felt complicated and somewhat discouraged. They felt like their feelings did not matter at all.

When eras changed, for better or worse, they could only accept it.

However, although the two sides stopped fighting, since the three Universal Civilizations expressed such a firm and aggressive stand earlier, this result undoubtedly made people feel like the Beyond Grade A Association had won.

This was one of the extremely few examples of a civilian organization forcing the three Universal Civilizations to take a step back. The reputation of the Beyond Grade A Association that had been reducing over the time suddenly rocketed, attracting all the attention in the galactic society.

Although voices of cursing the Supers never disappeared completely, they were lost in the sea of compliments. Many people's faces were hurting from this hard slap of an ending, no longer daring to voice out against the trending public opinion.

The Super Star Cluster Alliance was really the most dumbfounded party.

That's it? You guys aren't breaking up anymore?

How are we going to have a chance with the association if you guys don't quarrel?

Are we going to be abandoned again?

Being a spare tire… is so bitter!

Chapter 1313: Ahead

At the Beyond Grade A Association headquarters, the first plenary since the three Universal Civilizations decided to back off was underway. All the Beyond Grade A members arrived early at the venue, and none were not curious about what agreement Black Star had achieved with the three Universal Civilizations. They were all waiting for the president to give them an explanation.

"Frankly, this is all quite sudden for Black Star to just come to an agreement with the three Universal Civilizations. We heard nothing about it at all," Kasuyi complained.

"I wonder what kind of agreement the president made with the three Universal Civilizations. Given Black Star's personality, we shouldn't be the ones losing more than we have to gain." Kant's tone was uncertain.

Of course, no one present believed the three Universal Civilizations' public announcement. They all knew that Black Star had definitely made a deal with them privately; only, no one knew anything about it.

Psyker turned around. "By the way, Ames, you're close to Black Star. Did he tell you anything?"

"He didn't tell me anything." Ames turned to look at Hila, smiled faintly, and said, "But Hila might know a thing or two."

"… I have no idea either. I haven't seen him lately." Hila shook her head.

The people chatted for a while before Han Xiao's remote projection finally appeared in the main seat. He looked around and smiled.

"Since everyone is here, let's jump right in. I've summoned you guys mainly to tell you about the agreement I've made with the three Universal Civilizations, as well as the next steps for the association."

Han Xiao looked around, and seeing that everyone was listening attentively, he continued.

"The three Universal Civilizations have agreed to my terms. They've decided to remove the trade sanctions against us and will compensate us very generously for it. Also, they'll admit the official position of the Beyond Grade A Association, granting us the same rights as advanced civilizations. This will be written in galactic law. At the same time, we'll receive a territory at the edge of the explored universe that we'll have full rule over. That's roughly it."

As he said that, the entire place became completely silent.

The Beyond Grade As members were astounded, looking at Han Xiao with disbelief.

It was not that this agreement was bad but that it was way too good. They did not expect Black Star to be able to negotiate such outstanding terms, not to mention the fact that the three Universal Civilizations actually agreed with it.

A usual truce would be reasonable, but this was not a truce from the three Universal Civilizations at all. It was basically a surrender! No one would compromise this much unless there was a gun pointing at their productive organ!

Originally, they thought it would be good if the three Universal Civilizations were even willing to give any compensation. To their surprise, these terms solved more than half of the problems that had been bothering the association all this time.

"How did you do it?" Kasuyi could not help but ask.

Han Xiao subtly glanced at those Beyond Grade As from the Star Clusters and said, "I know you're all curious as to why the three Universal Civilizations agreed to such terms, but this is quite a complicated matter that doesn't have a definitive result yet. Plus, these benefits are not given to us for free; they're part of the deal, and the price is that we'll have to help the three Universal Civilizations in some situations."

Hearing this, everyone exchanged looks.

Seeing this, Han Xiao nodded and said, "If you guys have any ideas, feel free to bring them up. The foundation of the existence of our association is respecting the opinions of all members. If you guys aren't satisfied, we can discuss it."

Beiger coughed and made his stand, saying, "I think this is quite good. After all, us Revivors have already died once and can't use the Sanctum Revival again. It's good we don't have to take the risks of fighting a war."

Hearing this, quite a number of Revivors nodded. Completely convinced by Oathkeeper, they thought if they died again, they would have no choice but to live a meaningless life in the Underworld.

Dylan, however, snorted with disdain and said, "Tsk, what a disappointment. I thought a massacre was about to begin so that we could teach the three Universal Civilizations an unforgettable lesson to pay them back for what they did to us back then. Who would've thought that after a few hundred years, the three Universal Civilizations became cowards too? Black Star, why did you even bother to negotiate? The three Universal Civilizations are definitely in a difficult situation if they're willing to compromise, so we should've used this opportunity and made their situation even worse. I used to think you're a cruel and decisive person; I was wrong about you!"

"Hmm?" Han Xiao raised his brows and made a sound.

Dylan snorted and said with still a strong tone, "To think you're not a despicable person I thought you are but a wise man with vision, generosity, and greatness. No wonder you're our leader."

"Hmm." Han Xiao nodded with satisfaction.

The others looked away with despise and ignored Dylan's voice.

Kasuyi stepped out and said with a smile, "These terms are all pleasant surprises, so we have no problems with it. But, Black Star, the three Universal Civilizations are only saying all these things for now. They have yet to acknowledge our independence publicly. Are you sure they'll live up to the agreement? I still think they won't compromise easily."

"I'm sure for the most part, but we'll have to wait for some time."

Han Xiao shook his head.

He had already gotten Herberlon to speak with the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations, making what he said more convincing. When the three Universal Civilizations came to some results in their exploration, they would carry out the terms.

Furthermore, this matter was the center of attention for now, so the three Universal Civilizations planned to not bring more attention to it for some time. They only planned to announce it after the matter had cooled down to reduce its impact.

"I hope so." Kasuyi nodded before asking, "What are the next steps for the association then? Do you have any ideas?"

Han Xiao shook his head. "Continue to rest and accumulate our forces. We'll deal with the future by the time the three Universal Civilizations carry out the terms."

He recalled another idea he once had. When their political position is recognized and their territory was granted, the association's reputation among the Supers would reach a new level. Maybe they could then create a nation belonging exclusively to Supers, taking in all free Supers in the universe, making the association the ruling parliament of the nation.

One reason was that in order to develop further, they had to expand the size of the association and recruit more members. Of course, as the 'seeds' of Beyond Grade As, the more Supers, the better. Another reason was to maintain independence. Ordinary Supers living under the three Universal Civilizations' rule would have many worries, but if they had a new place to go, they would have a choice, and there would definitely be people who would be willing to become this nation's resident.

Furthermore, the conflict between the ordinary people and Supers had been getting worse and worse; both sides hated each other. Maybe giving Supers an opportunity to live away from the other side would be beneficial for both sides.

Of course, the three Universal Civilizations would undoubtedly be unhappy with this. Therefore, Han Xiao would not carry out any part of this idea before the threat of the World Tree Civilization erupted.

"All races are welcomed as long as they're Supers… Hmm, why does this idea sound so familiar?"

Han Xiao scratched his head.

If I remember correctly, this is quite similar to a character in an ongoing comic in my previous life, 'Big Mom'.

What am I then? Big Dad?

Putting this random thought behind, Han Xiao continued discussing with the others.

The meeting only ended after discussing matters for more than an hour. Everyone left relaxed and excited.

Han Xiao deactivated his remote projection. The moment his sight returned to the office, Phillip popped up.

"Master, hum… you have an advanced encrypted message. It's from the Super Star Cluster Alliance, hum…"

"Yoho, looks like their patience is running out."

Han Xiao opened the message, and it was an invitation from the Super Star Cluster Alliance to meet him in person.

He was not surprised. The association was originally working with the Super Star Cluster Alliance against the three Universal Civilizations. Now that it had stopped fighting the three Universal Civilizations, the Super Star Cluster Alliance became alone again.

Plus, the Beyond Grade As belonging to the Super Star Cluster Alliance who were in the meeting earlier definitely passed on the information about the agreement, and the Super Star Cluster Alliance would certainly be worried that the association and the three Universal Civilizations might work together again. Hence, they hastily came to test his stand.

…

Ten minutes later, in the Super Star Cluster Alliance conference room, the various leaders gathered and sat in their seats apprehensively.

Han Xiao's remote projection appeared in the room and immediately felt all the eyes focusing on him.

The Star Arc Civilization leader said with a deep voice, "Black Star, we agreed to fight the three Universal Civilizations together. What's all this?"

Han Xiao shrugged and said, "The goal of conflict is peace. The association's goal has already been achieved, so of course, there's no longer a need to continue fighting the three Universal Civilizations. This is beneficial for the association."

"What about our agreement?"

Han Xiao said slowly and calmly, "Our agreement consisted of four terms. Other than the first one being fighting the three Universal Civilizations together, the other three are all related to resources partnerships, which we can continue to do."

The Star Arc Civilization leader could not help but ask, "What if the three Universal Civilizations have a problem with that? Will you ignore our agreement because of it?"

"Since the three Universal Civilizations have recognized that the association can take care of the virus itself, it's an indirect way to admit that others have no right to interfere with the internal affairs of the association. Which galactic law did we violate by forming an alliance with you guys? So what if they have a problem with it?" Han Xiao shrugged. "Maybe we can change one of our terms from fighting the three Universal Civilizations together to the association not attacking the Super Star Cluster Civilizations actively other than to retaliate. Besides, the Sanctum Revival allocations I promised you guys are still effective."

They were quite surprised to hear this. They were already prepared for Black Star to stab them in the back, but for now at least, Black Star seemed to have no intention of doing that.

Han Xiao smiled and said, "Frankly, we don't trust the three Universal Civilizations, so we need to have a backup plan, which is why we're willing to maintain a good relationship with the Super Star Cluster Alliance. Also, you guys provided help when the association was troubled by the trade law, so personally, I'm willing to continue working with you guys. I have that much decency."

"I see…" The Star Arc Civilization leader was relieved.

Although this felt as wrong as cheating, Black Star keeping the promise of the Sanctum Revival allocations given to them was good enough.

…

After the participants made their stands, no matter how wild the conspiracies were, the matter calmed down very quickly. The galactic residents and the organizations gradually went back to their normal lives.

As the trade law was removed, the various channels of the association reopened, gradually regaining business. However, the plan of uniting the black markets was still ongoing and carried out by the players.

Big things happened every day, but life for ordinary people still had to go on. The issues between the three Universal Civilizations and the association went on and became just something people talked about over the dinner table, no longer brought up every single day.

However, under the calm surface, a storm was brewing. The three Universal Civilizations were secretly preparing for war while exploring the wormhole data left by EsGod that was named 'World Tree Path'.

With Han Xiao's warning, the three Universal Civilizations were very cautious. They had yet to discover any life belonging to the World Tree Civilization.

At the same time, taking Han Xiao's suggestion, the three Universal Civilizations formed a joint expeditionary army to enter the deep layers of the secondary dimensions in search of the so-called main body of the World Tree.

At one of the dynasty's outposts in the secondary dimensions, an enormous expedition fleet had gathered, carrying out its last checkup before departing. The dock was filled with the three Universal Civilizations' soldiers with serious expressions on their faces.

Han Xiao stood on the dock and watched this.

Harrison stood beside him carrying a backpack. Not knowing what to do, he said softly, "Your Excellency Black Star, what is the fleet searching for? Why do I have to participate in it?"

Han Xiao patted his shoulder. "Searching for something that will affect the fate of the explored universe."

"Must I go?" Harrison was on the verge of tears.

He was still young, yet to be that experienced senior explorer from Han Xiao's previous life. Plus, the World Tree war had not broken out yet, so people were not all on their highest alert, nor could he prioritize other things above his life.

Traversing into the deep layers of the secondary dimension was no easy mission. They had to pass through countless strange secondary dimensions, so god only knew what situations they would run into. Any mistakes could cause severe damages. Plus, communication was not convenient, meaning they would be like a fleet that advanced deep into enemy territory without having stable communication with the rest.

"What are you so afraid of? Didn't I give you a lot of equipment? They're more than enough to protect you in times of danger. You even have a Lord's Avatar and a Throne with you. I can teleport over anytime."

Han Xiao slapped his forehead.

"I'm scared I'll die before I can call you." Harrison looked discouraged. "Plus, there are so many people participating. With or without me won't make much of a difference, will it?"

Han Xiao sighed but could not reply.

In his previous life, Harrison discovered the main body of the World Tree, but this time, who knew if the Goddess of Luck would help him again?

Furthermore, the World Tree's main body was not without protection. Countless armies were stationed in the secondary dimensions around it; it was extremely dangerous. Once the fleet discovered them, it would be when they were discovered by the World Tree too.

However, without finding the World Tree's main body, the chances of winning were extremely thin. Sending an expedition army in advance was already being one step ahead.

Han Xiao was currently the only outsider working together with the three Universal Civilizations to find the World Tree. Other than Harrison, he had picked some trustworthy people to join the first batch of the secondary dimension expedition army, most of which were mechanical lives, along with some members of the Black Spirit Race.

As he comforted Harrison, the expedition fleet was finally ready.

Looking back several times every step he took, Harrison still entered the spaceship in the end.

Accompanied by the roaring engines made for travelling in the secondary dimensions, the joint expedition fleet slowly took off, turned into flashes of light, and disappeared in everyone's sights, heading toward the unknown future.

Chapter 1314: Reaction

After sending off the expedition team, Han Xiao stood at the dock for a while. At this time, Guzar, who was wearing a dynasty military uniform, walked over from behind and stood side by side.

The bearded Guzar took out a red cigarette from his shirt pocket, wiped his fingers, lit the cigarette, and took a deep breath. Then, he spat out a cloud of smoke and twisted his mouth a little before speaking.

"This is only the first batch. There will be a second and a third expedition team in the future. The deeper dimensions are unpredictable. I hope that the World Tree's main body that you mentioned really exists. Don't let them sacrifice for nothing."

"Don't be too pessimistic. Maybe they will come back safe," Han Xiao replied casually.

Guzar did not comment. He took out another cigarette from his pocket and passed it to Han Xiao. "This is a product specially provided by the dynasty's upper echelons. You can't buy it on the market. Try it?"

"I stopped smoking." Han Xiao waved his hands.

"Is that so?" Guzar put away his cigarette and shook his head. "Speaking of which, I've never heard of you having any hobbies. Don't you Mechanics have any entertainment needs?"

"How can smoking and drinking be more fun than machines?" Han Xiao glanced at him. "Just say what you want to say."

"Can't I talk to you?" Guzar shrugged.

Although Black Star had beaten them up not long ago, the two parties had now come to an agreement. The battle before was purely official business, and there was no enmity between them.

Most Beyond Grade As admired the strong, and the direct descendants of the three Universal Civilizations were no exception. They all respected Black Star's achievements and abilities.

"Next time. I'm quite busy." Han Xiao patted Guzar's shoulder.

Guzar sighed and said, "Alright, I'm here to tell you that His Excellency the Ruler is waiting for you online. He wants to talk to you about something."

"Why didn't you say so earlier?"

Han Xiao turned around and walked into the dynasty's outpost base. He went to the private communication room and picked up Marbruce's call.

"Ruler Marbruce, what's the matter?"

"Our exploration has made some progress. The probe has collected the exact coordinates. The Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device can already reach the territory of the World Tree Civilization, but we have no intention of sending troops for the time being."

The Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device of the Federation of Light had extremely high strategic value, so it was extremely useful.

It was a pity that the three Universal Civilizations only allowed him to interfere in limited areas. Most of the time, they only treated him as a consultant and did not allow him to use the World Tree passageway to send anything.

"Is there anything I can help you with?"

"We plan to bury some detection equipment and strategic killing weapons in uninhabited areas. For this, we need more intelligence, such as the star map on the other side and the division of factions… The efficiency of our detection is low, and as the detection range expands, the risk of encountering the creatures of the World Tree Civilization will also increase."

"So?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

"We plan to try to connect to the other party's network after we're done with our preparation and see if we can steal some of their information," Marbruce said. "We're here to ask for your opinion."

Han Xiao thought for a while and said, "If it's only superficial information, as long as we enter from an unimportant terminal node and erase the data before letting the Beyond Grade As analyze the other party's basic code words, the risk is controllable."

This was not hacking into the other party's network but browsing through the information on the internet. Therefore, the difficulty was not high.

The World Tree Civilization also had a communication system in the form of a quantum network, which was basically standard for advanced civilizations. However, the foundation of the communication method was not a quantum network but a mental network that the World Tree had. It was just that the latter was too transparent and simple, not as diverse as the quantum network.

"Then let the Beyond Grade A Mechanics take the lead and use the computational ability of the main artificial intelligence to gather the surface information of the other party's network. When the time comes, the intelligence will be shared with you."

After chatting for a while, Marbruce hung up the call. His purpose of calling was mainly to inform him of the exploration plan.

Han Xiao put down the communicator and curled his lips.

"Other than the secondary dimension expeditionary army, they did not allow me to interfere with other exploration tasks. It seems like they are still wary…"

The current situation was far from the stage of unity in his previous life. Although it was not to the extent of scheming against each other, they could not completely trust each other like they did in his previous life and cooperate without any worries.

After leaving the dynasty's outpost and returning to the army base, Han Xiao summoned Phillip and issued a special summoning order to the hundreds of Beyond Grade A seeds in the army.

As the three Universal Civilizations strictly controlled the World Tree passageway, he did not have much preparation to do at the moment. Other than improving the Void God's Trait Transformation and allowing his assembly line to churn out soldiers all day long, he could only wait for the players to work hard and slowly provide EXP.

Therefore, he planned to use the advantage of the interface to give the hundreds of Beyond Grade A seeds that had transferred to the army a year ago a long period of special training. He hoped that a new Beyond Grade A would be born from these people and strengthen the association's top-tier strength.

After sending the message, Han Xiao left the room and walked around the base for a while. Suddenly, he came across Jenny.

Han Xiao stopped in his tracks and said, "Ames has already returned to Floating Dragon. Why are you still here?"

Jenny crossed her arms and snorted. "It wasn't easy for me to get a holiday because of my refuge. I don't want to go back so soon to work overtime. Let Ames take care of it herself. I'll have some free time."

"So, you've rested well. No wonder your hairline recovered a little. I almost didn't recognize you."

"If you don't know how to talk, you can keep quiet. No one will think you're mute." Jenny rolled her eyes.

"Then have a good rest here. However, if Ames comes to ask for you, don't expect me to help you." Han Xiao shook his head and smiled before taking his leave.

Just as he was about to leave, he suddenly heard Jenny speak again. This time, her tone was a little hesitant.

"Um… I haven't seen Harrison in a while. He hasn't replied to my messages either. Where did he go?"

Han Xiao turned around and looked at her with surprise.

"The two of you really hooked up? I thought you rejected him, but it seems like you're the same as Ames; your body is more honest than your mind."

"Bullsh*t!" Jenny was furious. "I have nothing to do with that annoying fellow! I'm just curious!"

Han Xiao did not believe her at all, only casually saying, "He went on a secret mission. You probably won't see him for a long time."

"Secret mission?" Jenny hesitated. "Is it dangerous?"

"Of course," Han Xiao replied straightforwardly.

Jenny choked and hesitated for two seconds before whispering, "Then please tell him…"

"Tell him what?" Han Xiao immediately became alert.

Damn sister, be careful. Don't set up a flag so easily. It will lower Harrison's survival rate.

Jenny gritted her teeth, turned her head, and stubbornly said, "Just ask him, when will he return the money he owes me?"

"Tsk, your words don't even match what you're thinking." Han Xiao exposed Jenny mercilessly.

"It's fine if you don't want to help me!" Jenny was furious.

"I'll ask… but I might not be able to contact him at the moment. Let's talk when there's a chance." Han Xiao waved and left.

When he turned the corner, he looked back and saw Jenny still standing there with a lost expression.

"Tsk, and you dare say that nothing's happened."

Han Xiao smacked his lips and was about to leave when Phillip suddenly jumped out with a face full of surprised joy.

"Master, hum… Another army officer has become a Beyond Grade A!"

"Hmm? Let me see!"

Han Xiao was overjoyed and immediately switched to the surveillance interface.

In the image, a figure with Pugilist flames burning all over his body was sitting in the middle of the galaxy like a small star. It was Lothaire, who had been in seclusion for decades.

"After holding it in for so long, this guy finally gave birth… Bah, he advanced."

Han Xiao was relieved.

Initially, he thought that Lothaire would need a few more years to complete his transformation, but he did not expect him to break through this barrier so quickly.

Could it be that he got inspired by seeing me defeat the three Universal Civilizations?

After swapping into the King, Han Xiao teleported to Lothaire's personal training hall. The moment he looked up, he saw Lothaire completing his final evolution.

Han Xiao summoned his mechanical army and set up an energy shield around him.

After waiting for a period of time, the Pugilist flames on Lothaire's body slowly retracted. They seemed to take on a consistency like a solid crystal, and just by looking at it, one could feel an oppressive sharpness.

The nature of Pugilists' energy was ever-changing and varied. Lothaire's core energy attributes were 'Sharp' and 'Armor Penetration'.

Lothaire opened his eyes and surveyed his surroundings, immediately seeing Han Xiao. He quickly flew down and landed in front of Han Xiao.

"Your Excellency Black Star, I didn't disappoint you."

Lothaire's attitude was still respectful, and he did not lose himself due to the sudden increase in strength.

Han Xiao squeezed his shoulder and said with a smile, "You're a Beyond Grade A now, so you can address me as an equal. What do you think? Do you want to start your own organization?"

"I'm still willing to be your blade in the shadows. If not for your nurturing, I wouldn't have my current achievements." Lothaire shook his head and continued to address him respectfully.

Usually, Beyond Grade As would not continue to be under others, but Lothaire intended to repay the favor. Furthermore, the Black Star Army was an anomaly, and there were already two Beyond Grade As working as subordinates. With their seniors as an example, those who came later would be more accepting.

"Don't underestimate yourself. I helped you because you have potential."

As Han Xiao spoke, he punched Lothaire's chest, creating a dull thud.

Lothaire took a step back and rubbed his aching chest.

Seeing this, Han Xiao shook his head. "You have to continue training your body. You're still too weak right now. In the eyes of ordinary people, Beyond Grade As are already at the peak, but in the eyes of us veterans, this is just the beginning. You've just stepped into this threshold, so there's still a lot to train. I can fight dozens of new Beyond Grade As like you."

"I saw the live broadcast of your confrontation with the three Universal Civilizations, and I have no doubt about that."

Lothaire nodded. He was also convinced by Han Xiao's performance back then and was filled with respect.

"Since you've become a Beyond Grade A, let me give you a gift. I'll get you a Universal Treasure weapon in a while. What type do you want? If you don't want mechanical equipment, I can ask a Mage to help you build equipment with Enchantments," Han Xiao said.

Lothaire thought about it. "A pair of daggers will do."

"Alright, send me the specific requirements after you've thought it through. I'll customize it for you."

Han Xiao smiled and suddenly changed the topic.

"By the way, I have a mission for you."

"Where? Who's the target? When's the deadline?"

Lothaire immediately became serious, displaying the professionalism and discipline he had instilled in himself.

"Sigh, don't keep thinking about fighting and killing. It won't be good." Han Xiao coughed and said, "There's a genius Pugilist with extraordinary potential who is undergoing special training here. He already has a Beyond Grade A as his teacher. I hope you can train him for some time too and teach him some experience."

Karlot's bottleneck was still in the early stages, and only by accumulating more insight would he be able to level up quickly. However, the insight provided by each expert was different. Silver Shadow was almost completely squeezed dry of his insights, but Lothaire, who had just been born, would be a new crop field to harvest.

"Alright, I will do my best to teach him." Lothaire nodded. He was also curious.

The potential of a genius Pugilist who could make the Army Commander find a Beyond Grade A to be his teacher, just how shocking would it be?

In a turquoise space, the intertwined roots of the turquoise trees acted as the ground, and they were translucent. One could see the energy that was like light bubbles flowing within the roots, giving off a sense of green vitality.

In the middle of the space, a large number of roots rose up and formed a huge throne. A tall figure sat on it with his eyes closed as though he was sleeping. Vine-like roots crawled all over his body, and the blue and green fluorescence flowed along his body like lively little elves.

Suddenly, this figure trembled slightly and slowly opened his eyes. He raised his hand and gently patted the armrest of his seat.

The next moment, the roots on the ground moved on their own, intertwining and transforming into a flower bud. Then, the flower bud opened, and a tall figure appeared out of thin air, clad in a gorgeous robe.

As soon as he appeared, the tall figure bowed to the figure on the throne and softly asked, "What can I do for you?"

Hearing this, the figure on the throne leaned forward slightly and slowly said, "An abnormal reaction has occurred in the information state warning network. There might be an unknown Information Form that has interacted with us. Someone might be spying on us. Go and investigate."

"Understood, Your Excellency Tree King."

Chapter 1315: Movement

In a certain part of the World Tree Civilization, an artificial teleportation wormhole suddenly appeared and expanded. A few unmanned engineering ships flew out and quickly set up camouflaging and communication relay stations.

After the temporary base station was completed, the three direct Beyond Grade A Mechanics of the three Universal Civilizations used it as a springboard to send the data over.

In the data field, the quantum souls of 'Defender' Romo, 'Quantum Demon Spirit' Judith, and the other appeared. In their sights were the quantum network nodes that formed something akin to a resplendent sea of stars.

"Pay attention to the data disguise. If anything abnormal happens, cut the link immediately."

Judith gave a few stern instructions.

After the initial preparations, the three Universal Civilizations were officially carrying out their espionage plan. They sent out three direct Mechanics to make use of the various civilizations' main artificial intelligence computing power to browse the World Tree Civilization's network.

The World Tree passageway was only used as a springboard. Currently, the coordinates of the wormholes leading to the World Tree Civilization that the three Universal Civilizations had obtained were not limited to the data that EsGod had left behind. For safety reasons, they would rarely use the same wormhole coordinates twice.

This was the first time these coordinates were being used. They had also planned to temporarily seal it after stealing the intel.

The three of them did not waste any time, immediately using the basic translation language that they had deciphered not long ago, working together with their teammates to infiltrate a quantum network node. They began to collect data on a large scale and search for public information on the internet.

Every second, a huge amount of data would be sent to the advanced encrypted information processing warehouse created by the three Universal Civilizations.

The three Universal Civilizations monitored the situation from afar, and their efficiency was extremely high. The operation was completed very smoothly.

The engineering ship immediately dismantled and retrieved all the equipment, leaving behind a few strange-shaped bombs before returning to the explored universe through the wormhole.

The moment the engineering ships returned, the three Universal Civilizations closed the World Tree passageway on the other side of the wormhole. The artificial wormhole rapidly shrank and disappeared.

Immediately after, the bomb that was left in this area exploded at the right time. Chaotic energy waves spread out, covering the area and erasing all traces.

The area regained its calmness as though nothing had happened.

After an unknown period of time, a spatial rift suddenly appeared, and a translucent turquoise root emerged from within.

Ripples appeared on the surface of the roots, and a fleet flew out. At first, it was a little ethereal, like a phantom, but when it completely left the roots, the appearance of the fleet turned solid.

In the command room of the main ship, the captain stood beside a tall figure and respectfully said, "This is the abnormal reaction area shown on the information state alert. Holy Tree Emissary, should we start the inspection?"

This tall figure's name was Barbani, and he had a ferocious appearance. He looked like some kind of arthropod, clad in a suit armor, and his body exuded a weak blue-green energy. He was not of the same species as the surrounding crew.

Within the World Tree Civilization, the Holy Tree Emissaries were a special group with a high status and were the executors of the highest will. Only individuals who had a deep connection with the World Tree could take on this role. They could use some of the World Tree's abilities, such as warping, transformation, and so on.

"Activate the Information Form camera and see what's going on here." Barbani's voice was short and sharp.

This device could trace back what had happened in an area at the Information Form level. The more power injected into it, the longer it could trace back, and the clearer the details.

The order was given, and the fleet started operating very quickly. They could only see light green light beams scanning the surroundings, but there was no reaction from the areas they passed.

"There are no traces of any information form, so we can't know what happened here… We can basically confirm that an outsider has infiltrated this area."

The captain looked at the scan results and quickly came to a conclusion.

"Even the traces of any past Information Forms have disappeared. This means that the outsiders have a certain level of Information Form technology. Their level of civilization should not be low."

"Looks like we have new prey." Barbani was excited.

The captain looked at the time and analyzed, "Based on the time difference between us arriving at the scene, the target of the outsiders' infiltration might be entering our quantum network to steal intelligence."

"This is a good thing." Barbani did not care at all.

He was not worried that the information on the internet would be leaked. There were no key secrets hidden there. At the same time, this served as bait.

The Information Form warning network covered the entire World Tree Civilization's information collection, and it could detect if an outsider was spying on them. As long as they were entangled with the foreign information gathering, they would send out a warning. However, it was only limited to the alarm, and there was no way to steal the other party's information. Therefore, they could only discover that there were outsiders spying on them, and they did not know the exact situation of the other party.

However, this was not a problem. The World Tree itself had the nature of a high-dimensional information entity. The more outsiders knew of its existence, or the deeper the pilfering of data, the more obvious the connection would be.

As long as the interaction reached a certain standard, the World Tree would obtain a signal and sense the location of the other party's information gathering. Then, it would send the long-distance team to search in the direction of the other party.

This was similar to the soul connection of a Universal Treasure. It could be remotely located, but this relationship was reversed.

Most Universal Treasures would find it difficult to establish a soul connection, and they were extremely cold and aloof. Even if they acknowledged their master, they would only give in halfway. The Evolution Cube and the Spacetime Amber were both like this, but the World Tree was a Universal Treasure that accepted almost everyone.

However, outsiders would only be able to 'rub against the outside' and would not be able to obtain any substantial benefits from it. Instead, they would expose themselves.

This was similar to how if you said my name, I would be able to obtain information about you. It was similar to the characteristics of certain life forms in the universe, as though they had divinity.

Therefore, the intelligence of the quantum network was a kind of bait. It was to catch the 'fish' in the universe that had the ability to discover them and find prey.

However, the intelligence on the internet was not fake data. It was indeed true information left behind by the daily activities of countless citizens. However, all the secrets regarding the World Tree itself were strictly restricted and could not be uploaded.

"Alright, your mission is complete."

Barbani let out a sharp laugh.

"I'll suggest that the Tree King activate all the Information Form Foreseers and see if they can predict any information on these outsiders. Let's go."

As his voice fell, the turquoise energy on his body suddenly surged.

The gigantic root that was quietly lying on the side seemed to have received a signal. It suddenly curled up and swallowed the fleet before quickly retreating into the spatial rift.

The next moment, the spatial rift quickly closed, as though it never existed.

A few days later, on a secret training planet in the Black Star Army's territory, Han Xiao floated in outer space and looked down at the two meteors chasing each other on the ground. They collided time and time again, leaving huge potholes in the ground.

One of them was Lothaire, and the other was Karlot.

Lothaire controlled his strength and continuously trained Karlot in actual combat. While imparting his comprehension of martial arts, he was also practicing precise control of his strength. Karlot was like a sponge, rapidly absorbing the essence of the training to enrich himself.

"Now that I've found the right training method, this guy's improvement is tremendous."

Han Xiao nodded with satisfaction.

Karlot was not the only one. In the past few days, he had also been training the other Beyond Grade A seeds. He was teaching them according to their talents and providing them with a customized cultivation plan. The effect was not bad. He felt that if this continued for a long time, there should be many seeds that could 'sprout'.

Beep beep…

At this time, his communicator rang.

Han Xiao took a look and saw that it was a message from the three Universal Civilizations. It contained the intelligence from the World Tree Civilization's network.

He raised his brows, and his spirits immediately perked up.

As the players' intelligence channels were limited, it was difficult for them to be involved in high-level secrets. His understanding of the World Tree Civilization came from the war in his previous life, and it was basically common knowledge.

He knew very little about the situation of the World Tree Civilization at this time, and this information could help him to understand more.

"…Before the war, the daily life of the World Tree Civilization was similar to that of the galactic society. Speaking of which, in my previous life, the three Universal Civilizations only dealt with the invasion and never attacked the territory of the World Tree Civilization. This is the first time I've seen the detailed star map of their territory."

Han Xiao looked through it carefully and realized that it was all ordinary information. None of it was more important than the World Tree itself.

He found the three Universal Civilizations' names at the end of the message, saying that they would fulfill the agreement and acknowledge the association's position.

Although they did not verify the accuracy of the secret that I provided, the other ordinary intelligence reports have all been matched. The three Universal Civilizations should no longer be suspicious…

Just as he was reading the message, his communicator rang again. Han Xiao looked at it, and it was from Oathkeeper. The content made his heart tighten.

"An abnormal reaction from Destiny's Child?"

Han Xiao's eyes twitched.

If he did not remember wrongly, the last abnormal reaction of Destiny's Child was when the Intelligent Plague erupted in advance. Furthermore, it had created a new batch of sub-bodies, one of which was in his hands.

This was something that Oathkeeper had told him personally after he had formed a good relationship with him.

At this juncture, for Destiny's Child to cause problems again, he vaguely felt that something bad was going to happen.

Chapter 1316: Destiny's Child's Prophecy

At the Holy Accord Organization's secret base, Han Xiao, who was wearing the King mechanical suit, teleported to the exclusive Throne Teleportation Platform. Law and Fay were already waiting there.

"Your Excellency Black Star," the two greeted.

"Where's Oathkeeper?" Han Xiao looked around.

"He's waiting for you in the Destiny's Child lab. This is very sudden. Please follow us."

The two of them did not have much and led the way. Han Xiao followed them to their destination.

Walking into the laboratory, the room was filled with busy operators. Han Xiao immediately saw Destiny's Child locked in the transparent container and Oathkeeper standing beside it.

At this time, Destiny's Child had already woken up from his deep sleep. His body was curled up, trembling nonstop, and white spots kept flashing like a projection when the signal was not good. He turned blurry every now and then, and Oathkeeper had to constantly release his Soul Flame as if to comfort him.

The researchers in the room were sweating profusely as they operated the apparatus, activating the binding force field at full power and stabilizing his anchor in reality.

Han Xiao came to the device and looked at the various parameters. "What's the situation now?"

Oathkeeper frowned. "Destiny's Child has woken up and is now in a state of Information Form disturbance. The amplitude is the highest so far, almost breaking through the containment and turning into a High Dimensional Information Form. It's not over it yet."

"Have you found the reason?"

"Not sure yet. We can only communicate after he stabilizes."

Hearing this, Han Xiao clicked his fingers and summoned a set of stabilizing anchors. He set them up around him to provide assistance, and at the same time, he carefully sized up Destiny's Child. This was the first time he had seen his true body.

Every time Destiny's Child activated his ability, there would be an information state disturbance, which would cause the prophetic ability seeds to be planted randomly across the universe. Lodi, who had been receiving treatment, was one of the children who had awakened after the last disturbance. There had already been a breakthrough in stopping the transformation process.

At this time, Destiny's Child suddenly stopped shaking and turned to look at Han Xiao as though he was observing in curiosity. Suddenly, he raised his hands and pressed them on the inner wall of the container, releasing a happy mental wave. Everyone heard a child-like laughter materialize out of thin air.

Destiny's Child stared at Han Xiao like that. Not long after, his flickering body gradually stabilized and returned to normal.

Seeing this, Oathkeeper stopped what he was doing and looked surprised.

"How did you settle this the moment you arrived? He seems to like you very much."

"This is the first time we've met. You're too unreserved… Speaking of which, why do you sound like you've been robbed of your love?"

"…What nonsense are you talking about?"

Han Xiao teased Oathkeeper, but he himself was secretly surprised as well.

Destiny's Child seemed to be strangely close to him. Could it be that his [Primal Esper Ability Affinity] and [Perfect Energy Affinity Physique] had a part to play in this?

There was such a possibility. After all, the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy has thought that I was attractive on more than one occasion, and it even wanted to mess around with me…

Perhaps to a Primal Esper Ability Entity, these two talents are like catnip to a feline. No wonder Destiny's Child was attracted to me the moment he saw me. Who told me to make myself so attractive toward energy life forms?

Han Xiao thought to himself for a while before knocking on the container. Destiny's Child immediately imitated it, and the two of them interacted happily.

This scene made Oathkeeper a little frustrated.

In the past, Destiny's Child liked him the most, and he would personally do all the comforting work. He did not expect Black Star to only come once, and Destiny's Child, whom he had nurtured their relationship for so many years, immediately ignored him.

The most infuriating thing was that even before Black Star appeared, Destiny's Child would never take the initiative to get close to him…

It's clearly me that's supposed to be the one… Forget it, let's not talk about this.

After watching for a while, Oathkeeper said, "Alright, whatever the reason, it's enough to stabilize it. I'll ask him what's going on."

As he spoke, he pushed Han Xiao away and gathered his Soul Flame to communicate with Destiny's Child.

A few seconds later, Han Xiao heard Destiny's Child's intermittent words.

"I feel… the feedback of the sub-bodies… a convergence of information… threat…"

As Destiny's Child spoke, Han Xiao's mind was filled with chaotic and blurry images.

Han Xiao's eyes narrowed. In these complicated images, he suddenly saw information about the World Tree, such as the image of the World Tree roots spreading across the galaxy, or a group of robed people wreathed in turquoise energy meditating on the ground.

Oathkeeper did not know about the existence of the World Tree, so he could not understand it.

"What is this?"

"Wait, let me ask you a few questions…"

Han Xiao did not have the time to explain to him. He asked a few random questions and received a reply very quickly.

After listening to Destiny's Child's reply, Han Xiao quickly pieced the information together and analyzed it.

The sudden abnormal reaction of Destiny's Child originated from the World Tree. Both parties were entangled in the information state, and it sensed that the World Tree was using some method to locate their explored universe.

The reason he had a reaction was because of its affinity with the sub-bodies. The sub-bodies he once produced were randomly distributed across the entire universe. Not only did it affect the explored universe, but there were also Destiny's Children on the World Tree's side, which triggered its foresight ability.

To Destiny's Child, these sub-bodies were like his eyes, ears, and antennae, collecting information about the outside world.

Not long ago, the child of the World Tree activated its foresight ability. Because the medium was connected to the information gathering from the explored universe, the two parties had crossed paths. Because the explored universe was also where the main body was, it immediately triggered the warning mechanism. Therefore, Destiny's Child activated his ability to foresee the future and shared the memories and vision of his sub-bodies with the rest.

During this process, Destiny's Child felt the threat from the World Tree, akin to that of a natural enemy. He even foresaw the possibility of him being swallowed by the World Tree, thus leading to him almost wanting to turn into a high-dimensional information form and flee, which explained his previous actions.

In that case, the World Tree is using a prediction method to sense the explored universe, and the three Universal Civilizations are already exposed?

Han Xiao's heart tightened.

Indeed, as long as they had any sort of contact, the situation was already irreversible. They would be able to quickly sense each other sooner or later. The World Tree Civilization was stronger than the three Universal Civilizations, and even the three Universal Civilizations in his previous life did not know all the abilities and technology of the World Tree. It was too ideal to completely hide their tracks.

In his previous life, the three Universal Civilizations had been beaten to a bloody pulp. Even if they had won in the end, they had not completely understood the World Tree. Some of the auxiliary skills such as the Information Form warning alarms had not been used in the war, so the three Universal Civilizations were unclear of the full scope of their abilities.

Because the World Tree had taken the initiative to invade, their Information Form warning network that was used to prevent outsiders from spying was basically useless. Even the three Universal Civilizations did not know about it, let alone the players in his previous life.

The only good news now is that the World Tree Civilization only detected the existence of outsiders, and it does not have much information. Therefore, they are using the Information Form to search for us, which resulted in their interaction being discovered by Destiny's Child…

Han Xiao's brain worked quickly.

Luckily, Destiny's Child had scattered his body all over Galaxy itself, or else he would not even know that he had been discovered. At that time, even he would have been caught off guard by the other party's sudden attack.

Destiny's Child referred to the World Tree as his 'natural enemy'. One was a Primal Esper Ability Entity, while the other was a Space Wonder. Both of them had information-type abilities, but their focus was different.

According to the explanation of Destiny's Child, it could share information about the contact of the child. Because the child was connected to the World Tree, it could observe the overall movements of the World Tree Civilization to a certain extent, but there was also the risk of being exposed.

Only when the sub-body actively used its foresight ability and was entangled with the information form would the main body be able to use it as a disguise to obtain information from the sub-body. Otherwise, it would be easily discovered by the World Tree.

Even so, Destiny's Child was probably the only low-risk channel to monitor the movements of the World Tree. It was more convenient, more secretive, and more efficient than the detection methods used by the three Universal Civilizations.

Such an intelligence channel was a pleasant surprise, and there was no reason to ignore it.

Han Xiao thought about it and said in a deep voice, "You don't want to be devoured by the World Tree. Helping us is the best choice. Only by eliminating the other party can we eliminate the threat once and for all. Otherwise, even if you escape far away, there will still be risks."

Hearing this, Destiny's Child shook his body, his voice ethereal.

"How… can I help you?"

"Just try to hide yourself, monitor the other party's movements, and tell me everything."

"I… can do this."

Destiny's Child did not reject him. He suddenly clapped his hands together, and a small white ball of light separated from his body and floated in the container, drifting toward Han Xiao and sticking to the inner wall of the container.

Han Xiao understood and raised his brows.

"Is this for me?"

"Use it… to create a sub-body… and extend my senses…"

In his mind, Destiny's Child explained the use of this light cluster.

When it activated its ability, it could give birth to a sub-body in the entire universe, or it could give birth to a sub-body in a designated area. However, the latter had a prerequisite. It had to use its own energy to circle an area in advance and turn this area into an independent 'information assembly location'. Only then could it be designated as the birthplace of the sub-body.

To put it simply, this was akin to a hose running around its area… or rather, it was like a dog peeing on its territory.

Just as Han Xiao finished listening to Destiny's Child's explanation, a notification appeared on his interface.

You have triggered the mission [Destiny's Child's Plea]!

Mission Introduction: Destiny's Child has a good impression of you. Because it feels threatened, it has decided to seek your help.

Mission Requirements: Head to the designated location and use the energy of Destiny's Child to circle a sufficiently large area.

Reward: 120,000,000 Experience, +25 Destiny's Child Favorability, 1 Random Reward, milestone talent [Deep Within Enemy Territory].

[Deep Within Enemy Territory]: When you are operating within your enemy's sphere of influence, you are not easily discovered. At the same time, you will obtain a 3% buff to all Attributes.

"You want me to go to the World Tree Civilization?"

Han Xiao was stunned.

By limiting the birth area of Destiny's Child to the territory of the World Tree Civilization, the number of children would increase, which meant that more information would be intercepted.

Although the ability to encircle land had a time limit, its duration was measured by years. This could be used for a long period of time.

"It seems like I'm the most suitable person for such a hit-and-run mission. It seems like I'll have to apply to the three Universal Civilizations to head to the World Tree Civilization…"

Han Xiao nodded.

He got Oathkeeper to temporarily open the container and took out the ball of light.

As soon as it came into contact with him, the ball of light entered his palm and turned into a mark that stored the energy Destiny's Child had lent him.

"What's going on? What are you guys talking about?"

Oathkeeper's face was filled with confusion.

Han Xiao thought about it, pulled Oathkeeper aside, and briefly explained the situation.

"You're saying that the three Universal Civilizations discovered an even stronger Unknown Civilization?" Oathkeeper was surprised, but he soon understood what was going on. "No wonder the three Universal Civilizations made so many concessions."

"It's good that you know about this. It's not suitable for you to tell anyone for now. Remember to keep it a secret," Han Xiao instructed.

With the help of Destiny's Child, he naturally could not avoid Oathkeeper, so he told him the truth and made him understand the importance of the matter. Only then would he cooperate.

In addition, Oathkeeper's character had been tested, and he was quite trustworthy. There was no harm in letting him know.

"Don't worry, I won't tell anyone about this."

Oathkeeper's expression was solemn. He suddenly paused and softly asked, "You mentioned in the meeting that the three Universal Civilizations acknowledged the association's position, and we will have to help at some point. Is this what you mean?"

Han Xiao nodded. "That's right. If a war breaks out, the members of the association will have to participate in the war with all their might to fight against the foreign enemies. This is the deal, and we don't have any choice. Therefore, I need you to prepare more Sanctum keys."

"…I understand your plan. I will cooperate with you." Oathkeeper exhaled.

If the Beyond Grade As went all out to fight, they would probably suffer heavy casualties. Black Star probably wanted to use this opportunity to show everyone the truth of unlimited Sanctum Revivals. As someone who knew the truth, he felt that this was a very feasible plan.

While he was thinking, Han Xiao suddenly patted his shoulder.

"Then work hard. The organization will not treat you badly after this is done."

Oathkeeper frowned.

Tsk, I was so busy digesting the information that I forgot to steal the lines!

Chapter 1317: Dispute

The two of them chatted for a while before reaching a consensus. Han Xiao left a Throne and a Lord's Avatar in the Destiny's Child laboratory and interacted with Destiny's Child for a while before leaving the room. He turned around and went to visit the Revivors who were living in seclusion in the Holy Accord, gathering them for a meeting.

The current President of the Beyond Grade A Association had pointed out in the meeting that the Holy Accord Organization had to take the mental states of the Revivors seriously and help the Revivors follow the pace of the times. They had to follow the basic principles of people as their core and implement the 'two for one' requirement, which was to ensure the best treatment of every Revivor, yet not lose their vigilance.

The founder of the Holy Accord organization, Oathkeeper, praised the association's current achievements and emphasized that both parties had always worked together to contribute to the Beyond Grade As. He hoped that the association would continue to work together with the Holy Accord.

Many of the revivors expressed their admiration for Black Star's contributions to the Beyond Grade As and unanimously welcomed Black Star to come and give guidance to the Holy Accord.

No matter what, both parties still had a good exchange of opinions. After the daily communication, Han Xiao then left the Holy Accord Organization base and teleported back to Black Star Palace, which was a few Star Fields away.

Returning to his office, Han Xiao rubbed his chin. Without any delay, he contacted the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations and sent the information he had obtained from Destiny's Child through the encrypted channel.

Not long after, his communicator rang, and he received an invitation.

Han Xiao turned on the remote projection and arrived at the joint office of the three Universal Civilizations. He immediately saw the three leaders.

"Black Star, where did you get this information from? Is the situation true? You have to be responsible if you spout nonsense!"

As soon as they met, Marbruce fired off a string of questions. His tone was extremely serious, as if he was doing an interrogation.

The intelligence provided by Han Xiao showed that the World Tree Civilization had already discovered the traces of the outsiders and was trying to track them in reverse. This was a huge matter that affected the entire strategy, and they could not afford to be careless.

This piece of intelligence did not contain any evidence, so it looked like an irresponsible guess. Furthermore, even they only dared to carefully explore the uninhabited areas and had no clue about the World Tree Civilization's movements. Where did Han Xiao's intelligence come from? The three of them could not help but doubt its authenticity.

"I have a special intelligence channel. This is a special Primal Esper Ability Entity called Destiny's Child. It has extraordinary abilities at the Information Form level…" Han Xiao explained Destiny's Child's ability.

"Destiny's Child?"

The three of them looked at each other with doubt in their eyes.

This Primal Esper Ability Entity did not exist in the known Super High Risk Esper Ability Table, nor was it recorded in the secret database of the three Universal Civilizations. This was the first time the three of them had heard of this Primal Esper Ability Entity.

"So, you guys really don't know?" Han Xiao was helpless.

He had once tried to find out more about Destiny's Child. There were no records in the dynasty's database, so he thought that the information might be stored in a secret database. It seemed like the three Universal Civilizations did not know about Destiny's Child either, but they were indeed good at hiding their existence.

"The Destiny's Child is in your hands now? Is it reliable?" Louis asked.

"It's indeed in my hands, and there's no problem with the intelligence."

Han Xiao nodded and hid the existence of the Holy Accord.

Hearing this, the Pope of the Arcane Church said with a deep voice, "Words have no evidence. We can only confirm its authenticity after checking it. Furthermore, this kind of intelligence channel should be controlled by us."

Han Xiao shook his head, and his tone became solemn.

"At this point, you guys still have doubts about me? Who provided the secret information about the World Tree? It was me, right? I showed my sincerity, but what did you guys do? In order to confirm that the information is true, you guys went to explore the World Tree Civilization through the wormhole, and in the end, you were exposed… Of course, from your standpoint, this is understandable. I understand you guys, but it's also a fact that you were discovered by the enemy. No matter how correct your motives are, there's no way to change the predetermined bad outcome… Because I knew that you guys might mess up, I didn't tell you about the World Tree beforehand."

The three of them were stunned.

Marbruce coughed and took the initiative to explain.

"It's not that we doubt you, but we can't just trust the authenticity of the information. If we don't confirm it beforehand, it will be too late when a problem arises…"

"This isn't the first time you've said this, but what happened in the end? You're still following the confidential information I provided. The so-called confirmation is just unnecessary in my eyes. It will only increase the risk of exposure."

The three of them opened their mouths, not knowing what to say.

"Black Star, don't get too emotional," Louis said. "We have always been cautious and did not meet any life forms of the World Tree Civilization. With just the senses of a Primal Esper Ability Entity, I don't think we can be completely sure that they have already detected our presence…"

"You still want a hundred percent confirmation?" Han Xiao's eyes widened. "Then why don't you just show yourself and ask the World Tree Civilization? That will definitely be a hundred percent."

Louis' mouth twitched, and he stopped talking.

Marbruce said helplessly, "But the intelligence…"

Han Xiao cut Marbruce off.

"I know you're worried, and I don't expect you to completely trust me. However, you stole the intel from the network, so you should have confirmed the World Tree's attitude toward the outside world. Since everyone is prey, we're on the same side. Do you still need to worry about me having any bad intentions and remain specially guarded against me?

"The threat is imminent. Now is not the time for internal speculation. We all have to believe that what we're doing is for the same goal. We will not deliberately cause trouble. If I cannot confirm the authenticity of this information, would I dare say it? If you insist on checking and this information channel is exposed, what should we do?"

The three of them frowned.

That was true. They were comrades who were united against the enemy. They should at least trust each other.

However, since Black Star had made such a statement, could it be that he did not want them to confirm it on purpose so as to hide the fishy side of this intelligence? They had no choice but to think in this direction.

Seeing their reactions, Han Xiao knew what they were thinking and shook his head in disappointment.

"At the end of the day, the countless years of peace have made you arrogant, thinking that you can deal with any situation… Maybe my intelligence gave you too many misconceptions, making you feel that you have an advantage and can control the situation. It's a huge mistake! I hope you guys can recognize the reality. The World Tree is stronger than all of you combined. As long as it finds us to start a war, the situation will instantly go out of control. We can be wiped out at any time and become the next Karma Republic!"

"… What do you suggest?" Marbruce asked.

"I'll be straightforward. I will never give you this information channel. Even if you don't believe me now, you should consider dealing with this situation. The World Tree Civilization has advanced unknown detection methods and has discovered the traces of outsiders. They have entered a state of alert, but they have yet to succeed in tracking us down… Therefore, I suggest that we stop the regular exploration and reduce the chances of further contact. We will standby for the time being and give the secondary dimension expedition team more time to find the World Tree's main body."

"But if we don't explore, how will the intelligence come?"

"With all due respect, most of the intelligence that you guys have obtained so far is meaningless. Since there are no results, you might as well stop and use the channels of Destiny's Child."

"It means that we don't have to do anything but listen to you obediently, and take whatever you say… Do you think that's possible?" The head of the church, who was standing at the side, spoke with a dissatisfied tone. He paused for a moment before adding on.

"You can either give us Destiny's Child or let us send some researchers to study it together to prove that the intelligence is reliable."

Han Xiao smiled.

"Are you forcing me now? Yes, I can make concessions for the sake of righteousness. We can study Destiny's Child together and dispel your suspicions. If I don't do this, it will appear to be my fault. Because I have the channels, I have to make concessions and give in to benefits. If I don't let you guys have a share, you won't accept my opinion."

"You misunderstood. We…" Marbruce felt that the atmosphere was a little off and wanted to explain.

Han Xiao interrupted him once more, his smile turning cold.

"You three dogsh*ts, I've already tolerated you all for a long time! You guys don't seem to have figured out who here needs whom. Do you really think I have no other choice? I'm willing to protect the Galactic Society; that's why I'm helping you, since both of you are closely related. However, the universe is so big. Do you think I really need to stay here? If you anger me, I can just leave with the Beyond Grade A Association and the organizations under me. It's fine if I move to the unexplored universe or the secondary dimensions, leaving you guys to deal with the World Tree Civilization alone. Do you want to try?"

The three of them were shocked.

They almost forgot that the Beyond Grade A Association had a way out. With their abilities, they would be able to live very well even if they escaped into the unexplored universe. To the three Universal Civilizations, this was definitely the worst outcome.

As long as the Beyond Grade As made up their minds, they could completely abandon the galactic society that they had lived in for a long time. To be honest, even if all the living beings here died, it would have nothing to do with most Beyond Grade As. There was no reason for them to stay and fight.

If news of the World Tree spread, there would definitely be people who would choose to escape. If even Black Star, who had the Sanctum Revival, was not willing to stay, then the other Beyond Grade As would definitely choose to escape.

With such influence, Black Star was not a partner with no way out. He was an equal who held the bargaining power, a force that they had to fight for.

Marbruce could no longer sit still. "Don't be angry. That's not what we meant."

"Black Star… Your Excellency, our doubts are just a matter of fact. We don't have any thoughts about benefits," Louis quickly comforted.

Even the Pope had no choice but to lower his head in frustration. "…I didn't choose my words correctly and caused a misunderstanding. Please don't take it to heart."

We're the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations. When have we ever been so humble?

Seeing this, Han Xiao stopped being angry and regained his poker face as he slowly stated, "I will continue to share the intelligence, but whether you believe it or not is your problem. I can't be bothered. Also, I will be going to the World Tree Civilization's territory in a while to increase the surveillance of Destiny's Child. Remember to prepare the World Tree passageway or the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device… If we don't even have this bit of trust, I think there's really no need for us to cooperate."

"Alright, we will deal with it," Marbruce answered. Now was not the time to continue bargaining.

Han Xiao nodded and suddenly added, "One more thing. Hurry up and fulfill your promise, admit the independence of the association. Don't think of delaying it. Don't think that you can get away with it when the war breaks out. As I said, I'll just leave."

With that, the communication was cut off, and the remote projection disappeared.

There were only three people left in the room. They looked at each other with complicated expressions.

"I didn't expect to be scolded by him in person. Did we push him too hard?" Louis smiled bitterly.

"Don't look down on him. How could someone as ambitious as Black Star lose his cool so easily? He's just using this as an excuse." The Pope shook his head, paused, and said helplessly, "However, he did hit the nail on the head."

"Black Star is really…" Marbruce hesitated for a moment before sighing. "His wings are completely spread open. "

When Han Xiao returned to his office, he snorted and threw the communicator aside.

"These three are definitely born in the year of the dog. If I didn't give them two slaps, how would they understand who their daddy is?"

Chapter 1318: Establishment and Setting Off

As the saying went, if the sky collapsed, there would be a tall man to hold it up. Currently, only the three Universal Civilizations and Han Xiao were stopping the World Tree Civilization from pressuring the Galactic Society.

Under the surface of peace, undercurrents were brewing. Half a month quickly passed, and it was time for the Galaxy Central Civilization Court Assembly.

The Galaxy Central Civilization Court was hosted by the three Universal Civilizations, and the participants included the Super Star Cluster, Star Cluster, and Star System Civilizations.

Unlike the regional Civilization Conference of the various Star Fields, the Galaxy Central Civilization Court was the most authoritative Civilization Conference, the core of the entire galactic society. It was solemn and respectful, also known as the 'Central Council'.

Every year, there would be a fixed meeting period that lasted several months. During this period, there would be frequent meetings to review the issues submitted by the various civilizations, to coordinate the development of all the galactic civilizations, to mediate disputes, to discuss the management of the galactic society, and so on, including many topics such as civilian life, economy, military, and disaster relief.

However, the galactic residents did not pay much attention to this matter because they had meetings every year. Most of the time, they only talked about some old topics. Most of the galactic residents only looked at the brief news coverage after the meeting.

The venue of the Galaxy Central Civilization Court was shaped like a flower petal. In the center was the chairman's board, and around it were the representatives of the three Universal Civilizations. There were rows of fan-shaped seats that were arranged according to the level of the civilization. The Super Star Cluster Civilizations sat in the inner circle, and the Star System Civilizations sat in the outermost circle. The invited news reporters had a dedicated broadcast area.

At this moment, the venue was filled with diplomatic envoys from various civilizations. This conference had been going on for quite some time.

The president had just finished a round of voting and rejected a proposal to increase the security budget of the region. He then flipped to the next topic and looked at the representatives of the three Universal Civilizations. He cleared his throat before speaking.

"Then the next topic is a joint proposal by the Federation of Light, the Crimson Dynasty, and the Arcane Church. This proposal believes that the Beyond Grade A Development Association plays an indispensable role in maintaining the galactic society and has extraordinary influence. At the same time, it is dedicated to maintaining the peace and stability of the Galactic Society and has made an indelible contribution. This proposal is to revise the universal laws of the universe such as the Peace Treaty and make an exception to accept the Beyond Grade A Development Association, allowing it to enjoy an independent official position. Its rights and benefits are equivalent to the treatment of the advanced civilizations. May the proposer of the proposal come on stage to explain."

The president finished reading the topic according to the script. The venue, which was originally filled with small discussions, suddenly became silent.

Other than a portion of the subsidiary civilizations that were in close contact with the three Universal Civilizations, the other representatives were all stunned.

The three Universal Civilizations had made peace with the Beyond Grade A Association not too long ago, and now they were eager to help‽

Not to mention the inside story, there had never been such a precedent in history for a civil organization to have the same official position as a civilization. The three Universal Civilizations' proposal had opened a new path, and the rebound from the outside world could be imagined.

What made the three Universal Civilizations willing to pay such a price to obtain political benefits for the association‽

Most of the civilizations' representatives were dumbfounded. They thought that this was just a routine meeting, but they did not expect the three Universal Civilizations to suddenly throw out such a bombshell.

The news reporters immediately perked up.

This was juicy news!

Under the attention of everyone, the dynasty's diplomatic representative stood up and walked up the stage. He looked around the venue and slowly explained the reason for the proposal, emphasizing the unique position of the Beyond Grade A Association in the current galactic structure. His speech was full of praise, as though he wanted to praise the association to the skies.

After listening for a while, the expressions of the various civilization representatives turned strange.

Why does it sound so familiar? Did you guys just slack off and simply just change the negativity of the trade sanction declaration into positivity?

After the representatives of the three Universal Civilizations finished their respective statements, the president announced the start of the debate and consultation. A large number of civilization representatives immediately requested to speak.

Although the Galaxy Central Civilization Court was presided over by the three Universal Civilizations, if they wanted to add a new clause in the Universal Civilization Law, they still had to put it to a vote.

However, as the final winner of the exploration era, the three Universal Civilizations naturally would not be so stupid as to hand over too much power. They all gave themselves the privilege of having one veto and one decision vote.

The veto vote would negate the voting result of an issue, returning it to the proposal stage, to repeat another round of presentations, debates, amendments, and voting, and so on until they were satisfied with the result. If the decision vote power was used, the voting stage was skipped directly, but the priority was lower compared to the veto vote, which meant that only the three major civilizations could exempt each other's decision vote power.

However, the number of times the three Universal Civilizations had used their privileges could be counted on one's fingers. As long as it did not involve their own benefits, they would not interfere. Most of the time, they only acted as the judges and rarely took part in the battle.

The representatives of the three Universal Civilizations easily dealt with the questions of the participants, and they answered the sharp questions with one sentence.

Among them, the Super Star Cluster Civilizations were the calmest. They had long received this news, and while watching coldly, they were secretly trying to figure out what was going on between Black Star and the three Universal Civilizations.

Amid the excitement of the crowd, it was soon time for the voting. The civilizations' representatives who did not know about this earlier all had different opinions, and no one wanted to be the first to take on this issue.

The result of the vote was shown on the virtual screen. There were a lot of objections, and they did not meet the criteria to pass the draft.

The president took a look and said, "We don't have enough votes, so we shall reject this…"

Before he could finish, the Federation of Light representative knocked on the table and said, "My side will use our right to veto."

The president nodded, not surprised at all. "Then, let's enter the proposal stage again. Please…"

However, before he could finish, the Crimson Dynasty representative slowly said, "My side will exercise the decision vote."

The moment he said that, the Federation of Light and Arcane Church expressed their agreement.

Seeing this, the representatives of the various civilizations did not find it out of their expectations, but they were still surprised.

They had expected that the three Universal Civilizations would use their privileges, but no one expected them to use two privileges.

The three Universal Civilizations had basically never used two privileges at the same time. After a single veto, they would usually let everyone re-evaluate their decision and do things like lobbying during this period to fight for votes. This would more or less make the other civilizations feel they had a sense of participation.

However, after vetoing the proposal, a decision was immediately made. The representative's attitude was very firm, implying that this proposal had to be approved. It was unquestionable and very overbearing, as though they did not mind performing a one-man show.

"Are the three Universal Civilizations so determined to stand up for the Beyond Grade A Association? What exactly is going on?"

The representatives of the civilizations felt an inexplicable itch to understand the situation.

…

As many media outlets fought to repost the news, the news that the three Universal Civilizations were fighting for the Beyond Grade A Association's official identity spread like wildfire in the Galactic Society!

The conflict between the three Universal Civilizations and the Beyond Grade A Association had just ended, but another shocking news story broke out, instantly turning into the hottest topic.

The majority of galactic residents could not understand what the three Universal Civilizations were doing.

Not long ago, during the peace negotiations, although the three Universal Civilizations had given in, they at least had a dignified reason. How could they explain this now? Just reconciliation was not enough, and they even had to help the association to be promoted. What were they doing? Compensation for what?

First, they attacked aggressively. In the end, they were so scared that they took the initiative to give in. This was already embarrassing enough. He did not expect the three Universal Civilizations to compensate the association and furthermore insist that they were not cowards… Only a fool would believe that!

As soon as this proposal was exposed, it was met with strong opposition from a large number of galactic residents. Originally, they had already suppressed their dissatisfaction toward Beyond Grade As, but seeing that the association was about to become an official organization, many people could not take it anymore and started attacking the association. The most mainstream argument was that the association did not have the right to become an official organization and that they should not allow a Beyond Grade A group to have such an identity.

Due to the escalation of the class conflict, the Beyond Grade A Association had already become the main target of hatred. Seeing that the association was going to develop further and even be 'purified', many galactic residents were furious. This mentality was akin to seeing their enemy living a good life.

On the contrary, most of the Supers in the various Star Fields were excited. They had been looking forward to the Beyond Grade A Association being their leader, but they did not expect it to really come true. Furthermore, it was the first time in history. No matter how the association did it, many Supers were full of admiration.

With the official position, the three Universal Civilizations could no longer promote the association's illegitimacy. Supers no longer had to worry about losing their citizenship after joining the association.

Due to the three Universal Civilizations having a say in the Galaxy Central Civilization Court, many civilizations expressed their opinions through various channels. They first acknowledged the important influence of the association, but they tactfully felt that giving them an exception was a little too much. They claimed that they did not know about the private transactions between the three Universal Civilizations and the association and expressed their dissatisfaction.

Comparatively, the reaction of the players to this news was a little delayed, mainly because most of them did not quite understand the meaning behind it. In their eyes, it was enough as long as the Beyond Grade A Association was strong enough. These political things seemed meaningless.

However, after some storyline-loving players explained it on the forums, the players finally understood the difference.

"Treating a civilization as a country, which means that the Beyond Grade A Association used to be a company but is now a country?"

"Does this mean that the Beyond Grade As are building a nation?"

"More or less. Initially, no matter how powerful the association was, it was still a civilian organization. Now, it has finally evolved."

"I've figured it out! The main storyline should be based on the Beyond Grade A nation as the main body to witness the birth of a different Super civilization. Black Star is the highest leader, so it's called the Black Star Era?"

"66666, I understand."

"Sigh, as an old player who fell into this rathole in Version 1.0, I personally witnessed Old Black starting from nothing and climbing to his current position step by step. I'm so touched. It's like I'm recalling my youth… No, I have to watch Bun-Hit-Dog's Black Star Army series from the start!"

"Previous poster, please cover your ID when you're advertising yourself. Thank you for your cooperation."

On the forums, many players were extremely excited.

When the three Universal Civilizations and the association were in a standoff, many players thought that the main storyline would be a battle between the two sides, but they did not expect it to end with a truce. Now that a Beyond Grade A nation had been founded, the players felt that the main storyline missions would definitely revolve around this point, and they could not possibly be wrong this time!

While the outside world was abuzz with the news of the association being promoted, Han Xiao was already prepared and headed toward the territory of the World Tree Civilization.

…

At the border of the Abyss of Stars, an enormous fleet surrounded a Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device, which was currently heating up. Han Xiao was the only one inside.

"We have set the coordinates, which lead to a location that has never been activated. It's located in an uninhabited area. If what you said is true, then the World Tree Civilization has an unknown detection method. It's best if you leave immediately when you reach the other side and find a way to hide yourself…"

In the communication channel of the mechanical suit, Fleet Commander Simon was carefully instructing him on what to take note of.

"You guys can just send me there. I'll take care of the rest," Han Xiao replied.

Simon nodded. "Hmm, since you have the King mechanical suit, you don't need us to pick you up. Just adapt to the situation."

In the end, the three Universal Civilizations agreed to send Han Xiao to the territory of the World Tree Civilization. Because Han Xiao had the King, there was no need for them to wait and receive him.

To Han Xiao, as long as he left behind a Throne in the past, he could teleport to it anytime in the future. This was the reason the three Universal Civilizations did not allow him to participate in the previous exploration.

However, he was worried that the connection between the King and Throne would serve as a clue to his location, so he placed many Thrones in different secondary dimensions. Furthermore, he had to choose his location carefully when leaving the Throne in the World Tree Civilization's territory.

I hope I can achieve something this time…

Han Xiao's brain worked quickly.

This trip to the territory of the World Tree Civilization was only one of the goals of helping Destiny's Child. Besides, the World Tree Civilization had already discovered the outsiders. So long as he did not leak any information about the explored universe, he might be able to act more boldly. If there was a chance, he wanted to see if he could find clues about the World Tree's main body on the other side. This was extremely important. Just relying on the expedition fleet left too much to chance.

At the same time, he also wanted to see if [Virtual Purification—Restore] was effective on the members of the World Tree Civilization.

Just as Han Xiao was thinking, the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device finally finished its preheating and began to spin rapidly, turning into a circle of light.

"Cut off all the links," Simon said in the channel before turning off the communication network.

Han Xiao activated the silenced mode of his mechanical suit, blocking all network links, including Phillip.

Very soon, the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device reached its maximum speed.

Buzz!

All of a sudden, there was a flash of light, and the teleportation device rapidly slowed down. Han Xiao's figure had disappeared in front of everyone's eyes.

Chapter 1319: Nothing to Hide

The Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device felt almost the same as the King's Teleportation. His vision blurred, and his body became light. The figures of the three Universal Civilizations' soldiers around him disappeared, and he reappeared in an empty space in the universe.

This is the territory of the World Tree Civilization… Let's determine my location first.

Han Xiao quickly activated all kinds of detection devices to observe the surroundings. It was indeed a deserted region.

The exploration of the three Universal Civilizations was not completely useless. At the very least, they had stolen the star map of the World Tree territory from the internet, which gave him a lot of assistance in his infiltration.

However, because it was not convenient for him to connect to the network of the World Tree Civilization, he could not enjoy the GPS positioning of the network. He had to find a planet as a reference to confirm his exact location. Then, he would use a backup artificial intelligence synchronized star map model and utilize the space measurement technology as well as the calculation formula of star distance and vision to create a self-made navigation device. He had no need to rely on a network link. Although there would be some errors, it would be precise enough.

As he had come to the territory of the World Tree Civilization alone, it would not be convenient for him to communicate with the explored universe. Therefore, he could not obtain remote assistance at the moment and could only act on his own.

Han Xiao entered the quantum network but did not connect to the node. Instead, he used this method to check for densely packed areas of the node to determine where there were people.

I wonder what the World Tree Civilization's detection method is…

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. Ever since he came to the territory of the World Tree Civilization, there was a faint sense of danger in his heart, as if just staying in the territory of the World Tree Civilization was a dangerous thing.

Just relying on this intuition, Han Xiao could guess the reason for the three Universal Civilizations' exposure.

Just staying here makes me feel out of place, as if I'm being spied on. The World Tree has a powerful information state ability, so maybe it's a detection method specifically for foreign information states?

Logically speaking, the three Universal Civilizations had never come into contact with any life forms of the World Tree Civilization, and the areas they had explored before were all uninhabited areas. They had made sure to conceal themselves, so they should not be discovered. However, if the World Tree Civilization had set up an unknown information network in its entire territory, the situation would be a different case.

According to Han Xiao's understanding, the progress of the three Universal Civilizations' research in the Information Form state had always been slow, and there was no related technology to it. If their roles were changed and the World Tree Civilization used the same method to spy on the explored universe, the three Universal Civilizations would most likely not discover it.

I hope the mark of Destiny's Child will be of some use.

Han Xiao looked at the mark on his hand.

Destiny's Child was also an expert in the Information Form field, and he had the trait of being unobservable as a High Dimensional Information Form. This temporary mark could activate the corresponding concealment function, achieving a 'closed information loop' like Rody. It would not be observed by ordinary people, and it might be able to hide from the unknown surveillance methods of the World Tree Civilization to a certain extent.

However, the three Universal Civilizations had already alerted the World Tree to detect the presence of outsiders. The main reason he hid his tracks was to make it easier for him to carry out missions. As long as he did not reveal any information about the explored universe, it would not be a big deal if he was discovered. It was fine as long as he could escape in time.

Let's set up the map.

Han Xiao calmed himself down and activated all kinds of concealment devices before picking one direction.

After sailing in the direction of the quantum node for a period of time, a yellow planet finally appeared in his vision. It seemed to be a colonial planet. A few spatial cracks had opened up near it, and translucent turquoise roots extended out from within, inserted into the planet. They kept expanding and shrinking as though they were breathing.

The roots of the World Tree…

Han Xiao stopped and used this planet to calibrate his position in the star map, finally creating a navigation module.

He only looked from afar and did not approach.

If he could obtain a portion of the roots and use it to find the location of the World Tree's main body… It was a pity that his previous life had proven that this method would not work. He had to think of a different method.

Han Xiao looked at the yellow planet again and nodded.

This should be a planet that has been transformed.

Everything that the World Tree devoured would turn into information form storage after digestion, which could be remade into a physical entity. A planet being devoured did not mean that it would disappear, but it existed in a different form. The World Tree could build it again, and it only required a certain amount of energy and resources.

However, the resources needed to materialize did not require matching materials. The World Tree had an inseparable relationship with psionic energy. Psionic energy could be decomposed into many forms of energy, and it was often treated as a form of 'universal energy'. The World Tree also had a similar function, involving changes in matter.

For example, the materials used to make steel through the World Tree could be wood, seawater, or all kinds of random things. With enough energy, a series of unknown transformations within the World Tree would eventually turn into solid steel, like a high-level alchemy product that no one could understand.

Although the World Tree had a will, it was also a tool-type Space Wonder that was used by the civilization. After many years of experimentation, they had managed to calculate the synthesis requirements of countless objects.

It was because of this characteristic that the World Tree Civilization's war strength was extremely strong. They had almost never been disadvantaged, and their army was endless.

Many resources came from planets, and the World Tree Civilization would convert those valuable planets back in their main camp, allowing them to continue evolving and produce all kinds of materials. From there, they would accumulate more resources. Swallowing a planet in one go was like getting a one-time deal, and after it was converted, there would be a long-term harvest.

Now was not the time to cause trouble. After Han Xiao activated the navigation star map, he immediately left and disappeared.

After a long time, ripples suddenly appeared on the roots of the earth yellow planet, and a fleet quickly materialized.

In the command room, Barbani looked at the yellow planet curiously.

"There seems to be an abnormal reaction in the vicinity? Could it be that the outsiders are not satisfied with exploring the outskirts and wish to spy on our planet?"

The captain shook his head. "I'm not sure. The reaction of this information state alert is very weak. I don't know if it was a false report."

"Let's take a look at the Information Form camera first." Barbani waved his hand.

Very soon, the fleet activated this device, and the light green light screen quickly scanned the surrounding area. The results showed that everything was normal, and there was no situation where all traces of Han Xiao were cleared like the three Universal Civilizations.

The captain looked at the results, nodded, and said, "The traces of the information state are intact, and there are no abnormal clues. Given how the outsiders cleared all their traces last time, it's either a false report, or this time, the outsiders have even higher level Information Form technology."

"Could it be new prey‽" Barbani got excited again.

"Hmm, I can't rule out this possibility. The level of the later intruder's Information Form technology is clearly higher than the outsiders who cleared all the traces last time. They might be two different groups of people… However, there's the World Tree Root beside them. If the outsiders cleared all traces here like the previous time, they would have been discovered immediately. I'm more inclined to it being misinformation." The captain analyzed the situation for a moment before speaking out again. "To be safe, since the camera has lost its effectiveness, the other party might have used a high-dimensional information form, so we need you to personally investigate."

Hearing this, Barbani nodded and flew out of the cabin, entering space with just his bare body.

Then, a turquoise light emerged from his body and concentrated on his visual organs, emitting a hazy green light. He patrolled the area while scanning the surroundings.

Suddenly, Barbani stopped and looked in a certain direction. It was the area that Han Xiao had stayed in previously.

The green light in his eyes gradually grew stronger. At this time, within the range of the light, a blurry shadow that looked like water ripples suddenly appeared. It was like a cluster of glowing particles, just extremely dispersed.

"I see it. It's indeed a high-dimensional information form."

Barbani perked up.

The high-dimensional information state had an unobservable nature, and the related technology was very advanced. Even if one stood in front of it, ordinary people would not be able to detect it, and the information state camera would not be able to detect it either. The disguise provided by Destiny's Child's Mark was the high-dimensional information form state.

However, as the Holy Tree Emissary, Barbani could use the high-dimensional information vision of the World Tree to offset the 'Closed Information Feedback Loop'. He could view any High Dimensional Information Forms were previously unviewable to the eyes of others. That was how he discovered the trail.

Just by borrowing the high-dimensional information vision, he was unable to completely reverse the situation like a camera. He could not obtain any specific information and could only detect certain traces of movement.

"The number of outsiders is unknown, so there shouldn't be too many. They stayed around for a few seconds…" Barbani suddenly exclaimed in excitement. "Eh, this outsider seems to still be here."

In his vision, this light particle-like trail extended in two directions, pointing in the directions the outsiders had come and gone in. This meant that the outsiders had not teleported away but had continued staying in the territory of their civilization.

"Holy Tree Emissary, what do we do next?" the captain asked in the channel.

"Humph, wait in the tree. I'll chase after them and see if I can capture this outsider alive."

Barbani could not wait to move. He turned into a turquoise beam of light and chased after Han Xiao.

…

Meanwhile, Han Xiao was speeding through the universe, looking for a suitable starting point according to the star map.

Just as he was focused on his journey, the interface suddenly pinged.

You have triggered an urgent mission: Nowhere to Hide!

Mission Introduction: In the territory of the World Tree Civilization, outsiders have almost nowhere to hide. Your whereabouts have been discovered. Someone is following the clues you left behind.

Mission Requirements: Face the pursuers.

Reward: Unknown

Han Xiao frowned. "I had the concealment device activated and even used the high-dimensional information form of Destiny's Child's Mark, but I was still discovered so quickly. Is the World Tree's surveillance method so penetrative?"

Chapter 1320: Determined

The mission notification said that in the World Tree territory, there was almost no place for outsiders to hide. Han Xiao was now even warier of the World Tree's unknown detection methods.

Han Xiao frowned. The World Tree Civilization has far more control over their territory than the three Universal Civilizations. If I don't figure out what's going on, I'm afraid I won't be able to move an inch here…

Since his whereabouts had been discovered, he would only be pursued if he continued to escape. With the convenience of the World Tree's mental network, the pursuers could share information and surround him. It would be quite troublesome for him.

Looks like I have to adjust my plan. It's not suitable for me to carry out the mission now…

If they did not figure out what the detection method of the World Tree Civilization was, they would not even know how they were exposed, much less know how to avoid it.

Since the pursuers were behind him, he had no choice but to get rid of them. He wanted to see if he could find out the principle of the detection method from them. Furthermore, since he originally wanted to see if the virtual purification would work on the people of the World Tree Civilization, this was a good opportunity.

Due to the mechanism of the mental network, when he came into contact with the people of the World Tree Civilization, the scene of him taking action would be observed. There were many risks, such as the other party calling for reinforcements, and he might have to abandon the mission and leave.

However, this was not a big problem. It was not like he could only go to the World Tree Civilization once. There was no time limit for this marking mission. If he could not deal with it this time, he could do it next time. On the other hand, if he could learn about the World Tree detection method from the pursuers, it would be more valuable to him. At the very least, he would not have to poke around blindly in search of it.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. "Although I've been discovered, I still have an advantage…"

The current situation seemed to be that the enemy was in the dark while he was in the light. However, the pursuers had discovered him, but they probably did not know that he had detected the enemy through the interface mission. From another perspective, perhaps the enemy was in the light while he was in the dark.

Although he did not know what was going on with the pursuers, they were likely following his movements. He might be able to ambush them from the opposite direction and quickly end the battle so that the pursuers would not see too many of his methods.

"Tsk, I wanted to move stealthily, but you just had to force me."

Han Xiao's mouth twitched, but he did not continue forward. Instead, he turned around and flew a distance before beginning to set up his scheme.

A green beam of light streaked across the sky, speeding forward.

Barbani had been constantly activating his high-dimensional information form vision to track the traces left behind by Han Xiao. In his eyes, a path formed by light particles extended out.

"What guts you have, how dare you stay and try to gather more information? You're courting death."

Barbani was not angry but excited.

Although the Holy Tree Emissary had a high position and power, most of the time, he had nothing to do. After all, the World Tree was connected to everyone, and there were no criminals or rebels. There were basically no internal conflicts, and these experts had nothing to help with. Other than training and enjoying material benefits, there was nothing else they could do. Many of them did not even bother to show themselves and had been sleeping in the tree, living in the virtual world.

Now that he had finally encountered something interesting, Barbani was overjoyed.

"I hope these outsiders have some ability. Let me have some fun."

However, just as he was fantasizing, something out of the ordinary happened!

The space around him suddenly shook, as if it had solidified in an instant. Barbani's speed plummeted, as though he had fallen into a swamp.

At the same time, dozens of points of starlight suddenly appeared in his vision. The next moment, dozens of huge blue and white beams of light came from all directions, attacking from a distance. Barbani was at the intersection point of the beams, and the dazzling light instantly swallowed his body.

"This is an ambush‽"

The intense pain of his flesh evaporating like a volcanic eruption instantly swept through every nerve in his body. Barbani felt that his body was dissolving, and his life force was rapidly flowing out. The power of the attack exceeded his expectations, and he was shocked and furious.

Other than the outsiders, there was no way it could be anyone else. Barbani could not believe that this group of outsiders had sensed his pursuit. Not only did they not escape, they even wanted to attack him!

Barbani was shocked and furious. Just as he was about to struggle out of the restraints, a red light suddenly appeared from within the dozens of blue and white light beams. The next moment, the red light suddenly expanded and dyed the light beams red. The output power increased exponentially.

The intersection point of the beam exploded like the dawn from a red sun!

Barbani's figure was sent flying. He was covered in wounds and looked like he was burnt. He looked horrific.

The lethality of this round of attacks gave him a shock. He did not expect that with his ability, he would be heavily injured in a single exchange. He did not even see the enemy.

The outsiders this time actually had such powerful strength!

"I can't solve this alone. I have to call for help!"

Barbani was about to take action, but at this moment, a glimmer of light suddenly appeared in his vision and swept across his body.

His body suddenly froze, and he revealed a blank expression.

Han Xiao, who was looking at this area through a remote device, raised his brows in surprise.

"The virtual purification worked?"

Han Xiao had set up an ambush at the place he had passed by earlier and used a bunch of technology from Jayz's treasure to conceal it as much as possible. These dozens of high-intensity light beams came from a special hovering weapon array. It was a Universal Treasure-level machine, one of the parts of the Mechanical Deity.

Han Xiao had originally thought that the pursuers might be a fleet, so he had planned to launch an attack after failing the ambush. However, he found out that it was only a single person. According to his understanding of the World Tree Civilization, this person was most likely a Beyond Grade A Super like the Holy Tree Emissary or the Ancestral Spirit. It was impossible for him to be one of the Five Tree Kings.

Without saying a word, he launched an ambush and obtained the other party's combat information through the interface. He secretly heaved a sigh of relief.

Barbani's level was far lower than his, and his energy level was around 53,000. He was only an ordinary Beyond Grade A, and even if he could borrow some of the World Tree's power, he would still not be able to fight back.

Therefore, after using [Virtual Purification—Restore], Han Xiao was prepared to kill it immediately. However, the combat information made him stop. The interface indicated that the Virtual Purification was effective!

"It actually worked!"

Han Xiao took a deep breath.

When he obtained the skill [Virtual Purification—Restore], he had suspected that this move might be effective on the World Tree, but he did not expect it to actually come in useful.

The mental network of the World Tree connected everyone. To him, it was like an enormous smartphone, processing, distributing, and monitoring the information of every individual. All the lives devoured by the World Tree had their thoughts rewritten. No matter how much hostility they had, they would ultimately be loyal to the World Tree. The negative memories did not disappear but were diluted.

[Virtual Purification—Restore] purified intelligent targets infected by a virus, and the nature of those life forms that had been swallowed by the World Tree would also change, becoming some kind of symbiotic relationship. Even if they did not have a physical body, they could still live in the virtual world created by the World Tree, similar to an artificial intelligence. Therefore, Han Xiao was not sure if this would work, but it seemed like his hunch was right.

However, Han Xiao was not happy for long before he realized a problem.

The Virtual Purification only temporarily restored the other party's original thoughts, but the other party was still an individual devoured by the World Tree. This connection would not be broken, so the World Tree could rewrite the other party's thoughts at any time, covering the Virtual Purification effect. This meant that this move might only temporarily wake the other party up.

Furthermore, this move could only be used on those enslaved targets. If the target was originally loyal to the World Tree, it was obviously useless.

Fortunately, this guy called Barbani was not a native race of the World Tree Civilization but an enemy that the World Tree Civilization had devoured during their universe wars.

"This is…"

Barbani was stunned on the spot. Countless memories collided in his mind, and the memories of his civilization being destroyed by the World Tree's iron hooves came back to life. He even remembered that after he was devoured, he had become an accomplice in destroying his civilization, and countless of his own race had died at his hands.

His twisted mind quickly corrected itself, and his view of things returned to normal. The long-lost hostility and anger gushed out like a volcanic eruption.

"World Tree! What did you make me do‽"

Barbani covered his head with his hands, his entire body trembling. It was a furious roar, but it also sounded like a sorrowful howl. The pain contained within made Han Xiao shiver.

However, right at this moment, Han Xiao activated the short-range teleportation device and appeared beside Barbani in an instant.

"Are you awake? Time is of the essence, and I don't have the time to waste with you. Tell me the secrets you know while you're still clear-minded!"

Barbani withdrew from his grief and indignation, as he immediately recalled what he had been doing before he regained consciousness. These memories would not be erased by the virtual purification.

Without further explanation, he instantly understood the intentions of this outsider and his current situation.

Without any hesitation, Barbani immediately told him the secrets of the World Tree that he had. After he regained consciousness, no matter who this outsider was, as long as he became enemies with the World Tree, he would be someone worth helping.

Seeing that the other party was so understanding, Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief and focused on memorizing the content.

Barbani quickly explained the important secrets of the World Tree. Not long after, his expression suddenly changed, and a look of struggle flashed across his face.

"They've noticed. Leave quickly. The people of the World Tree will arrive at any time… It's monitoring everyone and has discovered that I've regained my will. I can't resist it and will soon have my thoughts rewritten."

Han Xiao also saw that the duration of the virtual purification in the status bar was rapidly decreasing, and his heart skipped a beat. He knew that the World Tree had already noticed this 'uncontrollable' individual.

He released his grip and was just about to retreat when he realized that Barbani had taken the initiative to raise his hand and push him away. Immediately after, his entire body lit up with lights that seeped through cracks in his body. He was going to detonate all his energy.

When the light was at its highest point, Barbani looked at Han Xiao deeply and said firmly, "We're hopeless. No matter who you are, don't lose!"

Boom!

The next moment, a violent explosion spread out, and Barbani exploded, turning into bright fireworks.

Han Xiao was slightly moved.

The actions of this 'awakened' were far more decisive than he had imagined. Only strong hatred could drive him to make such a choice.

I might have underestimated this move…

However, there was no time to think about it. Han Xiao quickly put away the mechanical equipment and activated the short-range teleportation device.

After a while, a spatial rift suddenly appeared in this area and out extended the roots of the World Tree. A huge fleet sailed out and quickly turned from illusory to solid. Several Holy Tree Emissaries descended and checked the scene.

"The Information Form alert has just issued the highest warning, indicating that the most serious information leak has occurred!"

The Holy Tree Emissaries had solemn expressions. They had rushed over as soon as they received the alarm.

Not long ago, the World Tree had shared what it had seen through the mental network, causing them to all be shocked.

"Barbani betrayed us? How is that possible?"

"He actually leaked the secret!"

"What happened? How did the outsider bewitch him?"

"He has turned back into a seed. We'll have to wait for him to mature again before we can ask him what's going on."

The Holy Tree Emissaries could not understand this situation because no one had ever betrayed the World Tree, not even having the thought of betraying it.

At this time, more and more spatial rifts opened up, and roots extended out, sending batches of fleets and experts over.

Suddenly, the Tree King's cold voice sounded in everyone's mind.

"Kill him; don't let this outsider leave alive!"

Chapter 1321: Secret and Pursuit

In the bright star space, Han Xiao's figure was speeding away.

"So, that's what happened. Information Form alert…"

Thinking back to the information he had just received, Han Xiao's expression was grave.

Barbani had told him quite a lot of secrets, including the Information Form warning networks, high-dimensional information vision, and so on. Han Xiao finally knew how the other party had discovered him, and he could not help but have a headache.

Unless he possessed Information Form technology that surpassed the World Tree, such detection methods were almost impossible to solve. No wonder the three Universal Civilizations had exposed themselves so quickly. It was indeed difficult for outsiders to do anything in the World Tree Civilization's territory.

When he triggered the alert, it should have been because he had observed the earth yellow planet and the World Tree Root at a close distance. As an outsider, he had interacted with the World Tree Civilization's information gathering, so he had been discovered. That was why the Holy Tree Emissary had come to check, using his high-dimensional information vision to track the traces he had left behind. Even with the mark of Destiny's Child, it was not effective in completely shielding him.

It was like having an extremely strong sixth sense. Anyone looking at him would allow him to be able to sense the direction of their gaze, and it might even be able to allow him to pinpoint their position.

"This won't be easy. I don't think I'll have a chance to complete this mission…"

Most importantly, as long as the alarm was not triggered, the World Tree would not be able to detect it even if he left a trace.

However, now that he had been discovered, the World Tree Emissaries could follow the traces and track him. Under such circumstances, if he used the energy of Destiny's Child to encircle the area, he was worried that he would be discovered by the high-dimensional information vision, and this would make it inconvenient for him to even leave a Throne behind.

According to the system of the Information Form Alert Net, it was not impossible to avoid it. As long as he had the awareness to avoid the interaction of information and only flew within the barren universe, not coming into contact with anything related to the World Tree, it was still possible to hide. Just like when he first teleported over, there was no information entanglement, so the World Tree did not discover it.

However, this was easier said than done. At the very least, the alarm had already been triggered this time, so there was basically no chance to hide anymore.

As for the other secrets, Barbani had also told him some of them. Some of them were already known by Han Xiao, and some were unknown to him.

The most important thing to him was the ability of the World Tree to sense the external locations where there was information about it. The more people who knew about it, or the deeper the conflict between the two sides, the more accurate the directions to the explored universe would be. This was not good.

"Although the three Universal Civilizations hid the information, they still let a portion of their people know about this in order to explore in secret… If we don't take further measures to keep it a secret, the number of people who know will only increase."

Han Xiao's eyes twitched.

The more one knew, the easier it would be to sense them. The World Tree's anti-tracking ability was too troublesome.

It was a pity that this information did not contain the coordinates of the World Tree's main body. According to Barbani, he had never read any related information in the mind network. None of the Holy Tree Emissaries or upper echelons that he had come into contact with knew anything about it either.

Even so, the value of this intelligence exceeded all the results of the previous explorations. It was probably the biggest gain of this trip. Only after uncovering the various methods of the World Tree could they take measures against it.

"Luckily, virtual purification is effective. Otherwise, I would not have been able to obtain these secrets."

Han Xiao thought that he was lucky. The intelligence that he had now exceeded that of his previous life.

After witnessing Barbani's resolute action, he realized that the effect of virtual purification might be beyond his expectations. There were many foreign races that had been assimilated by the World Tree. If everyone received the same awakening through purification, they could all become potential spies.

The World Tree would definitely target this move once it was prepared. Once someone 'lost control', it would immediately rewrite their mind and cause the duration of the virtual purification to plummet. However, at the very least, they should be able to have some time for self-destruction. This way, the foreign experts that the World Tree devoured might not be of any use.

However, the emissaries of the World Tree would not completely die. Once one died, they would turn into a seed and return to the World Tree, falling into a deep slumber. The World Tree could consume resources and time to mature the seed, allowing them to reawaken and revive. The mechanism was somewhat similar to the Underworld, but there were also subtle differences.

The foundation of an Underworld Spirit's existence was its soul. By obtaining a physical body, it could recover its combat power. As long as the Hero Spirit existed, it did not matter if its body died because it was still 'alive'.

The revival mechanism of the World Tree was different. It was an information-type ability, and every individual was unique. Because of the World Tree's connection, the information was refreshed in real time. When an individual died, they would not be able to maintain their consciousness like Hero Spirits, and their thoughts would become dormant as though they had really died, turning into 'seeds'. Only when the World Tree replenished their nutrients could they be revived.

From this perspective, the revival of the World Tree and the Sanctums had similarities. However, the revival of the Sanctums only required the activation of the Sanctum and did not require additional resources and time. The revival of the World Tree required a lot of resources and time, which meant that as long as one died, they would not be able to revive in a short period of time.

Han Xiao could not help but think of the 'military barracks' of the strategy games he played in his previous life. The production units needed to be trained, and the stronger the unit, the longer it would take.

"The revival principles of the World Tree and the Sanctums are related to the information form, but there is a unique principle. What will happen if the Sanctums revive the expert that has been devoured by the World Tree first? Will the connection still exist?"

Han Xiao could not help but be curious.

If it was possible, the Sanctum Revival might be able to continuously take away the powerhouses controlled by the World Tree, causing the strength of both parties to even out.

However, the possibility of failure could not be ruled out. After all, the individual had a symbiotic relationship with the World Tree, so even if the individual died, as long as the individual's information form template still existed, the individual who died might be judged by the Sanctum as still alive. That way, they would not be able to revive and would forever be enslaved.

Furthermore, according to the mechanism of the World Tree, Han Xiao even suspected that the World Tree was like the previous owner of the Underworld, keeping the information form of his subordinates and not allowing them to enter the Sanctum. Thus, there was no way for them to revive.

Han Xiao pondered. "For now, I can only guess. I'll only know if I try it myself… Hmm, but it's not convenient to take the risk now."

Since Barbani was dead, Han Xiao did not want to take the risk of using the Sanctum Revival. If the connection between the World Tree was not broken because of this, it would bring many more risks. This could be tested after the war broke out. At that time, he would not have to worry about being discovered.

All kinds of thoughts flashed through Han Xiao's mind. After digesting the new information, he opened the interface.

The mission [Nowhere to Hide] that he had triggered previously had been completed, and he immediately collected the rewards.

A notification popped up on his interface, showing that he had received 210,000,000 EXP, two Random Reward chances, and a Barbani Character Summon Card. However, the card was an offensive skill and was not very useful to him.

Other than that, it also indicated that the Favorability of the World Tree Faction had greatly decreased. At the same time, a new mission was activated.

You have triggered the urgent mission: World Tree's Rage!

Mission Introduction: Your actions angered the World Tree, and it sees you as a huge threat. It has decided to launch a large-scale operation to hunt you down.

Mission Requirements: Face the pursuers and escape from the territory of the World Tree Civilization.

Reward depends on mission rating. Mission rating depends on the amount of resistance put forth while escaping.

Remarks: The moment you activate this mission, it means that the World Tree has remembered you. No matter when it discovers you, it will hunt you down. This will take effect permanently.

"Heh, I really poked a hornet's nest."

Han Xiao clicked his tongue.

It seemed that the virtual purification had left a deep impression on the World Tree, and it saw him as the number one threat. As long as he was discovered, the World Tree would immediately chase after him.

The mission itself was very simple. If he wanted to escape, he could just use the King suit to escape. However, the rating depended on resistance. If he completed the mission so easily, he would probably get the lowest rating.

He did not have a chance to complete his original mission this time, so he could only come again at some point. However, Han Xiao thought for a while and did not plan to retreat immediately.

Since he had been discovered, he might as well use virtual purification to obtain more intelligence and kill some of the World Tree powerhouses at the same time, allowing them to return to their seed state and temporarily reduce the World Tree's advanced combat power. It was a pity that he did not know what would happen to the connection between the World Tree and the individual after the Spacetime Amber sealed the target. He did not dare take the risk at the moment, afraid that he would be remotely located after taking the amber away.

"However, this is the enemy's base camp after all. There are many strong people here, and there are many factors that can threaten me. If I treat this too casually, I'm afraid I'll fail."

Han Xiao calmed himself down and took out bombs that were specially used to remove traces. As he sped forward, he set them up along the way.

This type of bomb could remove the usual traces of information form, other than the high-dimensional information forms, preventing the information form from being read by the Information Form Camera.

Setting up these bombs could also expand the area that the World Tree Army could not detect, which was beneficial to him.

…

Behind Han Xiao was a huge fleet in pursuit.

In the command room, a group of Beyond Grade As looked out the window, using the power of the World Tree to light up the high-dimensional information traces.

"The outsiders have begun to eliminate their traces on a large scale. The other party already knows about the existence of the Information Form Camera from Barbani's mouth. This is most likely a targeted measure… Send more people to search the area to prevent the outsiders from leaving anything behind."

The tall figure standing at the front slowly spoke with an unquestionable tone. Everyone present followed his lead.

Tedrian, a Nine Leaf Executive Officer, was in charge of this chase and was the highest ranked person present.

There were five Great Tree Kings in the World Tree, and each of them had two Executive Officers who were ranked from One Leaf to Ten Leaf.

The Tree Kings were usually in a deep sleep, absorbing the power of the World Tree to strengthen themselves. Therefore, these Executive Officers were the highest Executive Officers who dealt with the affairs of the World Tree Civilization. Not only did they have a high position and authority, they also had powerful personal strength. None of the Executive Officers under the Kings were below the pinnacle Beyond Grade A level.

Other than him, there were other pinnacle Beyond Grade As in the room.

"If we just chase from behind, it will be easy for the other party to escape. I've already informed some Holy Tree Emissaries to use their roots to intercept them," a person beside him said with a deep voice. This was a high-level Holy Tree Emissary. He had a deeper connection with the World Tree, as well as stronger personal strength. He was far from what Barbani could compare to.

"There seems to be only one outsider. He's very strong, at least at the level of an executive officer. Be careful not to let him ambush you," another person said. This time, it was an ancestral spirit. This identity was usually responsible for matters related to faith.

The person who spoke was not an ordinary ancestral spirit but a member of the 'Thirteen Ancestral Spirits'. This represented the strongest thirteen of the ancestral spirits, all of which were at the pinnacle of Beyond Grade A.

"Don't worry, His Excellency Tree King has been paying attention. If the situation isn't right, he will come personally," Tedrian replied coldly before looking back.

"Barbani was bewitched by others, but there are no weak-minded people who are following me in this pursuit. I hope all of you can resist the strange bewitching methods of the outsiders."

Everyone nodded.

Although the World Tree did not know the theory behind the virtual purification, it felt threatened when it saw the performance of Barbani through the mental network.

To be on the safe side, the people who were sent to chase after the World Tree were all individuals who were loyal to the World Tree. There were no 'outsiders' who had their mindset overwritten.

Chapter 1322: Guerrilla Warfare

Right at this moment, the World Tree experts in the command room suddenly stopped moving. The movement in their High Dimensional Information Vision suddenly split into seven and headed in different directions.

"The outsider threw out bait to confuse our tracking; they are trying to disperse our manpower. It seems like they have the intention to retaliate."

Seeing this, Tedrian narrowed his eyes and said with a solemn tone.

One of the thirteen Ancestral Spirits, Roxilian, stroked his beard-like small tentacles on his chin out of habit and said slowly, "In this case, we can only split up. We can't ignore any trail."

Although the High Dimensional Information Vision could see through 'Information Closure' and track the traces, it could not trace back to the specific details like the Information Form camera.

The World Tree still had its limits, so they could not immediately tell which one of the seven tracks Han Xiao was on. Only by collecting enough information samples could they differentiate the traces. This would take some time, and they would have to follow the trail and collect samples to lock onto the outsider.

If the goal of the outsider was to escape, scattering thousands of trails was a good way to mix things up, and it was enough to stall for more time. However, since there were only seven trails, Tedrian guessed that the outsider had not given up and wanted to fight back.

Even if the other six trails were just bait, they had to deal with them to prevent the outsider from leaving their troops or other dangerous things in the territory of the civilization.

"Then let's gather more people. Our reinforcements are very fast anyway."

The high-level Holy Tree Emissary Offerman nodded in agreement.

The group did not have any objections. In the territory of the World Tree Civilization, they could travel quickly on the World Tree roots. As long as someone discovered the target and shared their location through the mental network, the others would arrive quickly.

"Leave some people to act as mobile support troops. The rest will split up."

Tedrian nodded.

Not only were they chasing from behind, but they were also following the direction of the trails, allowing some troops to pass directly to the front and intercept them. After confirming the changes in the trail, they would keep on shrinking the range.

The troops of the World Tree were constantly mobilized, gradually forming a large encirclement.

…

A fleet followed one of the trails for quite some distance, and the Holy Tree Emissary on the ship focused on maintaining the High Dimensional Information Vision.

At this time, a message came from the mental network. The sender was the intercepting troop in front of this trail.

"There's no follow-up information trail ahead. We're turning back and heading toward you, narrowing the search radius. Be careful."

Hearing this, the Holy Tree Emissary immediately perked up.

They were some distance away from the intercepting troop. Since the trail ahead had been cut off, it meant that the target was likely within this distance, and it was very likely that they would meet each other.

"Be careful. The enemy is close," the Holy Tree Emissary instructed the crew. He carefully sensed his surroundings and was a little angry.

It was a pity that the Information Form Camera was of no use this time. Otherwise, they would have no need to be so careful regardless of what the enemy had planned.

After traveling for some distance, an alarm suddenly sounded on the spaceship's radar.

"High energy attacks detected. Shield activated. Please watch out!"

At the same time, beams of light shot over from afar, penetrating the fleet's formation and quickly destroying many battleships.

"Enemy attack!"

The Holy Tree Emissary shuddered, and without hesitation, he called for reinforcements through the mental network before immediately activating his energy shield to protect himself.

A small mechanical troop surrounded by golden Mechanical Force suddenly charged over from the distance, closing in rapidly and firing continuously.

In the High Dimensional Information Vision, the source of this trail was this troop, but the outsider did not seem to be here.

"It seems like the trail I'm chasing is just bait." The Holy Tree Emissary had a frustrated expression, as though he was regretful that he had not caught up to the outsider.

At this time, spatial rifts appeared around them, and many roots extended out. Reinforcements quickly arrived, and several Beyond Grade As arrived.

Seeing this mechanical troop fighting with the fleet, everyone knew that this path was not where the outsider was.

"One trail removed; there are six left."

"Let's get rid of these mechanical troops first. Let the Holy Tree swallow them and analyze the information."

Without any hesitation, they charged forward, planning to end the battle quickly.

However, at this moment, one of the mechanical soldiers suddenly self-destructed, and a blue psionic light burst out, instantly swallowing the surrounding mechanical soldiers. The light expanded rapidly like it would never stop.

"Damn it, it's Primordial Psionic Energy!"

The expressions of the World Tree experts changed drastically; they hurriedly stopped and retreated.

The encircling fleet also dispersed and turned to leave immediately. However, there were still some spaceships that could not escape in time and were swallowed by the Primordial Psionic Energy.

The larger the sphere of light was, the faster it expanded. All matter and energy that came into contact with it were assimilated, and psionic energy expanded continuously.

However, at this moment, spatial rifts appeared once again. The World Tree roots extended from the cracks and stabbed into the psionic energy ball and absorbed its energy rapidly like sucking a jelly. Only then did the psionic ball stop expanding and slowly shrink until it disappeared.

Everything that had been devoured by the psionic energy before was completely destroyed.

The World Tree experts who had run far away finally stopped, their faces ashen.

This was not the stable secondary psionic energy but the violent Primordial Psionic Energy and quite large at that. Although they were Beyond Grade As, they did not want to test the Primordial Psionic Energy's strength with their bodies.

The Holy Tree Emissary had a lingering fear in his heart, and he angrily said, "That outsider must have set up Primordial Psionic Energy on all the bait to blast the pursuers to oblivion. Tell the others to be careful!"

The news quickly spread from the mental network to their comrades. Every chasing team immediately became cautious.

…

"A troop has already detonated…?"

Han Xiao was speeding through the universe when he suddenly sensed the Mechanical Force feedback.

Not long ago, he had sent out six mechanical troops to split up. On one hand, they were to split up the forces of the pursuers, and on the other hand, they served to act as a ward to see the size of the pursuers.

The mechanical army did not enjoy the protection of the Destiny's Child's Mark, which meant that all their actions would be seen through by the Information Form Camera. However, after receiving the Mechanical Force link, the mechanical army would be able to share the disguise of the Destiny's Child's Mark and become bait.

Han Xiao had left some tricks with the bait, and the Primordial Psionic Energy was one of them. He did not mind spreading psionic energy pollution in the World Tree Civilization's territory. Planting mushrooms in the enemy's home would not only damage the pursuers but also wipe out his own troops, preventing them from being swallowed by the World Tree.

However, he did not count on the Primordial Psionic Energy causing too much damage to the other party. After experiencing the war in his previous life, Han Xiao knew very well that the World Tree's ability to devour energy was just as effective against the Primordial Psionic Energy. This way of dealing with the psionic pollution was much more convenient than the three Universal Civilizations' method.

At this time, Han Xiao suddenly felt something. He turned around and saw a spatial rift not far ahead from which a World Tree fleet appeared.

"Found him!"

The Holy Tree emissary leading this intercepting fleet was both surprised and delighted. He immediately sent the location through the mental network.

Seeing this, Han Xiao turned around to attack. Golden Mechanical Force was released, and a large mechanical army emerged, bombarding the fleet unreservedly.

With his current energy level, the destructive power of his mechanical army was already shocking. It destroyed this small intercepting fleet almost instantly.

The Holy Tree Emissary hurriedly dodged and defended, but he was unable to withstand the firepower of the mechanical army. He was riddled with wounds immediately and was scared out of his wits.

At this time, spatial rifts appeared around him one after another. The first batch of reinforcements from the World Tree Civilization quickly arrived, and Han Xiao sensed five Beyond Grade As' energy.

However, he did not care. His energy erupted as he charged forward. A portion of his mechanical soldiers quickly gathered and turned into a small Mechanical Deity, almost instantly arriving in front of the injured Holy Tree Emissary.

Splitting rays were released from the fingertips of the Mechanical Deity, tearing apart the defense of this Holy Tree Emissary in the blink of an eye. Han Xiao activated the device in his palm; a spatial shockwave shot out, temporarily freezing the target in midair. Then, he threw a punch at the horrified Holy Tree Emissary.

Boom!

Shockwave erupted. The accumulated power of [Charge—Endless Potential] hit the Holy Tree Emissary's body with full force. The powerful force crushed his muscles and bones, and even his cells instantly withered.

Green blood exploded in midair. This Holy Tree Emissary's body disappeared, leaving only bloodstains on the mechanical fist.

With one punch, his HP was emptied!

"You aren't even an S+ rank, yet you dare to block my path. Do you think I flew so far for nothing? Let's start this by killing one!"

Han Xiao grinned.

The combat information showed that this Holy Tree Emissary's Energy Rank was less than 50,000, slightly weaker than Barbani. He had moved quite far, and the power of [Charge—Endless Potential] had stacked quite a lot. Together with the focus fire of the mechanical army, he insta-killed this Holy Tree Emissary.

He did not waste any time and immediately changed his target. He led his mechanical army and charged toward the five World Tree experts who had just arrived. The upgraded Celestial Punishment Edge was unfolded in his hands and slashed. The surging psionic energy turned into a sharp blade.

"Dodge!"

Seeing how Han Xiao had insta-killed their comrade, the expressions of the five World Tree experts changed drastically. They did not dare take the attack head-on and quickly left the fleet behind to escape.

Boom!

The fleet could not dodge in time. The battleships along the path were crushed by the Celestial Punishment Edge, instantly exploding into fireworks. The fragments of the battleships were swept up by the blade, turning into hot lava that splashed on the surrounding spaceships and burned their shields.

Han Xiao used Virtual Purification on the five of them. However, the five of them only swayed slightly before returning to normal. They did not look lost like Barbani.

"Is the World Tree on guard? It didn't send foreign races to chase after me. It reacted quite quickly."

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, but he was not surprised. He turned his blade and locked onto the weakest of the five people shown by the combat information. He charged forward, scaring the other party so much that he turned and fled.

The other four people hurriedly launched long-range attacks from the side, trying to restrain Han Xiao. However, it was like scratching an itch. Their focused fire could not even penetrate the Mechanical Deity's shield; Han Xiao could not even be bothered to block.

At this time, more and more reinforcements arrived. When these World Tree experts saw this, they immediately joined the battle. The number of people surrounding Han Xiao rapidly increased to double digits, and it was still rising.

However, what shocked the many World Tree experts was that even though the number of attackers had reached double digits, this outsider was still able to run amok as though there was no one around. He ignored the damage and only attacked without defending. He endured the focused fire of so many people and killed an Ancestral Spirit that he had locked onto. This gave them the second casualty!

However, as more and more reinforcements arrived, the group finally managed to tie down this outsider and stop his killing spree.

Not long after the battle, Tedrian and the others also arrived on the battlefield on the World Tree Express. They immediately saw the Mechanical Deity, which was protected by a large number of mechanical soldiers, fighting dozens of World Tree powerhouses without being suppressed.

"This outsider's combat strength is too excessive!" Tedrian's expression changed slightly.

"Could it be that he comes from a civilization with extremely advanced individual strength?" Offerman was shocked.

Looking at the chaotic battlefield, Roxilian was terrified. "It seems like I was too conservative in the past. He's definitely at the level of a Tree King!"

The three of them had previously judged Han Xiao's combat strength from what happened to Barbani, but now, they realized that this outsider's strength was a little frightening, far beyond their expectations.

"The situation isn't right. I have to summon the Tree King."

Tedrian made a prompt decision and immediately contacted his superior through the mental network.

This time, the Mechanical Deity suddenly unleashed its full power, temporarily forcing back the surrounding people.

The next moment, the Mechanical Deity disintegrated and revealed Han Xiao. The mechanical troops around him shrank rapidly and were absorbed into his body.

Han Xiao looked at the situation on the battlefield. There were more than thirty Beyond Grade As who had come to help, and there were even a few peak Beyond Grade As. Under such circumstances, there was basically no chance for him to continue killing. Furthermore, the World Tree was still sending in reinforcements, and if he stayed there, he would definitely be kicked around like a ball. Furthermore, the World Tree did not lack top-notch individual strength, and the five Great Tree Kings were each stronger than the last.

He turned to look at Tedrian and the others and narrowed his eyes.

"Tedrian, Roxilian, Offerman… Hehe, they're all familiar faces."

During the war in his previous life, there were casualties among the experts of the explored universe and the World Tree Civilization. Han Xiao naturally knew some of the powerful figures of the World Tree.

If he did not remember incorrectly, all three of them had blood of Beyond Grade As on their hands in his previous life. The previous owner of the Spacetime Amber had his head smashed by Tedrian, causing this Universal Treasure to fall into the hands of the World Tree Civilization. Later on, he was killed by Karlot.

Just as Han Xiao was recalling, something happened. Another World Tree root appeared, and a powerful pressure far exceeding that of the others spread out.

The next second, a tall figure with an imposing aura descended. His long white hair hung loosely, and his eyes were cold. His entire body was surrounded by blue-green light, mixed with dark-red electric arcs.

This person had a light green mark on his forehead, shaped like a burning flame. He was currently staring at Han Xiao.

"Yo, here comes a strong man."

Han Xiao raised his brows.

One of the five great Tree Kings, 'Subduing Tree King' Saint Grace Bellandor, a Pugilist. In his previous life, he caused huge casualties in the explored universe. 'Dragon King' Milizaus and 'Beast Ancestor' Gorutan had both died to him. In the end, Karlot and 'Love Carrier' Silver Shadow merged and killed him with great difficulty, almost dying together.

In his previous life, during the war, he had personally witnessed the Subduing Tree King attacking many times, and he had even been killed more than twenty times just by the shockwaves. It had left a deep impression on him.

"If I can kill you, the revival time will definitely be quite long…"

Han Xiao had this thought, but after looking at the dozens of World Tree experts around him, he immediately dismissed it.

If it was a duel, he would not be afraid of the other party. However, in the enemy's base camp, it was basically impossible for him to do this.

At this time, the World Tree experts who had been forced back earlier were about to surround him again.

However, right in front of everyone's eyes, Han Xiao's figure suddenly disappeared, leaving everyone dumbfounded.

"How did he disappear? Has the space anchor lost its effect‽"

Tedrian was shocked.

In order to prevent the outsider from teleporting away, they had locked this space during the battle. Logically speaking, other than the World Tree Express, which was unique to the civilization's territory, no other teleportation methods should work.

However, he soon received a reply from the others on the mental network, saying that the space lockdown was normal.

"He actually escaped in this almost impossible situation?" Roxilian was unhappy.

"It seems like he has some kind of special teleportation method that can ignore a spacetime anchor… Then we have no choice." Offerman frowned.

The group was instantly discouraged. They had finally surrounded their prey, and even the Tree King had personally descended. But they actually failed at the crucial moment.

Tedrian had no choice but to bow to the Tree King. "Your Excellency Tree King, we did not do our job well and let this outsider escape."

The Subduing Tree King glanced at him and said indifferently, "He escaped quite fast. Otherwise, I would have given him to the Mother Tree to devour and grasp the location of this foreign civilization."

"Sorry, I ruined your plan. It's my… Hmm‽"

Tedrian was about to continue his self-reflection when he suddenly stopped, his expression turning interesting.

At the same time, everyone present received the same message through the mental network.

The pursuing troops that had gone to chase after the other 'bait' had suddenly encountered the outsider and were completely wiped out. The Holy Tree Emissary, who had led the team, only had time to send out a distress signal before the sound disappeared. He was dead.

Tedrian's face turned dark with anger.

"This outsider did not leave! He finished another troop!"

…

At the same time, at the location of one 'bait' mechanical troop, Han Xiao grabbed a dying Holy Tree Emissary and broke his head.

Then, he took back the Throne that this mechanical troop was carrying and smirked.

He did not just put Primordial Psionic Energy in these 'bait' teams; he had also given each team a Throne without caring about the losses.

This time, he did not bring much equipment with him when he came to the territory of the World Tree Civilization other than bringing many Kings.

After so many years, he had used his banknote ability to accumulate a large number of Kings, so he did not need to worry about them.

Throwing away the corpse, Han Xiao licked his lips.

"Indeed, we have to fight in other people's homes."

Chapter 1323: Using Force to Break Tactic

Just as Han Xiao was about to use the King suit to teleport and finish another fleet, spatial rifts appeared around him, and the troops that had surrounded him earlier rushed over again.

However, before Tedrian and the others could arrive, Han Xiao changed into another King and disappeared in front of everyone. This time, he was teleported to a 'bait' team that had yet to be caught.

When the Tree King, Tedrian, and the others arrived, they were only left with the wreckage of the fleet and the corpse of another Holy Tree emissary.

"Damn it!"

Tedrian was furious.

Even though the World Tree Express' reinforcement speed in its territory was already fast enough, they were still a step too late, allowing the outsider to kill another one of their companions.

The other Holy Tree Emissaries and Ancestral Spirits also had gloomy expressions.

High Dimensional Information Vision had locked onto the target. Everyone had thought that this outsider had nowhere to run, but they did not expect him to have such a method, catching them off guard. Although the other party's trails were still visible, he teleported to another bait team that had yet to be caught, so they could not immediately lock onto Han Xiao's position. They had to retrace the trails.

The three Universal Civilizations did not know much about the World Tree, but equally, the World Tree Civilization had even less of an understanding about the explored universe. This was also the first time they had seen the King's teleportation method.

"If that's the case, the outsider might appear in other bait trails at any time. The trails are dangerous, and it's very likely that the pursuing troops will be killed instead…" Roxilian's face turned grave.

When they thought of the outsider's strength, they could not help but feel a chill down their spines. They could chase after him, but it was hard to say who would be the unlucky one.

"This outsider definitely wants to use this method to chip away at our forces. As long as we split up and chase after him, there will be a risk of us being killed. However, we have to chase after him and not let this level of strength roam freely in our territory… Speaking of which, what kind of civilization does he come from? To actually send out a Super of this level to take the risk alone, could it be that this civilization has many high-level combatants of the same level?" Offerman said with unease.

When they thought about how the outsider was not only strong individually but also had this kind of powerful mobility method, most of the people present felt a deep sense of fear.

Just one person had caused them so much trouble, running amok in their territory. This was a provocation to the entire World Tree Civilization.

Originally, it was a one-sided hunt, but not only did the outsider not flee, he even treated them as prey. They did not expect to fall into a passive situation in their own territory. This was something that had never happened before.

After fighting in the universe for so many years, which hostile civilization would not make careful probes when coming into contact with them? They had never seen such an arrogant guy.

"… No matter what, we have to solve this problem," Tedrian said with a deep voice. "Wake up those guys who are not showing themselves and join the pursuit!"

For the time being, he did not think of a way to deal with the strange teleportation ability of the outsider. However, since the target of the outsider was to kill the lone troops, it was a good idea to increase the manpower of every pursuing force to restrict the other party so that he could not deal any damage before the reinforcements arrived.

However, Tedrian was very worried that the outsider would send out another batch of bait to force them to split up. Initially, he could have collected a high-dimensional information sample to lock onto the outsider's route, but the other party's teleportation method made it possible for every 'bait' to turn into the main body, so there was no way to tell.

With that, Tedrian turned to look at the Tree King and nodded. "Your Excellency Tree King, what do you think?"

The Subduing Tree King had been listening to the discussion and did not interrupt. He then said slowly, "Notify me when you surround him… Also, I will clear out this Star Field and lock it down. There's no need to care about the losses."

After saying that, Subduing Tree King turned into a turquoise stream of light and disappeared among the World Tree roots.

He had already made a wasted trip this time, and it was likely that he would not be able to get rid of the outsider anytime soon. He did not want to be messed around along with the others.

Hearing this, Tedrian and the others heaved a sigh of relief.

The planets in the World Tree Civilization's territory were not formed naturally. Instead, they were high-value planets that the World Tree had 'regurgitated' using Information Form. They could freeze the current evolution at any time, swallow it back, store it in the information state, and restore it in another location.

With this characteristic, the World Tree was like a mobile base, taking away the entire civilization and relocating its base in the universe to deal with all kinds of situations. It was almost born for war.

Clearing this Star Field meant letting the World Tree take back all the planets and creatures in this area. This way, they did not have to worry about the outsider wreaking havoc everywhere.

Only the Tree Kings were given this level of authority by the World Tree and could give such an order to the World Tree. The others did not have the authority to do so.

However, the World Tree could not leave as it wished. After changing the location of the base camp, it had to 'take root' in this area from the beginning and turn into its own information assembly points, 'fusing' with each other. Some abilities could only be used in areas after fusion, such as the World Tree Express, which could only travel quickly in one's own territory like the stargates. In other places in the universe, it was impossible to arrive as casually as now.

Ohm!

At this moment, spatial rifts appeared again, and many troops that had received Tedrian's summons came to reinforce them.

Among them were many high-level Holy Tree Emissaries and Ancestral Spirits who had woken up from their deep sleep. There were also a few executive officers who had arrived, as well as some high-ranking military generals who were in charge of foreign battles. The size of the group was snowballing.

Although the opponent was only one person, the World Tree gave him a very high level of treatment. An army of this size was more than enough for a universal war.

…

The pursuit battle continued, and ten days passed in the blink of an eye.

In the past few days, Han Xiao had been kiting around this Star Field to deal with the encirclement of the World Tree's troops.

He split up the bait troops time and time again, constantly using King's teleportation to cut through the pursuing troops of the World Tree. Sometimes, he set up a Throne, but sometimes, it was just Primordial Psionic Energy bombs mixed with fake ones. At the same time, he also used the King's positioning function to repeatedly warp around, making the World Tree troops suffer.

The King was like a god of guerrilla warfare. Using this tactic, Han Xiao obtained some results, killing six Beyond Grade As.

However, as the World Tree experts gathered, it became more and more difficult to kill the enemies in every battle. Every pursuing force had a sufficient number of experts, enough to restrain Han Xiao for a short while. In the blink of an eye, dozens of Beyond Grade As would appear as reinforcements. With the peak Beyond Grade As appearing, Han Xiao was forced to reduce the time of each battle, not daring to stay in one place.

Furthermore, the size of the World Tree fleet was too large, and they surrounded the entire Star Field. Han Xiao's guerrilla warfare range also decreased, and the time it took for the pursuing troops to catch up to the bait was getting shorter.

At the same time, Han Xiao also realized that the navigation star map had lost its effect. The planets in this area seemed to have disappeared, and he could not locate them accurately.

"Could it be that the World Tree swallowed all the nearby planets? To deal with me alone, it actually paid such a large price."

In the empty space, Han Xiao sped forward alone while pondering.

This was somewhat out of his expectations. Only the World Tree had such rich assets and did not care about such a small loss, resolutely clearing out the field.

After more than ten days of guerrilla warfare, he had already fought the World Tree experts almost a hundred times and met a lot of 'acquaintances'. Other than the Tree King, almost all the pursuers had fought him.

Although he did not get the chance to kill the enemies later, Han Xiao was able to obtain a lot of information about the attributes of the World Tree experts through combat information. He also learned about the specific abilities of many of his opponents, which was all extremely valuable information.

"My guerrilla warfare range is getting smaller and smaller. If this goes on, I'll be blocked very soon. Furthermore, I can't kill the enemy's experts now. There's no need to continue guerrilla warfare…"

It was true that the World Tree could not restrain the King's guerrilla tactics, but this was their base camp; they could destroy all tactics with their army.

Although guerrilla warfare was good, when faced with the overwhelming strength of the World Tree Civilization and the rapid reinforcement system, it was reaching its limits.

"Time to slip away."

Han Xiao nodded inwardly.

Although he did not complete the map this time, the harvest was beyond his expectations. Not only did he obtain a lot of important intelligence, he also sent several World Tree experts to heaven. This was more than he had expected, so he could retreat. It would not be good if he stayed.

However, before he left, Han Xiao wanted to find an opportunity to meet the Tree King and find out more about the other party's combat information.

…

"All the bait has been cleared, and there's only one high-dimensional information trail left. The outsider has not sent any more bait, so we can lock onto his main body."

In the command room of the main ship, Tedrian looked at the current situation; his gloomy expression that had lasted for over ten days finally disappeared.

"We've finally surrounded him. This outsider is too difficult to deal with."

Everyone heaved a sigh of relief. God knew how they had spent the past ten days. An outsider had disturbed their peace.

The number of World Tree experts participating in the chase was much higher than ten days ago. There were six high-level Holy Tree Emissaries, seven of the thirteen Ancestral Spirits, and a few military commanders and executives. There were about twenty peak Beyond Grade As with an Energy Rank above 71,000, which was equivalent to two-fifths of all the peak Beyond Grade As of the World Tree Civilization.

At this moment, a high-ranking general in a military uniform coldly said, "Don't be too happy yet. Since he has such a teleportation method, there's a high chance he can escape."

Hearing this, everyone was a little helpless.

They naturally understood this logic, but after researching for more than ten days, they still could not crack the teleportation method of the outsider. Their requirements had already decreased from killing the outsider to banishing him.

"Let's chase the outsider away first before considering what happens next. This might be the strongest civilization we've ever encountered," Tedrian replied with a frown.

At this time, everyone's mental network suddenly received a message. The pursuing troops had finally caught up to the outsider's main body and shared the coordinates.

"Go!"

The faces of everyone present turned dim. They immediately activated the World Tree's Express and quickly moved through the roots.

Not long after, they arrived at their destination.

The outsider was floating in space and did not attack the pursuing troops like before. The pursuing troops were waiting for reinforcements and did not dare take the initiative to attack. For a time, there was no movement on either side.

Seeing this, many World Tree experts turned into streams of light and shot out of the fleet, landing around Han Xiao and forming an encirclement. More reinforcements were also arriving unceasingly.

The number of Beyond Grade As present quickly approached a hundred, surrounding Han Xiao like a tiger eying its prey.

Due to the elimination of all the bait this time, the outsider could no longer use guerrilla warfare to trick them. Tedrian then informed the Subduing Tree King.

Boom!

The next moment, the Tree King's figure descended rapidly, and his oppressive might swept through the entire place.

"Your Excellency Tree King."

Tedrian and the many World Tree experts greeted him in the mental network.

The Subduing Tree King looked at the situation and nodded. "You have finally surrounded him. Why aren't you attacking?"

"This outsider seems to be fearless. He will probably use that teleportation method to escape our territory," Tedrian explained.

Just as the two of them were conversing, Han Xiao suddenly raised his hand and pointed at the Subduing Tree King. He then curled his finger; energy fluctuations increased steadily, locking onto Subduing Tree King.

Seeing this action, everyone present understood what the outsider meant. He was provoking their Tree King.

The Subduing Tree King looked at Han Xiao with an expressionless face. He casually raised his hand and waved it down.

"Get rid of him."

Chapter 1324: Escape and Fear

Ten minutes later, in a certain space deep in the secondary dimension world, a light suddenly flashed; a figure fell out of nowhere and landed on a boundless, white sea of sand. It was as if it lost its balance and staggered.

Han Xiao barely managed to stabilize himself. He took a deep breath and put away the dark gold King mechanical suit, revealing his body that was covered in wounds. Blood spurted out from his wounds and seeped into the sand. Very soon, the ground was dyed golden red. There were large scorch marks on his body, and his cells were dying.

"Phew… almost lost my life. One against a hundred is indeed too much. Ouch, it hurts."

A burning pain filled his entire body, as though every single cell in his body was screaming in pain. Han Xiao's face trembled slightly. He took out a syringe and injected a tube of highly concentrated life essence from Aurora into his body. A numbing and comfortable feeling immediately swept through his body, suppressing the pain and filling his body with warmth.

The pale golden light surged, and the wounds on Han Xiao's body quickly closed up, restoring his body to its peak state. There were only congealed blood stains left.

It was quite a close call just now. The combined strength of more than a hundred Beyond Grade As had exceeded his limit, and there were more than twenty peak Beyond Grade As, as well as experts at the level of the Tree Guardian King. However, he was fighting alone.

They were all Beyond Grade As, so even if his combat capability was off the charts, as long as he did not break through to a new level, he could not completely ignore the difference in numbers. Just the Subduing Tree King alone would be difficult to deal with, and he was the strongest Pugilist he had fought so far. Furthermore, he had the help of a group of experts.

There was no need to elaborate on the process. It was impossible for him to have the upper hand, and it was also an extravagant hope to ask for a draw. The combined damage of so many experts had already exceeded his recovery speed, his HP fluctuating up and down like a roller coaster. At the most dangerous moment, his HP had even dropped below sixteen percent. If it were any other Beyond Grade As of the explored universe, they would already have died, and even Wuornos with Church National Treasure would most likely not be able to take it.

However, Han Xiao did not plan to fight to the death. He had hidden many abilities, mainly to achieve his goal and obtain the combat information of Subduing Tree King.

Although the other party's level was higher and some of his attributes were question marks, many of his abilities were exposed. The value of the information was not small. If he met the Subduing Tree King again, he would have a rough gauge in his heart.

After receiving the information of the Subduing Tree King, Han Xiao did not continue fighting. He immediately changed into the King and left. He came to the temporary secondary dimension where the King's Throne was buried and escaped from the siege.

"With the secondary dimension as a buffer, it will be safer."

Han Xiao patted his chest, shaking off the bloodstains on his body, and changed into a new set of clothes.

Although the probability of King's Teleportation being tracked by the World Tree was very low, to be safe, he still used the secondary dimension as a transit zone and did not directly teleport back to the explored universe.

Then, Han Xiao took back the throne and left behind the secondary dimension destruction device, shattering this secondary dimension and allowing it to be devoured by the chaotic space flow, removing all trails.

After doing all this, Han Xiao opened the interface to take a look. The [World Tree's Rage] mission was completed.

As expected, the bigger the ruckus he caused, the higher the mission rating. He had already reached the highest rating, and the reward was quite generous. Just the EXP alone was 740 billion, which was more than the EXP he had gained from defeating the three Universal Civilizations. With a large amount of EXP, he was closer to the level 360 Promotion.

Another reward notification popped up.

You have received 5 Random Rewards and the milestone talent [World Tree Nemesis].

[World Tree Nemesis]: When fighting enemies of the World Tree faction, damage increased by 12% and a certain probability of triggering [Fear] status.

You have received 5 God's Trait Transformation Points.

You have received 1 Universe Legendary Point.

Universal Legendary Point: [Mysterious Outsider]—You have made a name for yourself in the World Tree Civilization. Countless people know about you, a powerful and mysterious outsider, and they are shocked. Your deeds are being spread around here, awing the World Tree, and able to make children stop crying.

"Sweet." Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

There was no need to talk about [World Tree Nemesis]. It was a faction targeting talent, similar to [Elderly Killer]. Although its effect was simple, it was quite useful.

Five God's Trait Transformation Points was exactly what he needed. It was equivalent to building five Universal Treasures. Currently, the God's Trait Transformation—Void had reached the thirteenth level, and he was just short of the last two points to level up. This windfall was enough to raise the God's Trait Transformation—Void to the fourteenth level and still have some surplus that would push him close to the fifteenth level. This reduced his workload.

Finally, this Universe Legendary Point had clearly left a deep impression on the World Tree Civilization, and they were filled with fear of him. The next time they met, the people of the World Tree should be able to recognize him immediately.

There was also the last reward notification on the interface. Han Xiao looked at it and saw that it was a piece of each Sanctum fragment. This meant that his level of authority in each Sanctum had increased by one level. This was the bonus reward for the highest mission rating.

"Yo, good stuff!"

Han Xiao was stunned for a moment before he was pleasantly surprised.

Sanctum authority was something that he needed urgently. The higher the authority, the closer the time flow of the Sanctum was to the main universe. It was a pleasant surprise to be able to level up the authority from the mission.

Suppressing his excitement, Han Xiao left with his bountiful harvest.

In order to be safe, he planned to travel in the deep layers in secondary dimensions for some time before returning to the explored universe.

In the World Tree Civilization's territory, the battlefield was a mess. The wreckage of the World Tree fleet was everywhere. Roots were sweeping the battlefield and swallowing all the debris.

In the command room of a flagship not far away, many World Tree experts who had participated in the siege surrounded the Subduing Tree King. Their expressions were solemn and somewhat horrified. A portion of them had injuries on their bodies.

Tedrian pressed down on the table and said with a surprised tone, "There's no doubt about this outsider's combat strength. He's one of the strongest individuals we've seen in our many years of fighting in the universe. It's unbelievable that so many of us couldn't even kill him… It's basically certain that none of us are his match in a one-on-one fight. Even His Excellency, the Tree King, will find it difficult to gain the upper hand."

Many of the World Tree powerhouses felt a lingering fear, and many peak Beyond Grade As fell silent.

Even the expressionless Subduing Tree King did not refute and only shook his head.

Facing the siege of more than a hundred people, this outsider actually dared to stay behind and fight head-on. This was already very shocking to them, but they did not expect him to still have the strength to fight back and even injure quite a number of them.

Although they had the absolute upper hand in the siege just now, this outsider was unbelievably tough. He endured the focus fire of more than a hundred people and held on for more than ten minutes before retreating with the strange teleportation method.

Although the enemy had been expelled, the strong performance of the outsider had been deeply imprinted in everyone's hearts, almost becoming a trauma. Every time they thought about it, many of them could not help feeling deeply shocked.

"Although we chased this outsider away this time, we can't guarantee that he won't come again. This is very tricky," Roxilian said with a deep voice.

Tedrian nodded, his tone grave.

"If we can't restrict the other party's special teleportation method, our territory will become the other party's backyard. He can come and go as he pleases, putting us in a passive position… We can't always clear out the Star Field and send so many people to chase after him."

As he spoke, his expression became even more shocked.

"Furthermore, only a civilization with extremely strong individual strength will produce Supers of this level. Who knows how many high-level combatants there are in this foreign civilization? We've leaked too many secrets this time. If they send more Supers of the same level next time, we'll be in trouble."

Hearing this, everyone was worried.

Han Xiao's astonishing combat strength made them make the wrong judgment. They thought that there were more experts of the same level in the explored universe, and they could not help but be frightened.

They had always been conquerors, and they were basically the ones who took the initiative to invade. However, at this moment, they felt a rare sense of fear, and they even had thoughts of escaping.

"Then, what do you suggest?" an Executive Officer asked.

Tedrian clenched his teeth and said, "This unknown civilization has already grasped our coordinates. My suggestion is to clear out all the Star Fields and move our base immediately. This way, we can avoid being harassed by them. Then, we will think of a way to find out more about them."

"This is indeed a method, but we can't use our advantage…" someone objected. "If we stay here and let the enemy continue to harass us, information will become more connected. This way, we will be able to locate this unknown civilization faster. "

Before Tedrian could speak, someone else interrupted. "I don't think that's possible. This outsider used some tricks to bewitch Barbani. Now that the other party knows about the secrets of these abilities, they will definitely avoid more information connection."

Hearing this, everyone had a helpless look on their face. The biggest problem now was not that the outsider was strong but that the intelligence gap was too big. Their side had leaked too much information, but they knew almost nothing about the outsider.

The group was divided into two factions. One side suggested migrating while the other suggested staying. Both started arguing.

Tedrian turned around. "Your Excellency Tree King, what do you think?"

Everyone stopped discussing. In the end, it was the Tree King who would make the final decision.

The Subduing Tree King closed his eyes and pondered for a while before opening them again.

"There's no need to migrate. The loss of territories is not important, but the information connection is crucial. Now that we have had some interaction, I will speed up the sensing speed of the World Tree. At the same time, I will inform the Information Form Foreseers to increase the frequency of the prophecies. Then, I will get the expedition team sent out in recent years to speed up their journey…"

Subduing Tree King paused before continuing.

"Also, strengthen our internal surveillance and set up more detection devices. The outsider has already obtained some of our confidential information. We can't just rely on the Information Form warning network… If you find the outsider again, inform me immediately."

Despite the calm expression on the Subduing Tree King's face, his heart was actually racing. Han Xiao's strength had also shocked him, but he did not show it on his face.

Although he did not say anything, the Subduing Tree King had already engraved Han Xiao in his mind and was looking forward to fighting him again.

It was because of the fighting spirit that was compulsory to a Pugilist. But more than that, the World Tree had expressed its desire for Han Xiao…

In the face of all new things, the mother tree had an extremely strong appetite. It requested that the Subduing Tree King send this outsider into its mouth as a tribute.

As one of the executors of the World Tree's will, the World Tree's request was his mission, and he could not reject it.

Chapter 1325: Cause and Effect

After staying in the deep layers of the secondary dimension world for a few days, Han Xiao returned to the explored universe and immediately visited the Holy Accord Organization to ask Destiny's Child about the World Tree Civilization's movements.

As he arrived at Destiny's Child's laboratory with ease, the staff around looked at him before lowering their heads and continuing with their work.

"You came to see me…"

Destiny's Child sensed something and turned toward Han Xiao. He pressed his hands on the inner wall of the container and let out a happy mental wave.

Han Xiao smiled and knocked on the container.

Destiny's Child noticed that the mark on Han Xiao's body had yet to fade. He tilted his head and said, "You didn't… set the area?"

"There was an accident, so I didn't have a chance to do this." Han Xiao shook his head and said, "I need you to tell me what the other side is doing."

"Okay…"

Destiny's Child did not reject and shared the information in the mental link.

Han Xiao quickly browsed through the images. He could almost see the real-time movements of the World Tree Civilization.

He soon saw that the World Tree Civilization had been stimulated by him during the few days that he stayed in the deep layer of the secondary dimension, and they were looking for clues related to him. They had also increased the frequency at which the Foreseers activated their abilities, indirectly increasing the surveillance of Destiny's Child.

His trip had left a deep impression on the other party. The reactions of the World Tree Civilization entered his eyes through Destiny's Child's surveillance, so he was not completely clueless about the developments in the World Tree Civilization.

Destiny's Child was the most important intelligence channel at the moment. Observing the real-time movements of the other party would allow him to make targeted arrangements ahead of time. Like two players in a real-time strategy game, one side removed the fog of war while the other side was still trying to figure out the opponent's position. The difference was obvious.

Seeing the World Tree Civilization's disordered movements, Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief.

At this moment, black flames surged, and Oathkeeper arrived.

"Black Star, why didn't you tell me before coming?"

As he spoke, Oathkeeper's gaze swept between Han Xiao and Destiny's Child. His expression had the feeling of 'you guys had a rendezvous behind my back'.

"I'm just here to ask about the surveillance. I'll come over more often in the future. If I have to tell you every time, it will be too troublesome. Just get used to it."

Han Xiao waved his hands.

Do you think you're the leader? Inspecting whenever you want… Oathkeeper cursed silently.

"Alright, that's all. I have other things to do, so I'll take my leave." Han Xiao nodded. Without waiting for Oathkeeper to speak, he changed into another King suit and disappeared in the blink of an eye.

Oathkeeper helplessly retracted his gaze and turned to look at Destiny's Child.

Destiny's Child also ignored him. Seeing that Han Xiao had left, he went back to sleep. There was no initiative like when he met Han Xiao earlier, as if he was treating Oathkeeper like air; the discrimination was obvious.

Seeing that Destiny's Child was not giving him any face, Oathkeeper's mouth twitched. He took a deep breath, suppressed his heartache, and turned to leave.

…

In the conference room of the three Universal Civilizations…

Marbruce sized up Han Xiao's remote projection and said with a confused tone, "Black Star, you're finally back. What took you so long?"

Louis and the church leader were also curious.

After sending Han Xiao away, they had thought that Han Xiao's first exploration would not take too long, but half a month had passed in the blink of an eye, and there had been no news from him. If not for the fact that Han Xiao contacted them, they would have been unaware that Han Xiao had returned.

In the past half a month, the three of them had been living on tenterhooks. Because they were unable to contact Han Xiao, who was far away in the World Tree Civilization's territory, they had been worrying every day, thinking that something had happened to Black Star.

Seeing that Han Xiao had taken the initiative to contact them, the three of them heaved sighs of relief. They were curious about what Han Xiao had done during his long stay in the World Tree Civilization.

"There was an accident along the way, and I was delayed. Let's not talk about that for now. I got some intelligence on this trip. Take a look."

Han Xiao waved his hands. He was too lazy to chat with the three of them and went straight to the point, sending the World Tree secrets that were revealed by Barbani to the three of them.

A virtual screen appeared on the table, and the three of them could not take their eyes off it.

"This… this is all information you obtained from this trip‽"

Marbruce's eyes widened in disbelief to the point of being stunned.

The three of them originally had limited expectations for this intelligence. They felt that since Han Xiao had gone to the enemy's headquarters, it would be difficult for him to move easily. Even if he did gain something, it would not be too shocking. However, what was with this piece of intelligence? It was all unheard-of secrets!

Information Form warning network, Information Form camera… a ton of important strategic intelligence. It was obvious that this was not information that could be easily obtained. Could it be that Black Star had hacked the World Tree's secret database‽

The three of them could not help but feel a little dazed.

How many times had they explored the World Tree Civilization? The best they could have done was steal some general information from the internet, but it was all superficial. Black Star had only gone there once, but he had already obtained an explosive harvest. Be it the quality or quantity of information, it was countless times greater than theirs!

The repeated explorations of the three Universal Civilizations were not as good as Black Star's one trip…

The three of them looked at each other with complicated feelings.

Black Star had given them a headache when he was their opponent, but he was extremely reliable when he was their teammate. If not for the confidential intelligence that Black Star provided, they would not have known how passive their three Universal Civilizations were.

Suppressing the shock in their hearts, the three of them focused on browsing through the secrets of the World Tree that Han Xiao had shared. Their expressions kept changing—sometimes grave, sometimes surprised, and sometimes frustrated.

Very soon, the three of them read through the information and showed complicated expressions.

"So, this is how we were exposed…"

Louis sighed. After seeing the Information Form warning network, they finally understood how the World Tree Civilization discovered them.

"This kind of technology is impossible to guard against. The World Tree Civilization's research standard is much higher than ours regarding Information Form." The Pope frowned with concern.

"Looks like Black Star is right. We'd better stop the regular exploration…"

The three of them looked at the intel and felt immense pressure. At the same time, they were glad.

It was all thanks to Black Star for stealing these secrets. If not, they would have continued exploring without knowing what was going on, and they might have suffered a heavy blow one day. Now that they knew about the World Tree's detection method, they would be able to deal with it.

Marbruce could not help but ask, "…Black Star, how did you get this information?"

The other two also pricked up their ears.

"Nothing much, I just fought them and interrogated some people… By the way, I recorded the abilities of all the high-level combatants of the World Tree I fought. I am sending the files to you."

Han Xiao did not reveal his ability and gave a simple explanation. After thinking for a while, he shared the intelligence about the World Tree experts with the three of them. The information recorded was not as detailed as the combat information on the interface, but it was enough to roughly understand the abilities and combat strength of more than a hundred World Tree experts.

Gathering this information was not for his own use but also to let the Beyond Grade As in the explored universe gain a basic understanding of the enemy so that they would not be caught off guard. There was no need to hide it.

Seeing the data of over a hundred World Tree experts, the three of them were stunned.

Damn, did you go to infiltrate or to fight?

Having fought over a hundred high-level combatants in someone else's base camp, your life is really full of excitement!

"Isn't this too radical?" Louis could not help saying.

Han Xiao looked at him and spread out his hands. "If I did not do this, do you think those secrets would fall from the sky? Don't worry, although I fought the enemy, all traces were cleared. My intelligence channel monitored the real-time movements of the World Tree Civilization. They did not discover anything."

Marbruce was speechless and somewhat moved.

"Black Star, you took such a huge risk to gather intelligence. Everyone will remember your contribution…"

From his point of view, if not for collecting strategic intelligence, Black Star would not have taken the risk to fight the World Tree experts, resulting in him being pursued. All of this was for the big picture.

The other two also nodded and sighed.

Han Xiao raised his brows.

Seeing that the three of them had misunderstood his motives, he did not bother to explain himself. He was more than glad for them to think that way since there was no harm in it.

"No matter what, this piece of information you brought has extremely high strategic importance. It can provide an important reference for our strategic direction."

The three of them sighed for a while before getting excited.

Whatever the case, the intelligence that Black Star had obtained this time had solved their urgent needs. It was more than enough to change their strategic deployment.

The three of them began to discuss the next step of the plan, asking for Han Xiao's opinion from time to time.

Hearing that the three of them had finally accepted the suggestion and decided to stop the regular exploration, Han Xiao let out a sigh of relief. He had finally convinced the three Universal Civilizations not to do anything unnecessary, and his trust level had increased.

…

Somewhere in the unexplored universe, two spindle-shaped, dark-green spaceships sped through the endless desolate universe. Their concealment devices covered the trajectory of the hyperdrive light.

In the cockpit, more than ten operators sat in their seats and worked. No one spoke, and the room was silent other than the operating sounds.

The cabin looked clean and tidy, but traces of time could still be found in some subtle areas.

Every once in a while, the World Tree Civilization would send out exploration teams in different directions in an attempt to find other civilizations in the vast galaxy. These two spaceships were one of them, and the crew could not remember how many years they had flown for. It was like they were silently wandering in the cold universe.

Suddenly, the radar that had been silent for many years made a sound.

"Unknown metal object detected, direction…"

The people in the room were stunned for a moment, but they quickly reacted and immediately controlled the spaceship to fly in the direction indicated by the radar.

The two spaceships dragged streams of light and turned around. Very soon, the object locked onto by the radar entered their sights.

Not far away, an egg-shaped metal cabin was slowly traveling through the universe while letting out low-power exhaust flame. Its outer shell was mottled and had traces of cosmic radiation erosion, as if it had been sailing for a long time.

The people present looked at the metal cabin on the observation screen and had the same thought.

"This looks like… an escape pod?"

The group of them turned on the vital sign detection device; the extremely high level of technology penetrated the outer shell of the escape pod, detecting the life signals inside.

The appearance of the life forms in the escape pod was quickly displayed on the screen.

Chapter 1326: Interlude

After obtaining the secrets of the World Tree, the three Universal Civilizations accepted Han Xiao's suggestion and adjusted their strategy. They would no longer send any detection devices to the World Tree Civilization's territory, reducing the possibility of an information link forming between the two sides, and they increased their investment in the secondary dimension expedition team.

Han Xiao rested for a period of time. With the help of the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device, he made another trip to the World Tree Civilization's territory. Because he had the intelligence advantage this time, he carefully avoided contact and completed the mission safely, obtaining the reward [Deep Within the Enemy Camp].

After that, Han Xiao did not continue to infiltrate the World Tree Civilization's territory and harass them. He also reduced his contact with the World Tree Civilization and stayed in the explored universe to build machinery every day. Occasionally, he would go to the Holy Accord Organization to check on Destiny's Child's surveillance. On the surface, he returned to his normal life.

In the short term, he did not plan to go to the World Tree Civilization again. Now that the enemy was prepared, he was also afraid of getting into trouble. Furthermore, he had enough intelligence for the time being, so Han Xiao did not plan to provoke the enemy anymore and concentrated on expanding his strength.

The unaware Galactic Society maintained the pace of normal life. As time passed, the buzz created by the news of the three Universal Civilizations acknowledging the Beyond Grade A Association's independence also gradually cooled, but it did not disappear. The dissatisfaction of the galactic residents toward the three Universal Civilizations settled down and remained in their hearts.

After the political position was written in the galactic laws, the Beyond Grade A organization had a much better life. No matter how complicated the civilizations of the various Star Fields felt about this, they still acknowledged this point. They treated the Beyond Grade A Association like they would treat a civilization and increased their cooperation with the association.

Initially, all the organizations thought that the Beyond Grade A Association would take action, but the association continued to develop as usual and kept a low profile, as if they were not the recent topic of discussion.

Whether the Galaxy was chaotic or not was up to the big shots. Since the top organizations did not want to do anything, the life of the Galactic Society gradually returned to normal. Time slowly slipped away in this atmosphere.

…

In the Flickering World, more than ten small battleships with the army's insignia slowly landed on the Kunde Race's planet no. 77. They docked at a parking platform with three large transport ships. The wind pressure kept blowing out, blowing away the tiny dust on the ground. Landing gears propped out of the bottom of the ships, latching onto the Magnetic Force Suspension Lock and stopping steadily.

The cabins opened one after another, and groups of Kunde Race members wearing the standard armor of the Black Star Army alighted from the spaceships. Leading them was a tall Kunde Race member wearing the special uniform of the logistics department. It was Barton, who had been imprisoned and released by Han Xiao.

There were already groups of people waiting on the ground. They took the initiative to welcome them, and both sides exchanged greetings.

Barton was used to it. He waved his hand and said, "The supplies have been delivered. Help me unload them."

His prestige here was very high here. When the people heard his words, they started to work. They unloaded batches of goods from the transport ships, loaded them onto the transport vehicles, and sent them to different cities.

Barton stood at the side with his hands on his hips. At this moment, a Kunde Race member wearing a robe walked to his side and smiled.

"How long are you planning to stay this time?"

"…Half a day at most. The army's logistics department has a very important mission. I can't delay it. I'll leave after sending these supplies."

Barton looked back. The person who had spoken was someone he knew. It was the person in charge of this planet, a feudal lord-type figure.

Over the past few decades, the Kunde Race planets had been freed one after another, but due to some interference, there was no unified regime. Every planet had a feudal lord, and they were only responsible for the affairs of the planet. They allied with each other like a union.

After tens of years of adaptation, the Kunde Race gradually integrated into Galactic Society and got used to the various rules and regulations. However, they were still very weak and developed slowly. The industrial system was not complete, so relying on Supers to feed them was still their main way to obtain various resources.

In the past few years, a large number of the Kunde Race members had chosen to join the Black Star Army and acquired various resources through working for the army. As the subsidies for the various planets were decided by these Supers, their status was extremely high, and the various Kunde Race Lords had to fight for the support of the Kunde Race Supers, forming a dependent relationship.

"Yes, the army's work is more important. I was thinking of hosting you properly, but since you don't have the time, let's postpone it for next time," the supervisor said.

"We're already acquaintances. There's no need to specially entertain me." Barton shook his head.

"That won't do. You're a famous person from our planet after all. Planet No. 77 has been developing quite well all thanks to you," the supervisor said warmly.

"…Alright, you won't miss out on the supplies for the next period."

Barton sighed. He knew what the other party meant.

A few decades ago, after he was pardoned by Han Xiao, he had joined the army without a second word, determined to support his race, and slowly climbed up from the bottom.

As he was a Mechanic, Barton joined the logistics department after passing the internal assessment. He was initially a low-level researcher, but after successfully advancing as a Super to Grade B, he was promoted to a middle-level officer in the logistics department. He was one of the highest ranking Kunde Race Supers in the army.

Due to his position, his purchasing of resources was discounted. Thus, Barton's position in the Kunde Race was very important and prestigious. Every planet's feudal lord wanted to please him, and he was already used to it.

"How are the thoughts within the race now?" Barton changed the topic.

Hearing this, the supervisor turned to look at his people who were working and smiled. "We have been carrying out ideological reformations. There are fewer and fewer radicals, and most people now yearn for peace."

"That's good."

Barton nodded and looked at the Kunde Race members who were full of vitality. He could not help but feel gratified.

They had a grudge against the Crimson Dynasty for destroying their homeland, but the difference between the two sides was too great. Barton had always been using his position to request the feudal lords of the various planets to strengthen their ideological education so that their descendants would not be influenced by hatred.

After so many years of hard work, the Kunde Race had finally taken a positive development path, and the radicals were rare, unstable factors. Who knew what kind of trouble they would cause under the influence of hatred? Barton did not wish for his race to be implicated by a small group of radicals, destroying the peaceful situation that was obtained with much difficulty.

Luckily, the past few decades had changed the minds of most people, and the number of radicals seeking revenge had decreased. Most of the Kunde Race were satisfied with their current lives and had hope for the future.

"If only we could maintain this peace."

Barton sighed in his heart.

…

The courtyard of Bennett's residence on Planet Aquamarine was like a transparent greenhouse, filled with rows of plants. Bennett walked among the plants, holding a watering pot and slowly watering the plants. He was wearing regular clothes like an ordinary old man, and it was difficult to tell that he was the leader of a civilization.

"Father, we're here to see you."

The sound came from afar. Nero pushed open the door while holding Mia's hand. The two of them walked into the courtyard.

Bennett put down the watering pot and looked back. A kind smile appeared on his wrinkled face. He waved and said, "You guys are here. It's rare for you to have the time to come and see an old man like me."

"Don't say that. Your body is strong; you will still live for a long time. Today is your birthday, so don't say such things."

Nero brought Mia to Bennett and pretended to grumble.

"He-hello…" Mia greeted shyly. She was a Calamity Grade Super who killed without batting an eyelid, yet she was so nervous right now.

"You're here too. Don't just stand there. Let's eat together today. Have a taste of my cooking." Bennett looked at Mia with a satisfied expression as if he was sizing up his daughter-in-law.

Nero had brought Mia to meet his parents before, and Bennett knew that Mia was currently in a relationship with Nero. He did not interfere with his son's choice, and he was rather satisfied with Mia.

Bennett brought the two of them to the dining room beside the courtyard before returning to the courtyard to pick some fresh plants. He personally went to the kitchen to cook a table of dishes and hosted them with a smile.

One was the leader of a civilization, and the other two were Calamity Grade Supers. The three of them ate at the same table, talking about family matters like ordinary people.

After chatting for a while, Nero took out a tube of medicine from his pocket and said with a smile, "This is the birthday gift that godfather told me to bring over. It's a life potion personally made by Her Excellency Aurora. It can extend one's life and maintain one's youth."

"Please thank Black Star for me."

Bennett smiled and accepted the potion.

"Godfather expected you to say that. He wants me to tell you that with your relationship, you don't have to thank him."

"Alright, that's his style."

Bennett laughed and shook his head. He then turned to look at Mia and smiled.

"What about you guys? Do you have any plans to have children?"

Mia's face instantly turned red, and her voice was as soft as a mosquito. "That… I don't have such thoughts for the time being…"

Nero scratched his head and said embarrassedly, "It's mainly because the higher the life level of an individual, the harder it is for them to give birth to a child. Mia and I have tried many times and used all kinds of positions, but unfortunately, we were unable to…"

Bang!

Before he could finish speaking, a shy iron elbow landed on his ribs, causing Nero to almost suffocate.

"D-don't talk nonsense!"

Mia flew into a rage out of humiliation and subconsciously gave Nero a loving elbow strike. She immediately thought of Bennett and quickly returned to her lady-like sitting position like an innocent person.

"…It's good to be young." Bennett wiped off his cold sweat. The elbow strike from a Calamity Grade had made his hair stand on end, and he could not help but look at Nero.

Dear son, you've worked hard.

"It's… it's fine. I like this kind of play…"

Seeing Bennett's complicated expression, Nero quickly defended Mia and rubbed his ribs for a while, feeling pain and joy together.

After coughing twice, Nero changed the topic and said with a serious expression, "Oh right, godfather also told me to tell you something important."

"What is it?"

"Godfather said that he might migrate everyone on Planet Aquamarine."

"Moving the entire Planet Aquamarine?" Bennett was shocked. "Where to?"

"He didn't say. He just wants you to be mentally prepared," Nero replied.

Hearing this, Bennett's smile disappeared, and his expression became serious. He rubbed his chin and pondered, trying to figure out what Han Xiao meant.

To suddenly migrate Planet Aquamarine, could it be to move into the territory promised by the three Universal Civilizations to the Beyond Grade A Association? Or was it an emergency refuge?

If he was talking about refuge, could it be that some kind of battle was about to break out? But wasn't everything going well?

"I don't think it's a good thing…"

All kinds of thoughts flashed through his mind, and Bennett was secretly worried.

At the same time, on a wasteland on Planet Aquamarine, Hila and Aurora were walking slowly.

Not far away, there was a huge crater with rubble obliquely inserted into the ground like fragments thrown by a violent explosion. It was the ruins of the Germinal Organization, which was now protected as a historical document.

The two of them had originally come to visit Ames, but because they had come at the wrong time, they had been chased out. Suddenly, they wanted to revisit their old place, so they came to the Germinal Organization's ruins to take a stroll.

"Do you remember? I was locked up here in the past. At that time, I thought I would never be able to escape."

Aurora picked up a piece of metal and played with it.

Hila looked at her surroundings, and the memories of the past came back to life. She softly said, "That's right. I did so much dirty work for the Germinal Organization, saying that it was to save you. In fact, I was just as lost, sinking deeper and deeper like a walking dead. If not for Black Star, I probably would not have survived."

After experiencing so many things, the two of them could finally face the painful memories of the past. Looking back at the past, it was like a dream.

Aurora suddenly laughed and said, "Speaking of which, Black Star was so young back then, unlike now."

"Humans have to grow."

Hearing this, Hila's lips curled up slightly. She remembered the time she tortured Han Xiao for more than half a year, and when she thought of the infamous Black Star, she had a feeling of joy at having seen the big shot at his weakest. Although they were not really childhood sweethearts, they were old friends.

However, Hila's smile quickly disappeared, and she sighed with complicated emotions.

Aurora turned to look at her sister.

"What are you sighing about?"

"… I was thinking, if I had chosen to go with him when he first entered the galaxy, maybe now… I wouldn't be late."

Hila had a complicated expression on her face.

…

On Floating Dragon Island…

"Are you leaving?"

"Hmm, when I rushed over, the machinery was only half done. I have to go back and finish it."

Han Xiao put on his clothes, buttoned up his shirt, and covered his strong chest muscles, preparing to leave.

At this moment, two fair fingers grabbed onto his shirt and tugged gently.

"Accompany me for a while more."

"…Alright."

Not long later…

On the other side of Floating Dragon Island, in Aesop's residence, the plates on the table moved slightly, and the juice spilled onto the table.

Aesop held onto the cutlery and looked at the corner of the ceiling helplessly. The wall was trembling slightly, and dust was falling.

"Sigh, it's shaking again…"

Chapter 1327: Navigation

Half a day later, a light green force field rolled up a set of clothes and brought it into the air. Han Xiao reached out and put it on. He rubbed his tired waist, came before a mirror, and rubbed his cheeks.

Ames untied her hair and ran her fingers through it, letting her black hair flow down like a waterfall. She opened the fridge with her force field and took out a half-finished bottle of hard liquor. She poured it into two glasses and walked to Han Xiao's side. She sat on the edge of the table and handed one glass to Han Xiao with a smile.

"Have a drink?"

Hearing this, Han Xiao looked at her and took a sip of the wine. Ames smiled, tidying Han Xiao's clothes and straightening his collar.

"You've been quite busy recently. I tried to look for you some time ago, but I couldn't reach you."

"When am I not busy?"

Han Xiao licked his lips and tasted the wine; the sweet and cold taste filled his mouth.

Ames took a sip of wine elegantly and said with a teasing tone, "Be honest, where did you go a few days ago? Did you go to the secondary dimensions with someone else?"

"Nonsense. I've only entered the secondary dimension with you. At most, I'll add Kasuyi." Han Xiao finished the wine in one gulp, put down the glass, and casually combed his hair with his fingers.

Ames shook her cup and said with a smile, "You can be considered successful now. You've won independence for the Beyond Grade A Association. The three Universal Civilizations have acknowledged your identity once again. Most of the goals set by the association are completed. You can relax now, right?"

"It's still early. It's not the time to relax yet."

"Why? Are you still not satisfied and want to continue climbing up?" Ames raised her brows. "You're already one of the top big shots in the universe. It's a little dangerous for you to continue climbing up. Could it be that you want to steal the position of the rulers of the three Universal Civilizations?"

"You're thinking too much. I'm not referring to that but some other things. There's still a huge threat that hasn't been resolved, but I can't tell you yet."

Han Xiao glanced at her helplessly. He did not reveal too much information about the World Tree, not even to those close to him.

"Alright, you always have big plans anyway… but you won't be so busy all the time. You'll have to stop sometime."

"If this matter can be resolved successfully, I should be able to rest for a long time."

"Then I'll wait. Don't go back on your word." Ames smiled.

"We'll see how it goes. If I am free, I'll spend more time with you."

Han Xiao casually chatted for a while and was about to change into a King suit and leave when his communicator suddenly rang.

When he took it out, Han Xiao was delighted to see that it was Aesop.

"Heh, it's the old man. His timing is really accurate."

Ames looked over and said indifferently, "He must have called you because the earthquakes stopped."

"Do you want to come along?" Han Xiao waved his communicator.

"He's looking for you, not me. He probably has some prophecy to talk to you about, so I won't be going. I still have to see Hila and the others later. Go see the old man yourself. I'm going to take a shower."

Ames waved her hand lazily and patted Han Xiao's butt before leaving the room.

Han Xiao shook his head and left Dragon Emperor Palace. He arrived at Aesop's house with ease and was quickly welcomed in by the AI butler.

The moment he entered, he saw Aesop sitting on the sofa and raising his eyebrows at him.

"You're out?"

"You're asking the obvious."

Han Xiao curled his lips, picked up a piece of fruit from the fruit plate on the table, and threw it into his mouth. He sat on the sofa beside Aesop, placed one arm on the back of the chair, crossed his legs, and casually asked, "Why'd you call me?"

"Don't make so much noise next time." Aesop sounded helpless.

"It's not the first time. When did you start to care so much?" Han Xiao looked at him strangely.

"I'm saying pay attention to the impact it causes. Every time you guys are done, the logistics department has to repair it. They even thought that Ames was training, and they've complained to me more than once. They told me to tell her not to keep causing trouble for Floating Dragon."

Aesop shook his head.

He knew that the relationship between Han Xiao and Ames had been going on for a very long time. Although Ames was his adopted daughter in name, he knew that this kind of private matter had nothing to do with him, so he did not interfere nor did he have the ability to. Furthermore, Black Star had always satisfied him.

As an Ancient One with a rich romantic history, Aesop was quite open-minded in this respect, and he was not surprised at all that Ames had hooked up with Black Star. In his eyes, the two adults of the galactic era had known each other for close to a hundred years, and their statuses were on the same level. They had experienced many things together and found each other pleasing to the eye. Sleeping on the same bed was just a matter of time.

As for the fact that the two of them were not married, it was not a big deal in Aesop's eyes. The old marriage system had gone out of fashion a few thousand years ago. Galactic races had long lifespans, and they lived colorful lives. Lifetime monogamy was a backward system that many galactic civilizations had eliminated. Now, the mainstream marriage contract type was usually the legal polygamy system, as well as contracted monogamy system. However, no matter which type of marriage it was, it was no longer a necessity for galactic residents. Due to the strong population circulation, the identity registration of most galactic civilizations had long been simplified. The household registration was very simple, and many galactic residents raised their offspring before marriage. The civilization gave them high subsidies and even built a public foster home.

Han Xiao was speechless.

"You didn't call me here just for this, did you? If there's nothing serious, I'm going back."

"I'm not that bored. Of course, I have business to discuss with you."

Aesop calmed himself down, threw away the distracting thoughts, and said solemnly, "I recently saw a new prophecy. I saw an ominous cloud looming over the galactic society, containing blood and fire, roars and screams. It's very likely that a disaster is brewing… Do you still remember my prophecy? Endless wormholes opened, and countless fleets invaded. The two seem to be related, and an unknown war might break out in the near future."

"Is that so?"

Han Xiao raised his brows. Aesop's prophecy probably referred to the World Tree.

"You don't seem surprised?" Aesop blinked.

"Since you saw a prophecy, there's no need to hide it from you. You must be very curious about the reason the three Universal Civilizations compromised so much. This is the reason." Han Xiao shrugged.

Aesop was shocked. "So there are enemies. This makes sense. The three Universal Civilizations had no choice but to unite their forces, so they reached an agreement with you."

"That's about it. I can give you some information. The enemy this time is very difficult to deal with. It might be the strongest enemy the three Universal Civilizations have seen in all these years. As for the details, I can't tell you for now. Just be mentally prepared," Han Xiao said.

"…So a universal war is about to break out. Sigh, the days of peace are always so short. If it's an external enemy, it won't be a small war. Who knows how many people will die then?" Aesop sighed.

As he spoke, his expression turned solemn.

"Black Star, if the situation isn't good, I hope you can leave with Ames. There's no need for you to be buried with the three Universal Civilizations."

"… How tragic was the scene you foresaw that made you so pessimistic?"

Han Xiao raised his brows.

Aesop said with a serious expression, "I'm just taking precautions. Remember, if the situation isn't right, don't walk down the wrong path."

…

In the Void Dimension, at Kasuyi's palace, Kasuyi sat at one end of the table, facing Manison's remote projection. On the table was a virtual interface of Wayne Cards. The two of them were playing cards and chatting casually.

Kasuyi casually threw out a card and slowly said, "Now that the association has an official position, according to Black Star's personality, he should strike while the iron is hot and carry out the next step of the plan. But he's keeping a low profile and has yet to start a new plan. This isn't like him."

Manison looked at his cards and casually replied, "Black Star definitely has his own plans."

"Recently, he's been acting mysteriously, connecting with the three Universal Civilizations. I don't know what he's doing. Speaking of which, the three Universal Civilizations' concessions are quite strange." Kasuyi crossed his arms.

Manison did not mind. "The three Universal Civilizations' choice is obviously due to pressure, and there are only a few scenarios where pressure would worry them. Based on the current situation, the most likely scenario is the invasion of the enemy. Black Star should have reached an agreement with the three Universal Civilizations to fight the enemy together. Let's just wait."

"Not necessarily." Kasuyi shook his head.

Because he had information about the Iterations, he thought more about it. Other than the possibility of foreign enemies, he also felt that the three Universal Civilizations might have discovered the existence of the Iterations and thus dropped the conflict. However, this was all speculation. No matter what, he supported Han Xiao's current actions.

Although Han Xiao did not reveal the truth of the World Tree, many Beyond Grade As had thought about it over the past few days and roughly guessed that the reason for the current situation was the existence of external enemies.

However, since Black Star did not announce it, many of the association members had a tacit understanding and pretended not to know. In fact, many Beyond Grade As were already secretly preparing for battle.

…

Somewhere in the unexplored universe, the World Tree exploration team's spaceship had changed direction and was moving at full speed in hyperdrive. The crew in the cockpit were all excited, and there were a few trembling old Kunde Race members tied up in the corner.

"After so many years, I've finally found some prey."

The captain stared at the coordinates on the screen with excitement.

After wandering in the universe for so many years, they had been searching for unknown civilizations alone. The universe was so vast, so their chances were like finding a needle in a haystack. To the long-distance fleet, this was akin to a punishment of exile, and they only had a harvest today.

Not long ago, they discovered an escape pod with low technology and captured the beings inside. Through various methods, they obtained information from the memories of these intelligent creatures who called themselves the Kunde Race.

When the dynasty defeated the Kunde Race civilization, there were batches of people who escaped through the escape pods. After many years of travel and some chance factors, some survivors left the explored universe, and this escape pod was one of the escapees.

The Kunde Race's memories of the explored universe were only at the stage of the war between the Crimson Dynasty and them. Because they were a native civilization of the Flickering World and had never integrated into the galactic society, they did not know much about the explored universe.

However, to the World Tree exploration team, the most valuable information was the coordinates recorded in this escape pod, as well as the navigation records of the past few years. This gave them a navigation target that pointed to the original location of the Kunde Race civilization, which was the Flickering World Star Field.

Due to the uniqueness of the World Tree mental network, every exploration team was a universe coordinate recorder that was connected in real time. The coordinates of every location would be sent to the World Tree simultaneously.

This meant that as long as the exploration team arrived at their destination, they would be able to obtain the coordinates of their enemies. After the World Tree base analyzed it, it would be able to use the wormhole generator to send a large number of troops over. The three Universal Civilizations had also used this method when entering the World Tree Civilization's territory for the first time. It was basically a spatial technology that the advanced civilizations used.

At the same time, the exploration team was also responsible for carrying out intelligence work. They would infiltrate the unknown civilization and collect information about the other party. The World Tree would only invade on a large scale if they knew about the other party's state. They would not start a war the moment they discovered their prey.

"I wonder what level of civilization the prey we discovered this time is. Could it be the nest of the outsider who recently caused a ruckus in our territory? Tsk, I have to be careful!"

The captain muttered to himself and was extremely vigilant. He had also learned of Han Xiao's battle in the World Tree Civilization.

If the coordinates were really the hometown of that brave outsider, the danger level would be raised to the highest!

Chapter 1328: Discovered

In a certain restricted military area of the Black Star Army, two large Mechanical Deities were clashing like interstellar beasts in close combat. With every clash, sparks flew everywhere, and shockwaves spread out like endless ripples.

Bang!

Among them, the black and gold Mechanical Deity with a thick psionic shield slammed into the opponent's abdomen, causing light fragments to fly everywhere. Taking advantage of this collision, it opened up a small distance; countless light beams shot out from the cannon barrels on its shoulders, condensing into a golden beam of light that pushed the opponent away.

The Mechanical Deity that was sent flying rolled in space for a while before quickly stabilizing its body. Its flickering shield blocked the attack, and it was not injured.

"You are recovering well."

The black and gold Mechanical Deity did not chase after him. Its body opened and closed like scales. It retracted its weapon and spoke in the channel. It was Han Xiao himself.

The other Mechanical Deity was Herberlon. Hearing this, he stopped, stretched his shoulders, and said, "This configuration needs to be readjusted. The power output is not enough."

After waking up to prove the existence of the World Tree, Herberlon repaired his body with Han Xiao's help and recovered his combat capability. He then added various weapons and equipment to form different sets of equipment, constantly adjusting his state of operation. From time to time, he would spar with Han Xiao to test the combat capability of different configurations.

"I think this set of close combat equipment suits you quite well. Just add a few more sets of reactor modules. Although you can't beat me, you should be able to fight on par with the Mechanic Emperor." Han Xiao smiled.

To him, sparring with Herberlon was a good leisure activity. After all, most Beyond Grade As would not be able to withstand his size, and Herberlon was about the same size as him. At the same time, he was also durable and could fight freely.

Although Herberlon had once been defeated by the World Tree powerhouses, the situation he faced was one against many. His strength could not be underestimated. After recovering his strength, he would be able to enter the first tier of the Beyond Grade As in the explored universe, and he would even be able to reach the top tier. He would be a great help.

Hearing this, Herberlon disarmed himself, removed a metal tube from the groove on his arm armor, and threw it to Han Xiao. "Another mutated carrier."

Han Xiao took the metal tube and sized it up. He sensed some special structures from it, nodded, and put it away.

Although he was now a living body Mechanical Deity, that was a cheap trick, and it did not completely replicate the uniqueness of Herberlon.

Herberlon's body was extremely strange. Flesh and blood life combined with mechanical life, and the mechanical parts that were assembled over a long period of time had a chance to undergo a natural mutation like biological tissues, turning into special equipment similar to Apostle Weapons.

A body like Herberlon was a treasure in the eyes of the average person. Any piece of it would contain a shocking amount of technology. However, Han Xiao only needed the mutation module; he made Herberlon dig out the mutated body tissue from time to time and give it to him for research. This was one of the rewards for testing Herberlon's body.

After doing all this, Herberlon asked, "How's your contact with the World Tree going?"

"Not too bad. I have obtained quite a few secrets now, so I'll temporarily hold back and accumulate my strength…"

Han Xiao briefly explained the process of him stealing the secrets of the World Tree, as well as his current strategy. This was the information that he said he would share when he invited Herberlon to fight the World Tree together.

Hearing that the three Universal Civilizations had gained an advantage in intelligence with Han Xiao's help, Herberlon hesitated for two seconds before saying, "The three Universal Civilizations are really lucky to have someone like you…"

If one were to ask Herberlon how he felt right now, it would be envy and jealousy.

The Karma Republic that he was in did not react until they were attacked by the World Tree Civilization. They were caught off guard and easily defeated. He could not help but envy the fact that the explored universe had Black Star. If the Karma Republic had Black Star's help, at least they would not have lost without any resistance…

Herberlon had mixed feelings as he said, "It's a pity that we didn't have such luck and did not have someone like you."

"Cough, it's not that bad…"

Han Xiao was helpless.

Why are you suddenly flattering me? Did I ask you to flatter?

Just as he was about to comfort, his communicator rang.

He took it out and saw Oathkeeper's message.

'There are new discoveries in Destiny's Child surveillance. Come quickly!'

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and immediately lost the mood to chat.

He casually bade farewell to Herberlon and teleported to the Holy Accord with the King.

His vision blurred, and he arrived at Destiny's Child laboratory. This time, Oathkeeper was waiting for him in the room.

"What's going on? What's the situation?"

Han Xiao looked at Destiny's Child and walked to Oathkeeper's side.

"Things have changed. Take a look."

Oathkeeper had a serious expression and was not in the mood to joke. He moved aside.

Han Xiao turned around and connected with Destiny's Child. Information flowed into his mind, and his expression changed.

"The World Tree exploration team got our coordinates‽"

This information was somewhat unexpected, and Han Xiao's mood immediately became heavy.

Destiny's Child's surveillance came from the interaction of information when the sub-bodies activated their foresight ability. This time, the intelligence that was caught was that an exploration team of the World Tree had found the coordinates of a new unknown civilization. The World Tree used all the information that this exploration team had as a medium for foresight and organized a large number of foreseers to activate their abilities. Therefore, Destiny's Child knew about the situation of the exploration team.

As such, Han Xiao saw in the intelligence that the World Tree exploration team had discovered a group of Kunde Race members, as well as the information they had obtained from them. The coordinates pointed to the old location of the Kunde Race civilization, which was in the middle of the Flickering World.

The surveillance intel showed the origins of these Kunde Race individuals. They were the survivors of the war. Although the refugees knew almost nothing about the galactic society, causing the World Tree to not know if this unknown civilization was the same group as the outsiders who were spying on them, the coordinates' exposure was a fatal matter. The World Tree would definitely investigate thoroughly before letting the matter rest. Then, they would be able to find out more about the three Universal Civilizations.

Han Xiao frowned. "For such a thing to occur…"

In his previous life, the World Tree invasion had been unstoppable, and they had come prepared. It was obvious that the exploration team had discovered the three Universal Civilizations long ago, but they had been secretly stealing intelligence and only started fighting when they were ready.

No one knew when the World Tree first discovered the three Universal Civilizations, but to Han Xiao, it did not make sense for it to be so early. It was most likely due to the butterfly effect. Due to his influence, the path of the Kunde Race refugees had changed, and they had unfortunately run into the World Tree exploration team.

Without the coordinates, it would be difficult to find something. If they knew the location, their efficiency would be multiplied countless times, not to mention in the vast galactic universe. The World Tree exploration team had the same logic. In his previous life, the exploration team had most likely searched aimlessly, finding a needle in a haystack, and coincidentally arrived in the explored universe. Now that they had the navigation coordinates, they could directly travel in the direction of the explored universe. The time to arrive in the explored universe would definitely be much earlier, exposing the three Universal Civilizations in advance.

"What do you plan to do?" Oathkeeper asked with a deep voice.

Han Xiao came back to his senses and frowned.

"If that's the case, I can only interfere. I can't let the World Tree find us easily."

Destiny's Child's surveillance showed the location of the exploration team. The only thing he could do now was intercept the exploration team halfway and try not to let the World Tree figure out the three Universal Civilizations' details. He would win some time and let the three Universal Civilizations mobilize their forces publicly, officially turning into war mode to face the enemies.

However, no matter what he did, the World Tree had already obtained the coordinates, and finding the Flickering World was a foregone conclusion. Even if he destroyed this exploration team, there would be a continuous stream of reinforcements.

"I thought there was still a lot of time, but plans can't keep up with the changes…"

Han Xiao shook his head helplessly.

He had finally managed to convince the three Universal Civilizations to follow his suggestion and reduce their contact with the World Tree Civilization, giving the secondary dimension expedition team more time. However, the unexpected factors turned out contrary to expectations. The Kunde Race Civilization had once been destroyed by the dynasty, and now, the refugees brought an even greater disaster to the three Universal Civilizations. It was like a cycle of fate; no one could be blamed.

Sighing, Han Xiao composed himself.

No matter what, it had already happened. He could only think of a way to deal with it and accept reality.

…

"The World Tree has discovered our coordinates?"

In the conference room of the three Universal Civilizations, the three of them received Han Xiao's intelligence and were shocked.

"As for the details…"

Han Xiao explained the whole story. After he left the Holy Accord, he had immediately shared this intelligence with the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations.

After hearing the explanation, the three of them looked solemn.

The three of them did not have any other thoughts about the Kunde Race escapees leaking the secret. At most, they would curse that they were unlucky. They were more relieved that Han Xiao had the surveillance channels to discover the World Tree's movements this time.

After all, they did not have the overpowered information network like the World Tree. If they were infiltrated, no one would be aware of it.

After pondering for a while, Marbruce said in a serious tone, "Black Star, I'll leave the exploration team to you… Everyone, from now on, we have to enter a state of war."

Chapter 1329: Interception

Somewhere in the unexplored universe, Han Xiao's figure appeared out of thin air with a flash of light.

"This is where the exploration team passed by…"

Looking at the coordinates, Han Xiao mumbled to himself.

The World Tree used all the intelligence of the exploration team as a medium, which naturally included the route of the exploration team. Destiny's Child also intercepted the detailed coordinates, so Han Xiao used the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device to enter the coordinates and teleported to this unexplored area that the three Universal Civilizations had never set foot in.

The exploration team had passed by this place recently, so they were naturally not far away.

"According to the coordinates given by the Kunde Race, the exploration team is heading this way…"

Han Xiao took out the interstellar locator, adjusted his position, and locked onto a direction.

With the navigation coordinates, the exploration team would most likely advance in a straight line. Therefore, he could confirm the direction of the other party. Although the exploration team was very fast and had already run ahead, he could use this method to give chase.

With a flash of his Mechanical Force, the gate of the secondary dimensional army camp opened, and a large number of mechanical troops rushed out. Han Xiao led a group of troops and chased after them in a straight line to the navigation coordinates, while the rest of the mechanical troops scattered in different directions.

This was partly to be safe, as they were afraid that the exploration team would take a detour. Also, their task was to set up a stargate terminal nearby. The three Universal Civilizations had set up a terminal on the other side of the stargate, allowing the two sides to connect.

This was related to the next step of the plan that they had discussed before they set off. Due to the World Tree's devouring mechanism, the three Universal Civilizations did not wish to start a war in their own territory. This would be too passive, so they decided to use the stargate to send a large number of troops to this area and build a defensive circle along the exploration team's route. At the same time, they would stop the World Tree's subsequent exploration teams and increase the difficulty of infiltration.

Between the defense circle and the Flickering World, there was still a large area that had yet to be explored as a buffer zone. Even if the World Tree broke through the defense line, it would not be able to immediately attack the territory of the explored universe. This way, the three Universal Civilizations would be able to bombard the area as much as they wanted with their strategic weapons. They would try their best to eliminate the World Tree's strength to reduce the number of enemies attacking.

These were all necessary preparations. However, from Han Xiao's perspective, an all-out war would not erupt just because of this. He had learned about the World Tree's habits from Barbani. Even if it discovered that they had built a defensive circle, the World Tree would not attack rashly. It would most likely take a detour and find a way to infiltrate their base to steal intelligence instead.

The World Tree mainly focused on invasion. It looked very aggressive, but that was not the case. After Barbani's explanation, the World Tree's biggest advantage was that it had an endless supply of troops and its amazing radar technology, which was its hard strength and intelligence ability. Why was it always able to launch an all-out invasion? It did not rely on brute strength but more on having detailed information about the enemy before the battle, understanding their weaknesses and accurately striking straight at the hearts.

As Han Xiao calculated in his mind, he brought his mechanical army and activated hyperdrive, turning into streams of light that flew across the galaxy. All of them were equipped with high-speed hyperdrive engines, and with the support of Mechanical Force, they were even faster than the exploration team.

After chasing for a long time, the two spaceships of the exploration team appeared in his radar.

"It's indeed in this direction…"

Seeing that his target had appeared, Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief. Destiny's Child was indeed powerful, or things would not have gone so smoothly.

The exploration team had activated a concealment device, but they could not avoid his detection, and he would not be easily discovered by a small exploration team.

Han Xiao had no intention of going up to communicate with them. He waved his hand and ordered a group of mechanical troops to set up a Space Stabilization Anchor to force the exploration team out of the hyperdrive mode. He then raised his long-range weapons and locked onto the two spaceships.

Not long after, the two spaceships of the exploration team crashed into the trap set up by the mechanical army. With a sudden jolt, their speed plummeted and returned to normal mode. Han Xiao opened fire without hesitation, and a thick stream of high-energy particles shot out from the muzzle and swept past the two spaceships.

The shields of the two spaceships shattered in the blink of an eye, and the bodies of the spaceships melted, disappearing without a trace. In an instant, both the spaceships and the personnel on board were annihilated. A small exploration team naturally could not withstand Han Xiao's attack.

Seeing that the target was successfully eliminated, Han Xiao shook his head, but he could not be happy. He knew that this was only the beginning.

Due to the connection of the World Tree's mind network, it was basically impossible to mislead this exploration team. Right now, the World Tree base camp definitely placed a lot of importance on the progress of the exploration team, so if anything went wrong, the World Tree would discover it. It was equivalent to the 'mainframe' having all the data prepared. He could hack the exploration team, but he could not hack the World Tree's main body. It was very easy to detect tampered data. By getting rid of the exploration team, he could only buy some time.

Han Xiao did not leave immediately. Instead, he gathered the spatial coordinates around him and summoned the construction team to set up the location.

At the same time, in the World Tree Civilization…

"…The mental network connection of the exploration team has been cut off. The members of the team have all been turned into seeds. They are suspected to have been attacked."

In the main hall of the Tree Kings, Tedrian stood under his throne and reported the situation with a shocked tone.

Due to the discovery of their prey, the World Tree Civilization had been paying close attention to the progress of the exploration team and had been communicating with the team telepathically. The moment the exploration team lost contact, the upper echelons noticed it.

"Enemy attack? Could it have been done by this unknown civilization? How did they discover the exploration team?"

The Tree King frowned.

At this moment, another Tree King sitting by the side laughed and slowly said, "It seems like this unknown civilization isn't simple. They either have a special anti-surveillance method similar to the information state alert network, or they built an outpost outside their territory… It's also possible that the refugees discovered by the exploration team were just a trap."

There were five thrones in the hall, each corresponding to one of the five tree kings. At this moment, three of the thrones were empty, and only two tree kings had appeared. One of them was the Subduing Tree King, and the one who spoke was the Heart Tree King, Minacho, a pinnacle Beyond Grade A Psychic.

After Han Xiao caused a huge ruckus, the World Tree Civilization entered a state of alert, and the Heart Tree King woke up from his deep sleep. Two of the tree kings were on standby, and the other three were also observing the current situation.

At this moment, there were still a few executives waiting in the hall. Hearing this, one of them asked, "Trap? Are you saying that the coordinates obtained by the exploration team are problematic?"

The Heart Tree King did not comment directly, instead casually replying, "The coordinates and intelligence provided by this group of refugees might have been specially forged by an unknown civilization. Their goal might be to lure the enemy in and lead outsiders into the trap they have prepared… After all, the universe is so big; we're not the only hunters."

The executives' expressions became more solemn.

The exploration team had only just discovered the coordinates when they were wiped out. They had no choice but to be wary of this unknown civilization.

In the process of conquering the universe, it was not as if they had never met a tough opponent. They had seen civilizations that were also focused on invasion, and they had always been on guard against such existences.

This time, Tedrian exclaimed and said, "That's not right. If this is a trap to lure the enemy, there's no need for this unknown civilization to attack the exploration team. This will only alarm others. They should be showing their weaknesses instead."

The Heart Tree King smiled and nodded. "That's right, so the possibility of it being a trap isn't high. This unknown civilization probably doesn't wish to come into contact with outsiders and is afraid of being exposed. However, their actions have also exposed some things… After the unknown civilization discovered the exploration team, they immediately attacked without any intention of capturing them alive. Isn't this suspicious?"

Hearing this, the eyes of many executives flickered.

"Logically speaking, if a civilization discovers an exploration team of unknown origin, there's a high chance that they will capture them alive and try to obtain intelligence…"

The Heart Tree King nodded and slowly said, "That's right, but this unknown civilization did not do so. Maybe it's because they're cautious, but it's more likely that they have intelligence on us and know that the World Tree has a mental network link, so they don't dare show their faces, afraid of being observed… Think about it, if they didn't know about our mental network, what are the chances of them destroying a foreign exploration team so carelessly?"

Tedrian was shocked. "So what you're saying is that this unknown civilization might be the hometown of the outsider who stole a lot of our secrets?"

Everyone's expression changed.

The psychological trauma that Han Xiao had left on them was not small, and it was still fresh in their minds. Just the mention of him made many World Tree members feel pressured.

"All of this is just speculation. As for what exactly happened, we'll have to verify it first." The Heart Tree King waved his hand and calmly said, "The next step is to locate the coordinates that this exploration team has recently passed by and reopen the wormhole tunnel. We'll send advance troops there, continue the exploration, and advance toward the navigation coordinates… Whether it's a trap or not, this is the only clue we have at the moment. We have to investigate it thoroughly."

"That was also my intention." The Subduing Tree King nodded.

The executives bowed in unison. "Understood. We will assemble the fleet now."

Somewhere in the Central Galaxy, a few enormous stargate devices were placed in the middle of the galaxy. At this time, the channel was not opened, so it only existed as a gigantic circular mechanical device.

In front of these stargate devices, there was a fleet that stretched endlessly. The armies of the Federation of Light, the Crimson Dynasty, and the Arcane Church had been waiting there for a long time.

These stargates were a set with the stargate terminals that Han Xiao had taken away. As long as Han Xiao completed the terminal connection, the two sides would be able to build an express channel.

After learning of the World Tree's existence, the three Universal Civilizations had been secretly gathering troops. Currently, most of the armies were on standby, ready to move out at any time.

While Han Xiao was dealing with the exploration team, the three Universal Civilizations efficiently gathered their troops and waited to set off.

"With Black Star's efficiency, it should be soon."

In the main flagship of the Federation of Light, the commander-in-chief, Simon, was playing with an antique replica pocket watch, looking down at the time from time to time.

The surrounding crew members all had solemn expressions on their faces, and the atmosphere was stifling.

At this time, the few stargates outside the window activated one after another, and a dark blue space vortex appeared within the ring device. Starlight sparkled, and it led to the exit on the other side.

Seeing this, Simon closed his watch and placed it into his pocket.

"All troops, move out!"

Chapter 1330: Public Announcement and Response

In the area where the exploration team had been wiped out, Han Xiao's mechanical army had already set up the stargate and activated the channel. The space vortex slowly spun, and not long after, batches of troops from the three Universal Civilizations flew out from the stargate.

Simon immediately saw the mechanical base floating in the starry sky outside the window. This was a temporary stronghold built by Han Xiao.

Simon sent Han Xiao a message. "We're here."

"I see you. Here is the exploration team's projected route. I'll leave the rest to you," Han Xiao replied casually before sending the intelligence to the various commanders.

Simon nodded. Without exchanging pleasantries, he turned and gave the order for the fleet to start moving.

The allied troops of the three Universal Civilizations immediately split up, and the construction team built the prototype of the defense circle on the spot. The mechanical army then followed the exploration team's route, setting up a space stabilization device along the way. Because the World Tree could only take coordinates based on the exploration team's route to open wormholes, the three Universal Civilizations' method was a perfect counter.

Looking at the three Universal Civilizations' fleets working in an orderly manner, Han Xiao nodded.

Although both sides had come into contact in advance, compared to his previous life, the three Universal Civilizations were in a much better position. The World Tree had yet to grasp their strength and was not prepared, so they could not invade from the secondary dimensions. Therefore, the three Universal Civilizations only needed to pay attention to the battlefront of the main universe for the time being, which saved them a lot of time and energy. Furthermore, they still had the upper hand at the moment, managing to keep the enemy outside their territory. The situation was quite good.

Everyone was engrossed in their preparations for a long time. Suddenly, a spacetime anomaly occurred somewhere on the exploration team's route, attracting everyone's attention.

A wormhole vortex appeared out of thin air. However, along the way, the wormhole was disrupted by the stabilizing anchor nearby. The process was interrupted, and the wormhole was destroyed.

"The teleportation of the World Tree failed."

Seeing this, many of the officers of the three Universal Civilizations were overjoyed. This was obviously because after the exploration team died, the World Tree had tried to send the next batch of troops. This proved to the three Universal Civilizations that their current plan was effective, able to successfully stop the World Tree's teleportation team.

This way, the World Tree could only choose to teleport to further coordinates and keep trying until it succeeded. At that time, the three Universal Civilizations, who were prepared, would naturally surround and intercept them.

Since the plan was effective, Han Xiao did not keep an eye on it. The three Universal Civilizations would be in charge of this. With more people, the efficacy would naturally be higher.

Leaving behind a Throne, Han Xiao changed into the King and returned to the explored universe. He still had many things to do.

…

After Han Xiao returned to the Beyond Grade A Association headquarters, he immediately called an emergency meeting. The association members received the news and all attended.

Ever since the three Universal Civilizations' ban was lifted, Black Star had not summoned everyone so urgently. In the venue, many Beyond Grade A projections landed on their seats and gazed at Han Xiao curiously.

Kasuyi turned and asked, "Black Star, why did you call us for an emergency meeting?"

Han Xiao looked around and said with a deep voice, "I know that all of you have always been curious about the basis of our ceasefire with the three Universal Civilizations. Previously, due to the confidentiality agreement and some strategic considerations, I did not disclose it to the outside world. However, the situation has changed. I can tell all of you that… because the three Universal Civilizations discovered a foreign civilization that lives on aggression and threatened the safety of the entire galactic society, they chose to compromise with us at the crucial moment. They hope to work together with us to fight against the foreign enemy."

Hearing this, the expressions of the Beyond Grade As present changed. Some came to a realization, some were shocked, and others remained unsurprised.

Many people had already faintly expected this possibility, so they did not show a great reaction.

Manison's eyes flashed, and he slowly said, "This is the deal that the three Universal Civilizations gave us for our independence?"

"That's right." Han Xiao nodded.

"How strong is this enemy?" Kasuyi was curious.

"Because of some reasons, it's not convenient to reveal the details for the time being, but the overall strength is very strong…" Han Xiao briefly described the size of the World Tree.

After hearing the introduction, many people looked at each other and frowned. They were afraid of the strong enemy that Han Xiao described.

"I never thought that I would have to fight alongside the three Universal Civilizations in the blink of an eye."

"The enemies are so strong. Can the three Universal Civilizations win?"

"Even if we win, it will probably be a tragic victory."

Many people whispered to each other, worried.

Dillon frowned. "In other words, we still have to work for the three Universal Civilizations?"

Han Xiao waved his hand and said, "It's just a deal. Furthermore, we're also the prey of the foreign enemies. We have nothing to do with the three Universal Civilizations."

"Bullsh*t! The three Universal Civilizations can't even take care of themselves, so we can definitely leave on our own. They won't dare stop us at this juncture, but aren't they using our lives to protect the three Universal Civilizations?"

Dillon was clearly dissatisfied. His hostility toward the three Universal Civilizations was very firm.

"If we join the battle, who knows how many people will die? Even if there's the Sanctum Revival, I think…" Beiger hesitated.

The majority of people there were willing to fight the three Universal Civilizations for the treatment of the Beyond Grade As because of what happened in history, but for them to ally and fight alongside the three Universal Civilizations, it was the exact opposite.

Among that group, the Revivors took the lion's share. They felt that since they could no longer enjoy the Sanctum Revival, losing their lives for the three Universal Civilizations was not worth it.

Protecting the people was not a priority for a portion of the Beyond Grade As. After all, the strength of an individual was different from that of a civilization. If they did not need to rely on the masses, they naturally did not have much obligation to protect them.

Now that the problem of the Beyond Grade As was basically solved, many of the Revivors had achieved their goal, and their mentality was inevitably going to shift toward being independent.

Han Xiao took in everyone's expression and said, "These are the terms of the deal. If we don't participate in the battle, the association's independence and status will be nullified."

Dillon snorted. "Come on. It's not even certain if the three Universal Civilizations can win. We'll be risking our lives to fight, but if the three Universal Civilizations lose, these agreements will still be useless. To us, it's a bloody loss… There is clearly a method to gain something without risking our lives!"

"You're right, but there are two sides to everything. This is also an opportunity. Furthermore, we were all born from this galactic society, so this is not the time to abandon our homeland. Escaping should not be the first choice." Han Xiao shook his head.

"Alright, let's assume that we've defeated the enemy. But what if the three Universal Civilizations take the opportunity to wipe us out again? Will we still have the strength to fight back then?" Dillon questioned.

"Of course, I've considered this. Don't worry, we won't be the main force fighting against the foreign enemies. The three Universal Civilizations will only suffer greater losses than us. By then, the association will still be able to retain enough strength or come out even stronger."

Dillon snorted coldly. "It's easy to say. I don't care about the others, but I won't agree. You want me to fight for the three Universal Civilizations? No way!"

Han Xiao ignored him and looked at the others. "What are your thoughts?"

Listening to the argument between the two, many Beyond Grade As had different expressions. Some were hesitant, while others remained calm.

"Black Star is right. This is a deal with risks and benefits. We're not fighting for the three Universal Civilizations but for our homeland. At least for me, I'm already used to living here. If it's not necessary, I don't want to watch the galactic society be destroyed," Kant said slowly.

Kasuyi nodded and said, "No matter what, it's too early to discuss escaping before the battle starts. I believe that Black Star's intention is not to fight to the death. If the situation is truly irreversible, with his style, he will not lead us down a path of no return."

"That's right." Secret Master nodded expressionlessly.

Other than the Revivors, most Beyond Grade As understood Han Xiao's actions. After all, not everyone was willing to abandon their hometown. Furthermore, as a Beyond Grade A, even in the face of a universal war, they still had the confidence to protect themselves and would not panic. Being scared away by the enemy was not within the consideration of most. Whether they could win or not would only be known after they fought.

Hearing this, Han Xiao nodded before looking at Dillon and the others. "The war has yet to break out, so you still have plenty of time to consider. The association respects the opinions of every member and will not force anyone to participate in the war… Of course, if you change your mind one day, I welcome all of you to fight alongside us."

"Humph, even if the galactic society is gone, I will not regret my attitude today!" Dillon snorted.

Han Xiao's expression was calm, and he was not angry. It was normal to have disagreements. He had already considered this point.

However, in his previous life, everyone in the explored universe was a soldier, so it was clear that most of them were upright. Furthermore, in his previous life, Oathkeeper had convinced many Revivors to participate in the battle at the critical moment. Clearly, it was not just because they were emotionally moved but more because the Sanctum Revival was used as a bargaining chip to move all the Beyond Grade As.

When the truth of the unlimited number to Sanctum revivals was exposed, he believed that these cold and aloof combat avoiders would come back knocking.

Han Xiao gave some instructions before announcing the end of the meeting. Everyone left with their own thoughts, except Manison.

Han Xiao looked at him and asked, "What do you have to say to me?"

Manison crossed his hands on his legs and calmly said, "This is a once in a lifetime opportunity. Do you want to reconsider my route?"

"What, you want to replace the three Universal Civilizations?" Han Xiao smiled.

"Can't we?" Manison glanced at Han Xiao. "If we lose, just pretend that I didn't say anything. If we win, this is a very good opportunity. It might be the weakest moment of the three Universal Civilizations so far, and the Virtual Mutiny Virus in our hands will come in handy."

"You still haven't given up. In fact, the things you want are even more exaggerated." Han Xiao shook his head.

Manison was expressionless. "When the three Universal Civilizations recover, they will still see us as a thorn in their side. As long as they stay on our side, we won't be able to have any true peace. Your method of checks and balances is effective, but isn't it better to solve the threat once and for all?"

"It's too early to say that. Let's focus on dealing with the enemies."

Han Xiao waved his hands.

…

To the citizens of the galactic society, this was a normal day, but on this day, the peaceful life in their eyes was easily broken by the galactic announcement issued by the three Universal Civilizations.

The three Universal Civilizations announced that a powerful foreign civilization was planning to invade the galactic society. The entire universe was to enter a state of war, requesting the Flickering World and many other Star Fields to begin mass migration.

This earth-shattering news swept through every Star Field like a hurricane. All galactic residents and civil forces who saw the news could not believe their eyes, thinking that it was fake news.

However, the actions of the three Universal Civilizations proved that this was not a joke. Large batches of official fleets forcefully migrated the civilians in the various Star Fields, and the various civilizations cooperated extremely well. Spaceship after spaceship of galactic residents of different races were sent to the transport ship, heading toward the hinterlands of the explored universe.

The recently renowned Beyond Grade A Association also issued a statement, proving that the three Universal Civilizations were not lying. They would fight against the enemies together and start to recruit Supers from all over the universe.

This series of actions did not pause at all. It was as if they had been prepared for this. The tension of the impending storm swept through the entire galactic society.

There had been no related news before this, and the situation had come too suddenly. It was as if a meteor had landed on the calm surface of the sea, causing huge waves. The public opinion exploded instantly.

However, one characteristic of the interstellar era was that the people were used to seeing all kinds of strange things. They were adaptable and could accept things fast enough. Although the period of long and comfortable life slowed down the reactions of many people, the majority of the galactic residents still quickly accepted the fact that a war was about to break out. They did not have time to think too much and quickly responded.

Fortunately, the conflict between the three Universal Civilizations and the Beyond Grade A Association had given many galactic residents an experience. At this moment, they were practically escaping without hesitation.

Without the forced migration of the three Universal Civilizations, most of the galactic residents left the border Star Field of their own accord, forming a huge migration wave. The public stargates were all jammed, and the fleet could extend to the end of their sights.

At the same time, the armies of the three Universal Civilizations began to move toward the periphery of the Star Field, requiring the majority of the area to start their war preparations.

In daily life, the various Star Fields were all living areas. Once a war broke out, the entire explored universe would be a strategic location in the eyes of the three Universal Civilizations. All Star Fields were war zones with different functions.

Chapter 1331: Scheming Against the Enemy

In the conference room of the Super Star Cluster Alliance, many leaders were discussing the coming war intensely.

Ever since the three Universal Civilizations issued the universal war mobilization, the leaders of the various civilizations had put aside their other work, treating it as their top priority at the moment and actively asking the three Universal Civilizations about their enemies.

However, due to the magnitude of the issue, there were too many civilizations that were eager to obtain information. The three Universal Civilizations only gave a unified reply and briefly explained the situation of the information entanglement. They said that they wanted to control the number of people who knew about it and that it was not convenient to publicize any intelligence on the enemy for the time being. Therefore, the other civilizations did not know anything about the enemy.

However, even if some civilizations were dissatisfied with the three Universal Civilizations, they would still follow the instructions of the three Universal Civilizations and cooperate with the strategic plan when facing external wars.

After all, the three Universal Civilizations were the rulers, and their determination to protect the safety of the explored universe was unquestionable. At the same time, they were also the pillars of the galactic society. None of the civilizations objected to the three Universal Civilizations having unified command during the war, and even the Super Star Cluster Alliance did not dare object.

A Super Star Cluster leader knocked on the table and said, "The invasion of foreign civilizations is not a small matter. For some reason, the three Universal Civilizations did not reveal the details of the enemy, but for them to put on such a show, it's clear that they have met a strong enemy."

"According to the attitude of the three Universal Civilizations, this time, it's most likely a mature Universal Civilization, not something those natives can compare to," another person guessed.

Everyone had a heavy expression on their face. This was not the first time that the explored universe had dealt with an unknown civilization. In history, there would occasionally be new Star Fields being developed, and the most recent example was the Flickering World. The Kunde Race war was similar, but the natives and Universal Civilizations were worlds apart. The intensity of the war was on a completely different level.

The Universal Civilizations in the unexplored universe were basically the overlords of a region. This was no longer a small skirmish when they were fighting the natives but an interstellar war. They no longer had a perfect chance of winning like they did when they were teaching the natives a lesson.

The three Universal Civilizations had put up a defensive stance in their base camp, so it was obviously not the side that took the initiative to attack. It was most likely the side that was invaded, which made the heads of the Super Star Cluster Civilizations feel that something was wrong. No one wanted to start a war in their own territory, and even if they won, their territory would suffer a huge loss. However, the three Universal Civilizations had chosen a defensive strategy, which proved that they were likely at a disadvantage, so they could only passively resist the other party's invasion.

"The conservative strategy of the three Universal Civilizations has exposed their lack of confidence. We should prepare a path of retreat. If the three Universal Civilizations become losers, we must think of a way to protect our civilizations," the leader of the Star Arc Civilization said.

In the eyes of the upper echelons, nothing was inevitable. They would never believe that the three Universal Civilizations could not be defeated or destroyed. They had to consider every possibility and plan ahead.

"It's a pity that the three Universal Civilizations will not disclose information about this foreign enemy. We can't analyze the other party's social status, political orientation, and attitude toward the outside world…" Someone shook his head.

"It seems like we can only wait until the war starts before we know the situation of this foreign civilization. Only then can we make a decision based on the actual situation. Before that, we can only arrange our own 'life tinder' storages," the leader of the Star Arc Civilization replied.

After discussing for a while, one of the Modo Three Kings suddenly spoke in a low voice.

"Speaking of which, this might be our chance to break the stalemate."

Hearing this, the eyes of many Super Star Cluster leaders flickered.

They stayed in the explored universe and had always been restricted by the three Universal Civilizations. Only external forces could help them break the balance. Their previous attempt to enter the Flickering World had failed, and although the Beyond Grade A Association had potential, it did not seem to be of much use now. However, external enemies were the biggest variable, and it was an opportunity to change the situation.

The Star Arc Civilization leader rubbed his chin and slowly said, "The most ideal situation would be for the three Universal Civilizations and the foreign civilizations to both suffer. We would then take over and rule the galactic society.

"Of course, they will be wary of us. If this path doesn't work, we can take the opportunity to evacuate. The three Universal Civilizations won't have the strength to stop us. We can bring our civilization to a faraway place and become the new rulers there. We can enjoy the resources and develop freely. We won't be restricted and suppressed like today."

Everyone's eyes lit up.

As the saying went, they would rather be a chicken's head than a phoenix's tail. The Super Star Cluster Alliance had been the number two for too long, and they had been beaten up by the three Universal Civilizations every day. If there was no outside interference, they would never have the chance to turn the tables and would forever be positioned below the three Universal Civilizations.

If they could get rid of the restrictions, then migrating to the enemy would also be a choice.

At this moment, the Star Arc Civilization leader changed the topic.

"However, without the enemy's intelligence, it's not suitable for us to make a decision… The three Universal Civilizations will most likely be wary of us and force us to be the main force. This will reduce our strength and cause us to be less of a threat. Therefore, we still have to see how the war goes."

All the leaders nodded with subtle expressions.

Since the enemy had yet to arrive, it was impossible for the civilizations to be united.

The war was sudden, and the announcement of the three Universal Civilizations spread throughout the galaxy. This also shocked the players, and their reactions were intense.

"Suddenly going to war? I haven't even brushed my teeth!"

"Isn't the main storyline the rise of a Beyond Grade A nation? Why did it suddenly become a galactic war?"

"Tsk, I got the main storyline wrong again. I really can't guess this version!"

"Actually, all of this is possible, but the level of intelligence we have access to is not high enough. We can't get any inside information and can only analyze the surface."

Many players on the forums were shocked, but shortly after, most of them became excited.

War? That's good! I can participate in the main storyline again!

As a group that wanted to see the world in chaos, the players welcomed war. After the three Universal Civilizations and the association became good friends again, many players could only operate the black markets to farm daily necessities. Although they were very free, they did not have a main storyline goal, so they were still overly idle and dying of boredom.

Now that a universal war was about to break out, it might be the largest war they had ever seen. Most of the players could not wait to participate.

Coincidentally, Han Xiao also issued a recruitment order to the army players, gathering all the combat-ready soldiers of the army to await orders in the Flickering World.

At Black Star's call, almost all the players in the army responded, dropping the black market mission in their hands and gathering at Black Star Palace.

At the border stargate station of the Dawn Star Cluster, the diverse civilian spaceships lined up in front of the stargate and entered in batches under the supervision of the Crimson Dynasty fleet. These were all galactic residents who had responded to the migration and were leaving the Flickering World on a large scale.

Practically all the galactic travel companies assisted in the migration, mobilizing their spaceships to transport batch after batch of galactic residents out of the country. Not only did they respond to the call, but they also took the opportunity to make a huge profit.

Currently, all galactic flights did not care about comfort, only the number of passengers. Unless they chose VIP cabins that were many times more expensive, they could not expect any special treatment.

In a large travel ship, countless galactic residents were squeezed into the main hall of the ship, and all kinds of races could be seen there. These were all ordinary passengers, and most of them were chatting with their companions. There were many worried people, and the main hall was extremely noisy.

"The recent disturbances have been too frequent. Those rulers have been creating trouble for us, and now we can't even rest in peace," one universal human could not help but complain.

One of the people beside him said with a dissatisfied expression, "Who says so? Some time ago, the three Universal Civilizations confronted the Beyond Grade A Association, and I thought that something big was going to happen. It was not easy to get rid of the storm, and now there's going to be a war. How annoying."

"Since it has already happened, let's not complain too much." A well-dressed passenger sighed and said, "I only hope that this migration will ensure our safety."

"As long as the three Universal Civilizations can stop the enemy at the border Star Field, we shouldn't have to worry. No matter how fierce the battle is, it won't threaten us," another passenger said.

"It's hard to say. In the past, when we encountered foreign civilizations, the three Universal Civilizations did not order us to migrate on a large scale. The enemy this time is probably very strong. I hope the three Universal Civilizations can be more reliable. Otherwise, the inner Star Fields won't be safe either," someone said worriedly.

The cabin was filled with anxiety, and the more they chatted, the more worried they became.

Other than personal safety concerns, many people were worried about their lives.

"The people from the border Star Fields have all migrated to the inner Star Fields. It will be crowded, and living resources will be more scarce. The prices will definitely increase…"

"Sigh, it wasn't easy for me to build up some savings. I don't know how long I can last. I hope my job opportunities won't be affected. As long as I don't go to the frontlines, I'm willing to do anything."

Many passengers sighed.

At this moment, something happened outside the window, attracting everyone's attention.

There was a long queue in front of the stargate, and the neighboring stargate was deserted. However, at this time, a fleet of ships suddenly sailed out from the stargate and arrived in the Flickering World. The armor of the ships had the insignia belonging to different Beyond Grade A organizations.

The next moment, these fleets turned into dense streams of light and headed in the opposite direction of the refugee fleet, heading toward the war zone.

"Are those the fleet from the Beyond Grade A Association?"

As the passengers watched the fleet disappear from their sights, some of them suddenly had a strange expression.

Among the crowd, there were some galactic residents who had criticized the association online during the confrontation between the three Universal Civilizations and the association. Seeing this scene, their emotions were complicated.

In the intercept area, a large number of mechanical strongholds were lined up in the starry sky, and the orbit formed by the Space Stabilization Anchor extended out, covering the route of the World Tree exploration team.

The efficiency of the three Universal Civilizations was astonishing, and it did not take long for them to form a defensive circle, forming a war zone as the frontline to intercept the World Tree.

In the past few days, the three Universal Civilizations had been setting up a space stabilization orbit along the exploration team's route all day long. The range was getting larger and larger, and they had already discovered that the World Tree had tried to form wormholes in different locations many times, but it had been disrupted by the space stabilization anchors and ultimately failed.

In the temporary base, Simon and the other commanders stayed in the combat staff room and spoke softly before the tactical star map while Han Xiao and many Beyond Grade As listened from the side.

After the meeting, Han Xiao brought Kasuyi, Kant, and the rest of the Beyond Grade As to the intercept area. They took charge while understanding the current situation.

The Flickering World had many Beyond Grade A organizations' territories, and they were already preparing for war. With so many officers, there was no need for them to keep an eye on them.

Other than the association members, there were also many Beyond Grade As from the direct line of descent of the three Universal Civilizations present. They were also there to prevent the World Tree from sending Beyond Grade As.

Simon pointed at the star map and solemnly said, "According to the statistics, the other party has already attempted to open the wormhole channel five times. The coordinates are getting further and further away, and the last time, they approached the edge of a stable space orbit.

"The coordinates that the other party will choose next should be a long distance away. It might be outside our observation range… The defense circle is not complete yet. Black Star, we still need your help."

"I'll try my best."

Han Xiao nodded.

Setting up a space stabilization orbit would only buy some time, and the teleportation location of the World Tree would be far away from the defense circle. However, it would not be able to cover the route that the exploration team had left behind over countless years. As long as the World Tree moved the teleportation coordinates far enough, it would sooner or later teleport a new exploration team over.

If the new World Tree exploration team was outside of their observation range, it would be more troublesome. The other party could take a large detour, and the defense circle of the three Universal Civilizations had yet to be completely built, so the probability of intercepting them was limited. The best way now was to rely on Destiny's Child's intelligence channel to locate the subsequent exploration team's location and target it to prevent anyone from escaping.

The premise was that its sub-body on the World Tree side had grasped this information, or else Destiny's Child would not be able to obtain the location. Luckily, this channel was very hidden, and the World Tree side should not be aware of its own information leak. They would still use the power of the sub-body to solve the problems for the exploration team.

Beep beep beep…

At this time, Han Xiao's communicator suddenly rang.

The room immediately fell silent. Everyone stopped talking and looked at Han Xiao.

Han Xiao took out his communicator. It was a message from Oathkeeper.

After reading the content, his eyes flashed.

"The World Tree has successfully opened the wormhole, and the new exploration team has arrived. It's four days away from the most stable spatial node… Everyone, we have to fight them."

Hearing this, everyone's pupils constricted.

Although they were mentally prepared, they were still in a heavy mood upon hearing that they would officially fight the World Tree troops. Han Xiao was the only one in the room who could treat this calmly.

Chapter 1332: Encounter and Adjustment

In the vast starry sky, a spatial fold appeared out of thin air; it started to spin faster and faster, quickly turning into a wormhole. Hundreds of thousands of World Tree battleships sailed out.

"Finally."

In the command room of the main ship, a creature that looked like a stick insect stood with his arms crossed and spoke in a gleeful tone. Judging from his attire and the series of medals on his chest, he was a high-ranking officer.

Orwell was a commander of the World Tree Military. He was part of the 'Foreign Battle Command Corps'. This was a talent pool formed by the elites of the World Tree. This person was in charge of logistics tasks like exploration, infiltration, and stealing intelligence. Currently, he was in charge of Exploration Team No. 274.

His skin was like a leaf, and his veins could clearly be seen. There was a faint green light flowing through his body, and he looked like a plant spirit. This was one of the Blessed Races of the World Tree, Green Demon.

Not all races annexed by the World Tree had the qualifications to become a Blessed Race. The Blessed Race was an elite race that had obtained the World Tree's endowment. Just like the Beyond Grade A race, they had an extremely high rate of Super Awakening, as well as special talents and a natural connection to the World Tree.

Orwell fiddled with the medals on his chest and slowly gave the order. "All units, pay attention. Follow the planned strategy, split up, and go to the navigation target. Try to avoid any enemy fleets. Our goal is to reach our destination, not to be in a stalemate with the enemy's intercepting troops."

The previous wormhole tunnels had been disrupted by Space Stabilization Anchors and could not transport them over, which led to the 274th exploration group being on standby for a few days. The World Tree naturally guessed the three Universal Civilizations' strategy and knew that this 'Unknown Civilization' wanted to stop them in this area and prevent them from reaching their territory.

Thus, the World Tree decided to have the exploration team take different routes. With hundreds of thousands of exploration ships, every additional route would increase the number of teleportation coordinates of the World Tree. As long as the other side's space stabilization orbit could not block in time, they could slowly explore until they reached the other side's territory.

This method was time-consuming, but the World Tree did not lack patience. The method was simple, rough, and effective. If one path was blocked, they could just take a longer detour next time. Sooner or later, they would be able to penetrate the opponent's interception net. Their advantage was that they did not care about losses, and they had enough capital to make mistakes. They were least afraid of a tug of war.

Under Orwell's command, the hundreds of thousands of battleships scattered and disappeared into space.

The personal troop of Orwell followed the path of the previous exploration team.

"Although the Executive Officers think that this civilization is suspected to be the hometown of the outsider from last time, there's no way to confirm it at the moment. Even if it is not, we don't know if there are individuals with great powers here…"

Orwell narrowed his eyes and casually glanced at a figure resting in the corner of the command room.

The World Tree had specially sent a Holy Tree Emissary to follow the ship. If they encountered the enemy's intercepting troops, they would act according to the situation. The goal was to force out the powerful individuals of this unknown civilization, so it did not matter even if they died.

…

Three days later, a small Arcane Church fleet searched along the path of the exploration team.

The captain was connected to the command channel, listening to the reports from the other troops with a serious expression.

"Currently, we have intercepted a total of 7,200 enemy ships. We have discovered that the enemy is taking detours in different directions. We are not sure of the total size of the enemy…"

"Sir, this is not good for us," the deputy said worriedly.

"It's indeed disadvantageous." The captain nodded solemnly. "But we can only try our best to stop them."

The World Tree had too many troops, and not all the routes would be used as mediums for foreseers. Therefore, even Destiny's Child's channels could not monitor all the routes of these exploration groups. The three Universal Civilizations could only send troops to patrol the area like a sieve, sifting through the various areas to intercept any fish that escaped the net.

This method was akin to finding a needle in a haystack, and it mainly depended on luck. It would also cause the troops to be scattered. However, the defense circle had yet to be built, so they could only use such stupid methods to deal with the attacks of the World Tree. No matter how troublesome it was, they could not let the World Tree Exploration Group penetrate the line of defense.

The extraterritorial defense circle was a huge project. The principle was to treat the Flickering World as the center and build a virtual sphere. It would expand and expand until it covered the current position. Then, the three Universal Civilizations would cut a spherical arc in the direction of the World Tree's advance and expand or shrink according to the situation, forming a three-dimensional boundary to determine the basic range of the defense circle. Then, they would build a large number of wormhole support bases to make up for the problem of the battle line being too long.

Due to the size of the arc, this seemed like an impossible project, but it was actually only limited by manpower and resources. With the efficiency of the three Universal Civilizations, the size of their military power, and their resources, it was enough to take on such a project. Since they did not want to be driven straight in by the World Tree, they could not just build a defense line willy-nilly.

The captain was about to speak when the anti-stealth radar suddenly issued warning signals. It pointed diagonally ahead, showing a group of moving unknown targets.

"We've come across them! Let's go!"

The captain immediately gave the order.

The fleet immediately changed direction and headed toward the target. The target that the radar had locked onto did not turn around, and it headed straight for them.

Not long after, this Arcane Church fleet met with the personal troop of Orwell.

"Fire!"

Without another word, the captain roared with a ferocious expression.

The Arcane Church fleet immediately opened fire, firing a volley of shots. The cannons on the spaceships lit up with a dark red light, and a dazzling beam of light shot out. At the same time, Orwell's subordinates also retaliated.

Two waves of light crossed each other and shot into each other's formation, creating sparks on the shield.

Neither party intended to communicate. The moment they met, it was like a battle of thunder and fire. They exchanged blows in full swing.

While the two sides were fighting intensely, a mental wave suddenly exploded from the main ship of Orwell and swept across the Arcane Church fleet.

The Arcane Church battleships reacted as though they had received a shockwave. They shot out complicated magic circuits formed by energy and blocked the mental waves head-on. The explosions caused sparks to fly, and the magic circuits immediately became much weaker.

"Beyond Grade A Psychic! Requesting support!"

The captain's expression changed, and he immediately requested for help in the command channel.

Because there were too many search teams, the limited number of Beyond Grade As meant they could not allocate one to each team, so they were all on standby in the main base. Only when the search team met a World Tree expert would they be able to request Beyond Grade A reinforcements.

In order to prevent ordinary crew members from having their memories stolen by mind spells and psychic powers, the spaceships had all been specially modified. They had set up a psychic barrier enhancement device and engraved special industrial enchantments to block mental attacks. The number of times it could be used depended on the strength of the other party, so the crew inside the carrier would not be killed instantly upon meeting.

Not long after he said that, a shadow suddenly appeared on the battlefield. It then solidified, and Kasuyi descended through the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device.

"Is this the individual power of the World Tree?"

Kasuyi narrowed his eyes with a flash of interest.

The next moment, boundless psychic energy gushed out like a flood and slammed into Orwell's troops.

The psychic energy released by this Holy Tree Emissary suddenly rolled back and turned into a shield to protect the fleet. However, it only lasted for a few seconds before it was crushed into dust by Kasuyi's endless psychic energy. The exploration fleets were crushed into scrap metal one after another and exploded into fireworks.

Seeing this, the Holy Tree Emissary hurriedly rushed out of the main ship and launched an attack on Kasuyi. The psychic waves turned into a needle beam and shot toward Kasuyi's brain. It immediately made a ding sound and could not penetrate Kasuyi's thick mental barrier.

Kasuyi did not say anything else and released an even more condensed psychic energy, immediately binding this Holy Tree Emissary. The huge difference in energy level made the opponent almost unable to move.

"Let me see your memories…"

Kasuyi's eyes flashed, and his psychic energy entered the Holy Tree Emissary's brain.

This was the first time he had come into contact with a World Tree expert. Before this, he had only heard about it from Han Xiao and had not personally experienced it. At this moment, he could not help but want to pry into the other party's memories.

However, the moment the psychic power entered the mind of this Holy Tree Emissary, a majestic pressure suddenly attacked through the mental link.

Boom!

An indescribable sense of fear crashed into Kasuyi's heart. Kasuyi instantly felt a bone-deep sense of fear, as though he was being looked at by a boundless beast.

An intense sense of warning suddenly rang in his mind. It was as if something extremely terrifying would happen if he did not cut off the mental link.

Because the World Tree's mental network was connected to all individuals, once one tried to use mental means to peer into the memories of an individual, it was equivalent to connecting to the World Tree. Outsiders would immediately feel the immense pressure of the mental network, as well as the strong pressure, and the World Tree would notice it. If one decided to forcefully maintain the mental link, it would instead give the World Tree a chance to devour the soul. At the very least, it would be wiped out and the person would go crazy.

"This is the World Tree?"

Kasuyi hurriedly retracted his psychic energy, his eyes filled with shock.

He finally understood why Han Xiao was so wary when he mentioned the World Tree.

Although it was just a glimpse, he almost felt like he was about to collapse. The pressure of facing a high-level existence was deeply engraved in his heart.

Kasuyi dispelled the thought of spying on the memories and exerted more strength, bombarding the Holy Tree Emissary with his psychic energy. Not long after, the Holy Tree Emissary's consciousness was shattered, and his body exploded into pieces.

In the only remaining exploration ship, Orwell lit a cigarette and took a puff. He looked at the artillery fire outside the window and shook his head helplessly.

"Tsk, tsk… I hope my luck will be better next time."

The next second, cannon fire drowned the spaceship, and a loud explosion occurred. All the crew members, including Orwell, turned into seeds and returned to the arms of the World Tree.

…

At the same time, in the World Tree Civilization…

"What a powerful Psychic. He killed Manny so easily."

Tedrian and the other Executive Officers' faces tightened.

They had been watching the entire process through the mental network.

"Did you see how the Psychic arrived? It's similar to the teleportation method that the outsider used last time," the Heart Tree King calmly said. "There's a seventy-percent chance that this unknown civilization is the hometown of that outsider."

The Subduing Tree King nodded. "This is good news."

They had already felt the pressure from that outsider the last time. If they met another enemy at this time, they would also doubt if they could fight on two fronts and eat two prey at the same time.

However, now that they had almost confirmed that the two of them were the same enemy, it was a relief. If that was the case, the exploration team had discovered the enemy's nest when they had no clue about it. It was simply a blessing!

"The standard of this Psychic should not be as high as that outsider, but it's still powerful enough. Ordinary Holy Tree Emissaries are far from being his match. This is indeed a civilization with extremely developed individual strength," Tedrian muttered.

The Heart Tree King nodded and slowly said, "The other party's strategy is very clear. They plan to build an interception circle here. It's obvious that it hasn't been built yet, so we can destroy it… Next time, we'll choose to teleport to the coordinates at the back and have the troops build a temporary base there as a guide point. When the time comes, we'll gather a large force and launch an all-out attack."

"We don't have to do what we did in the past. Should we first find out more information before launching an all-out attack?" The Subduing Tree King glanced at him.

"Of course, we have to collect intelligence, but if we only focus on this, it will be too conservative and inflexible. It's best to adjust the plan according to the situation. Probing information is one thing, but it's also important to take the opportunity to disrupt the enemy's deployment. There's no conflict between the two. If we let the enemy build an intercepting circle comfortably, we will have to spend more than ten times the cost to break through. We might as well take action now and destroy the enemy's plan."

The Heart Tree King narrowed his eyes. The World Tree Civilization was pragmatic, and he did not have a habit of waiting for others to finish preparing before attacking.

Chapter 1333: Assemble

In the command room of the main base of the intercepting zone, reports of successful interceptions were being sent back one after another. Simon and the others were surrounding the real-time star map to control the entire situation, while the Beyond Grade As were on standby. The ten Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Devices outside the window were still in a state of preheating, ready to move at any time.

At this time, a light flashed in the corner of the room. Kasuyi, who had changed into a King suit, returned to the room with Han Xiao's Mechanical Force wrapped around his body, immediately attracting the attention of others.

"You're back? How do you feel?"

Han Xiao raised his brows and took back the King from Kasuyi.

Because the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device was only responsible for one-way teleportation, the intercepting troops would naturally not take another set of teleportation devices. Thus, Han Xiao lent the King mechanical suit and had the other Beyond Grade As take one when they went out. He would then use Mechanical Force to pull it back after they were done, increasing the efficiency.

"The Beyond Grade As of the World Tree are quite powerful." Kasuyi nodded solemnly.

"However, I was trampled to death by you… I feel like you're indirectly praising yourself." Sun Hunter was suspicious.

"Ahem, I'm evaluating him as an ordinary Beyond Grade A, so don't include peak Beyond Grade As," Kasuyi muttered. "The other party's psychic energy is stronger, and that light green energy seems to have greatly increased his mental strength. His strength should be able to match 1.6 times Psyker's."

"That's quite good. The dynasty has Kohler, and you guys have Psyker. This kind of bottom… basic combatant is more convenient for us to compare our strength," Lotus Swordsman said.

Luckily, the two of them were not there, so no one jumped out to refute. Everyone nodded.

"You're talking about the increase in combat strength brought about by the World Tree Union. Basically, all the Beyond Grade As of the World Tree Civilization enjoy this amplification. It's equivalent to having a Space Wonder-level Universal Treasure," Han Xiao explained.

"So, the average combat capability of the enemy Beyond Grade As is higher than ours?" Manison's Lord's Avatar asked.

"You can say that." Han Xiao spread out his hands. "However, the high-end combat power should be about the same. The Five Tree Kings and their Ten Leaf Executive Officers are all extremely strong. The Thirteen Ancestral Spirits and the high-level Holy Tree Emissaries are extraordinary. There are also the high-level military commanders who are in charge of fighting outside all year round. We can still fight them."

"That doesn't sound good." Secret Master shook his head.

Kasuyi frowned and said, "Speaking of which, I tried to pry into the other party's memories just now, but I felt a high-level pressure. If I did not retract my psychic energy in time, I might have been heavily injured… Is that the power of the World Tree?"

"That's right; that's the World Tree. Don't use your mental power to detect the memories of any member of the World Tree. They are all connected together and are protected by the World Tree. Their thoughts are also monitored. If there are any deviations, they will be corrected to prevent spying or possession," Han Xiao explained.

"They're like slaves, never able to betray their master…" Kasuyi sighed before asking curiously, "Then, how did you get the information from them? "

"Is there even a need to ask? I'm stronger than you guys," Han Xiao said honestly.

Everyone was speechless.

Although it is the truth, why do we want to hit you so much?

The others ignored Han Xiao and asked Kasuyi all sorts of questions. Although everyone present had read the information about the one hundred World Tree experts that Han Xiao had collected last time, they were still very curious about Kasuyi's combat experience.

Han Xiao did not mind. He shook his head and walked over to Simon and the others. As he listened to the orders from the upper echelons and staff officers, he looked at the changes in the real-time star map.

The star map was densely distributed with light dots, each representing an intercepting team. Their movements changed and were drawing forks in some places, which meant that they had successfully intercepted the enemy. There was a circle of light around the forks, as well as lines that extended out, representing the possible routes of the other World Tree exploration forces.

"The interception situation is not bad, thanks to your intelligence," Simon said when he saw Han Xiao walking over.

"We're just helping each other." Han Xiao did not mind.

Simon nodded, then sighed. "However, the intercepting circle is still too passive. We can only try our best to prevent the World Tree exploration team from entering our territory, but we will lose if we keep defending. As long as the enemy takes a wide enough detour, there will be some that slip through the net sooner or later. We can only think of ways to delay this moment."

"That can't be helped. After all, the opponent is the World Tree." Han Xiao shrugged.

"…That's right. This civilization is practically born for war. If it were any other opponent, we wouldn't have to be passive like we are now. What a troublesome enemy."

Simon was helpless.

The three Universal Civilizations were also tyrannical civilizations. If the enemy was not a war machine like the World Tree, with their current intelligence advantage, they might have already thought of a way to take the initiative to attack… However, there was no strategy that could be used in all situations. Taking the initiative to attack also depended on who the opponent was. If they ignored the actual situation of the opponent and used the example in the tactics manual, they would most likely suffer heavy losses. After all, they were not like the World Tree Civilization, which could fight without any heartache. With the example of the Kama Republic, the World Tree was not most powerful in their aggressive attacks but their encroachment.

Furthermore, Han Xiao's intelligence had already shown that the main body was the foundation of the World Tree. If this was a real-time strategy game, the World Tree Territory would at most be a sub-base. The main base would still be in the fog of war, and the three Universal Civilizations would expose the location of their main base and be under attack. It would not be worth it to exchange their main base with a sub-base, not to mention that the enemy troops were even faster.

After sorting out his emotions, Simon took out his pocket watch and said, "The intercepting circle is still in the construction phase, and we're short on manpower. How long will it take for the fleets of your Beyond Grade A Association to arrive?"

"Soon. They're gathering toward the teleportation point," Han Xiao replied.

Currently, the Flickering World was rapidly turning into a war zone, and the unrelated parties were leaving at high speed. The Federation of Light took out a large pile of Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Devices and set up a gathering point in the Dawn Star Cluster to send the rest of the troops over. The fleets of the Beyond Grade A organizations such as the Black Star Army were rushing there.

Simon nodded. "It should be as fast as possible. The more manpower we have, the sooner the interception circle will be completed. The longer we can keep the World Tree outside of our territory, the better."

…

The interstellar era emphasized efficiency. Advanced space travel capabilities reduced the time needed to travel, and many things could happen every day. However, at a higher level, many things required a long period of evolution.

Over the next few days, the three Universal Civilizations' intercepting troops played hide-and-seek with the World Tree's Exploration Group No. 274. The exploration teams were wiped out one after another, but because of the detours, the battle line was getting longer and longer.

At the same time, the reinforcements of the Beyond Grade A organizations arrived at the intercepting area and quickly entered the construction of the interception circle. The wormholes were quickly built and connected together like a huge net, forming layers of barriers. The area expanded rapidly every day and spread further.

The intercepting zone was already the frontline, and more Beyond Grade As arrived one after another after settling their matters. The number quickly approached a hundred.

At the observation tower of the main base, Han Xiao stood in front of the huge floor-to-ceiling window and looked at the bright galaxy. He seemed to be thinking about life, but he was actually browsing the forums to see the reactions of the players who had arrived at the frontline.

Just as he was focused on reading the post, he suddenly heard footsteps approaching from afar. Han Xiao closed the interface and looked back. It was Hila and Aurora.

"You guys are here too?" Han Xiao glanced at them.

"Just arrived." Hila's expression was calm.

"I knew that with your personality, you definitely wouldn't miss such a battle."

Han Xiao shook his head.

He did not force the two sisters to participate, nor did he force them to stay behind. After all, the two of them were Beyond Grade As, and they had to respect each other's wishes. If they came willingly, he would not stop them. Furthermore, the two sisters were indeed exceptional combatants.

"Since we have to fight the enemy together, we naturally can't stay out of it. With our current strength, I don't feel comfortable receiving protection," Hila said slowly.

Han Xiao looked at Aurora. "What about you?"

"Ah? Since my sister is here, I will definitely follow. What if she gets beaten to death? Also, my ability should be very useful." Aurora smiled.

"She might be safer here than me." Hila snorted. This was one of the reasons she did not stop Aurora from following her.

"With you around, the safety of the other Beyond Grade As will be guaranteed." Han Xiao nodded at Aurora.

"Don't misunderstand, we have other plans. This is a good place to strengthen the Underworld."

Hila waved her hands.

"This is indeed a good opportunity." Han Xiao nodded in agreement.

With the Underworld, even if the warriors below Beyond Grade A died, they would have a chance to be reborn. The meat grinder of war had always been a treasure ground for collecting souls. As long as the Underworld could store them, it would not be a problem.

However, the World Tree warriors were bound together, and they would not lose their souls even if they died. They would probably not be able to capture them, and the Underworld would most likely only be able to retrieve the dead warriors from the three Universal Civilizations. Furthermore, Han Xiao did not dare let the two sisters take the risk to capture the members of the World Tree. If the World Tree connection was not broken because of this, the coordinates of the Underworld would probably be exposed. It would not be good if the World Tree followed the clues and attacked the Underworld.

However, this did not affect the strategic importance of the Underworld. In Han Xiao's eyes, the Underworld had the ability to change the entire situation, and its effect was not inferior to the Sanctum Revival. In some ways, it even exceeded it. It was a pity that Aurora's powers were not strong enough. If she was allowed to grow for a few decades or even a century, the power of the Underworld would be even higher.

Han Xiao turned back to look out of the window and said in a deep voice, "I have a feeling that the World Tree will not sit back and watch us deploy our defenses. They will probably organize a large-scale attack very soon, and it will be the first time the three Universal Civilizations and the World Tree are fighting a large-scale battle."

"Is this your intuition?" Hila raised her brows.

"No, it's just a prediction based on the style of the World Tree." Han Xiao stroked his chin and sighed. "No matter what, you have to protect yourselves. I might not be able to take care of you in this universe-level war."

"I will take care of myself," Hila replied calmly.

…

In the territory of the World Tree Civilization, endless fleets were laid out in the universe, and streams of light were still coming from afar, turning into new troops that integrated into the group, expanding the scale of the army.

The executive officers nodded inwardly.

Once the Heart Tree King decided to launch an attack, they immediately gathered all the armies and waited for orders.

Due to the superior nature of the mental network and the fast movement in the territory, the efficiency of the World Tree Civilization in gathering troops was extremely astonishing. Very soon, they formed a large expedition army with a fleet of eight billion battleships, ready to attack at any time.

An executive officer turned to look at the two tree kings. "Your Excellency Tree King, when will the assault begin?"

The Subduing Tree King did not speak but turned to look at the Heart Tree King.

"The scale is still not enough. Gather more people," the Heart Tree King said slowly.

"The required scale is…" Tedrian asked tentatively.

"This is the first time we're fighting, so let's take this as a greeting. The size of our fleet should be at least fifty billion, or else it will be hardly presentable. If they can't even withstand such a small attack, then we can adopt more daring tactics in the future."

Heart Tree King's tone was so calm that it was as if he was only throwing out a small chip on the gambling table.

However, he paused and said, "Right, we have to consider the possibility of that outsider joining the battle. That person is not easy to deal with…"

Chapter 1334: Intelligence Advantage

The intercepting operation was still ongoing. As the enemy had only brought one Holy Tree Emissary, with the rest of their troops lacking individual strength, Kasuyi was the only one who took action. The other Beyond Grade As did not have the chance to take action and merely continued to wait.

In the compartment of the command room, almost a hundred Beyond Grade As were gathered there, doing their own things. Some were supervising the situation, some were resting with their eyes closed, some were dealing with matters, some were chatting casually, and there were even some who were playing cards in such a serious setting.

"Speaking of which, it has been some time since the two of us sat down to chat."

Kant looked at the direct descendants of the three Universal Civilizations and sighed.

When the three Universal Civilizations were targeting the association, Han Xiao did not allow the direct Beyond Grade As to participate in the meeting. After the lockdown was lifted, due to various things being delayed, the three Universal Civilizations had yet to regain the normal treatment that the direct Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations received in the association. Therefore, the time they spent on standby in the main base was when the members of the association and the direct Beyond Grade As finally got to sit together and chat.

"Now that we have a common enemy, let's not talk about the past for the time being. We're just doing our own thing." Oulou sighed and looked at Han Xiao with a complicated expression.

"Heh, don't confuse us with you guys. You guys have masters, but we don't. It's all for ourselves." Sun Hunter curled his lips.

Oulou was silent for a few seconds before changing the topic. "I saw that the members of your association are not here yet. Why aren't the others here?"

"They're still considering it." Kasuyi shook his head.

"You guys are participating in the battle, and they're watching from behind and taking advantage of us? You guys can accept this?" Oulou raised his brows.

"So, you should kneel down and be grateful to us… Damn it, just thinking about it makes me feel so noble," Sun Hunter cursed.

Kasuyi helplessly explained, "Someone has to set an example. If not for Black Star, we might not have come."

This time, Clotti, who was resting with his eyes closed, opened his eyes and slowly said, "Then, do you have the resolve to die in battle?"

Hearing this, everyone paused and looked over.

Clotti was expressionless as he calmly continued. "We, the direct descendants, are all participating in the battle with the determination to sacrifice our lives. Aren't you self-serving people afraid of losing your lives? Even if there's the Sanctum Revival, I'm sure none of you are willing to spend your chance to revive and give the initiative of your life and death to others."

"…You're right. Of course, no one is willing to sacrifice themselves if they can survive. However, they have to personally experience the strength of the enemy before they know what they're doing," Secret Master replied calmly. "Therefore, don't expect us to fight to the death for you. We're just fulfilling our end of the bargain. We've already done our part by coming to help."

This time, Oulou looked at Han Xiao, who did not participate in the conversation, and asked, "Black Star, if we die, you will help us revive, right?"

Hearing this, Han Xiao turned around and gave a brief reply.

He was not familiar with Oulou in the past, but after interacting with him for the past few days, this person was indeed not difficult to deal with.

"Yes."

"Ha, then I'm relieved. If I can leave my body behind when I die in battle, please use the Spacetime Amber and preserve me as a specimen to let me take it away when I revive. I don't want others to covet my handsomeness and steal my body for their collection."

Oulou made a joke, but no one laughed.

Sun Hunter rolled his eyes. "Do you think you're funny?"

Han Xiao could not be bothered with the people who were chatting. He looked away and continued to browse the forums.

At the moment, more than ninety percent of the players in the universe had arrived at the frontline. Most of them were rubbing their hands in anticipation of the war.

This kind of large-scale war operation had always been a good opportunity for the players to accumulate experience. Most of the army players participated in the operation, which would allow Han Xiao to gain experience more efficiently.

However, the players had yet to reach the level limit of the version. The first choice for EXP was to level up on their own. After reaching the level limit, they would then have a lot of extra EXP to do other things.

This meant that when most of the players reached the maximum level, his efficiency in harvesting EXP would increase by a lot. This was not his fastest harvesting speed.

It's a pity that the usage of the players in this scenario is not as good as it was in my previous life…

Han Xiao felt helpless.

The World Tree War was supposed to be a later version, but due to the butterfly effect, it had been brought forward to Version 5.0. In his previous life, this would only be considered a middle version. The players were lacking a few extra versions to accumulate, and the upper limit of their levels would be a few dozen levels lower. Thus, they would not be as useful in the main battlefield as in his previous life.

In his previous life, the players had very high strategic value. The Immortals who were formed by high-level Supers had contributed a lot to many battlefields. Now that this force was gone, it would definitely affect all aspects of battle.

Fortunately, the fate of Hila and Aurora had been rewritten by him, and the Underworld should be able to fill this gap.

Beep beep beep…

While he was pondering, his communicator suddenly rang. It was a message from Oathkeeper.

Han Xiao took it out to take a look, and his expression changed.

"The World Tree is recruiting an army, estimated to be in the tens of billions, ready to launch an attack!"

Hearing this, the chatter in the room disappeared. Everyone stopped what they were doing and turned to look at him. There were all kinds of expressions such as seriousness, surprise, and fear.

Han Xiao immediately walked out of the cubicle to share information with Simon and the others. The other Beyond Grade As also stood up and followed behind Han Xiao.

Simon and the other commanders had been monitoring the situation outside the cubicle the entire time. Upon hearing the intelligence that Han Xiao had shared, their expressions changed, and they hurriedly opened their long-distance communication to report the situation to the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations.

The figures of the three Universal Civilizations' leaders appeared on the remote communication screen. The three of them listened to the report with solemn expressions and nodded.

"Is the World Tree Civilization preparing to launch an attack? Got it. We will send the order to gather the various armies to the frontline and prepare for a tough battle."

As he spoke, Marbruce heaved a sigh of relief.

"Black Star, your intel this time is still very timely and bought us quite some time."

The World Tree Civilization was still in the recruitment phase, and the fleet had yet to be gathered, but Destiny's Child had already detected it and sent it to Han Xiao. This was a huge advantage, and the other party would not arrive so quickly, so they had plenty of time to prepare.

Knowing the other party's next move ahead of time, the three Universal Civilizations would be able to deal with it ahead of time. Black Star's intelligence network had already made contributions more than once, and every time, the three Universal Civilizations felt like they had been given coal during a harsh winter.

Han Xiao nodded. "A fleet of tens of billions is not easy to deal with. Although I have provided intelligence, you are the main force."

The World Tree Civilization had sent out tens of billions of battleships, which was indeed quite a large force. However, in terms of a Universal War, this was not an all-out attack. The scale of tens of billions was not at the level where they were invincible.

The mobilization capacity of the two civilizations could not be compared in the same breath for internal and external battles. When there were no external enemies, the three Universal Civilizations would control their military strength to an appropriate standard. They would not expand their army on a large scale to avoid excessive military expenditures, instead mainly focusing on accumulating strategic resources. However, once they fully entered the state of war, they would quickly turn into a militaristic mode. All the military factories under their flag would explode with soldiers day and night, and their military strength would increase every day.

The scale of the World Tree's assault was not enough to make the three Universal Civilizations give up on intercepting them. Unless they could not stop them completely, it would not be the time to use their rear strategic strength to exchange for more time.

At this moment, a staff officer touched his chin and said, "Since the other party is still recruiting troops, should we take the initiative to harass them?"

Hearing this, everyone turned to look at him before looking away.

Simon glanced at him, shook his head, and said, "The World Tree's information state warning network is spread all over the territory. If we encounter it, we'll be exposed. What can we do to disrupt it? Furthermore, any army can move quickly in the territory, almost instantaneously. Their mobility is far beyond ours. It's a natural ambush circle. Once exposed, we'll be surrounded by countless fleets. We'll be devoured no matter how many we send."

Another commander on the side brought the topic back on track and said with a deep voice, "The wormhole reinforcement base already covers the current intercepting area. No matter which blockade area the World Tree hits, we will be able to start the battle and stop the other party."

The intercepting circle was divided into many levels, and there were strategic zones of different depth between the different levels. The reinforcement base station was the connecting channel, which ensured that the various regional troops in the horizontal longitudinal area would look out for each other. Regardless of whether it was the observation level or the garrison level, they had completed the allocation. No matter where they met a strong enemy, they would be able to quickly send their main force.

As for whether the World Tree's assault team would hit the intercepting circle, it was not a big problem. Although the intercepting circle was still under construction, it would still be effective even if it was not fully formed. It was similar to running a race; as long as their expansion speed was slighter faster than the enemy, it would remain effective. At the same time, the intercepting team was also constantly setting up spatial anchoring orbits to eliminate the coordinates of the exploration teams' routes, constantly moving the enemy's starting point backward as much as possible to return to its original position, causing them to only be able to resume their usual voyage and remain in the intercepting circle.

"It seems like the World Tree doesn't plan to only give us appetizers. It's preparing to give us a proper meal… This is the first time I've experienced a Universal War of this scale." Oulou's eyes flickered.

At this time, Secret Master pinched his fingers and calculated in his mind before saying with an expressionless face, "My death omen is flashing."

With that said, he changed his hand gesture, and magical waves spread out.

Everyone sensed something and looked over curiously.

"What did you just do?"

"I shifted my bad luck," Secret Master said calmly.

"Who did you transfer it to?"

"Him."

Secret Master pointed at Han Xiao.

Han Xiao looked at the Luck Reduction status on the interface with a face full of question marks.

"Do we have a grudge?"

"No."

"Then why did you push your bad luck on me?"

"Anyway, you're not afraid. There's no room for your luck to decline."

"…"

Han Xiao's mouth twitched.

Are you treating me like a trash can? If not for the fact that I have enemies now, I would let you know why one's anus is called a chrysanthemum!

Chapter 1335: The World Tree's Strongest

In the territory of the World Tree Civilization, a multitude of wormholes were maintained in the starry sky, and the roots of the World Tree extended out from them. Fleet after fleet shuttled back and forth, continuously adding to the size of the expedition army. There were all kinds of battleships.

There was a floating lookout tower made of pale green roots nearby. The Subduing Tree King and the Heart Tree King stood there, scanning the expeditionary army's lineup.

The Heart Tree King calmly said, "The high-level combatants this time include Executive Officers Three Leaves to Nine Leaves, seven high-level Holy Tree Envoys, the Thirteen Ancestral Spirits who are ranked from second to sixth, four army leaders, and other experts. There are 107 of them. This size is enough to test the strength of the opponents and see how well developed they are."

"Pretty good." The Subduing Tree King nodded.

There were more than a hundred World Tree experts participating in the expedition. Normally, such an expeditionary force would have a rather low survival rate. However, when the Heart Tree King sent out these members, he was already prepared to sacrifice all of them.

Sacrifices did not mean that they would be given for nothing. Using high-level combatants to kill each other was their usual method of fighting against strong enemies. If the enemy's high-level combatants died, they would be gone, but their high-level combatants would only return to their seed form after dying. They would be able to reawaken after waiting for a certain amount of time in their bodies, which was undoubtedly beneficial to the World Tree. They opted for a war of attrition to disintegrate the enemy's strength step by step, reducing the strength of both sides.

The World Tree had used this method to defeat one enemy after another. Up till now, it had never been defeated by anyone, so there was no reason not to use it.

The Heart Tree King turned around to look at the Subduing Tree King and said, "They lack a leader. You will go with them this time."

"I want to go too? Three Leaf Forest, Four Leaf Amrein, and a few commanders are enough to lead the troops. There's no need for me to take the risk."

The Subduing Tree King frowned. He was not too willing to participate in this expedition. The experience of returning to the seed form was not comfortable, and the recovery time of a Tree King was longer than others.

The Heart Tree King shook his head. "The other party's information gathering has not been interfered with by our side. The Mother Tree's authority will not be able to penetrate the area covered by their information gathering. It will require the level of a Tree King to allow the Mother Tree's projection to descend, so you have to go."

"…Okay."

The Subduing Tree King nodded and did not ask why it was not left to the other Tree Kings.

Among the five Great Tree Kings, he was the only one who had no other abilities other than fighting. From a pragmatic point of view, sacrificing him was the most cost-effective. He was already used to being the vanguard.

"We might meet that outsider on this trip. You'd better accept a baptism before setting off, or you might not be his match," the Heart Tree King instructed.

"I'll go and prepare."

As soon as he finished his sentence, the Subduing Tree King turned to leave.

…

After receiving the intelligence that the World Tree was preparing to launch an attack, the three Universal Civilizations quickly reacted. The highest-level military order was passed down like an electrical signal through a neural network, controlling the limbs of the 'giant' Universal Civilization. All the armies rushed to the front line like they were gathering strength with clenched fists.

Every few minutes to a few hours, a fleet would arrive at the intercepting zone. Other than transferring the main army, the three Universal Civilizations also recruited the troops of the other advanced civilizations, mobilizing the entire explored universe. As a result, the strength of the intercepting zone increased rapidly, increasing by one billion per day.

While staying near the teleportation point, Han Xiao had seen almost all the main battleships of the various civilizations in the past few days. The three Universal Civilizations had all kinds of battleships, and the top-class battleships that represented the strongest units stood out like cranes among chickens.

At the same time, the transportation troops of the three Universal Civilizations continuously sent over all kinds of Universal Treasures. All the equipment used for individual strength was temporarily lent to the Beyond Grade As, and even the members of the association could distribute them according to their needs. The other strategic Universal Treasures were given to different fleets.

Atop the temporary base's lookout tower, many Beyond Grade As stood in front of the window and looked out.

The surroundings had already become a sea of battleships, almost blocking out the starry sky. It was as if there were only countless battleships glowing with a metallic luster. If one looked far away, this scene was like the scales of a gigantic beast.

"What a huge army. This is the first time I've seen something like this."

Many people gasped.

It was rare to see the three Universal Civilizations mobilize so many troops. Internal conflicts did not have such intensity, and only the exploration era war could be compared to the current one.

This was the first time that many of them had experienced a Universal War. Seeing this, they had a new understanding of the mobilization of the three Universal Civilizations.

Although they did not know what the World Tree Army was like, just the sight of the three Universal Civilizations' army was enough to raise their morale.

"There's not much we can do in such a fierce war. Strangling the high-level combatants on the other side is our mission," Kasuyi said with a deep voice.

"The enemy has many high-level combatants, so it won't be easy for us. With their style, they will surely think of a way to deal with us," a Beyond Grade A beside him said with concern.

Hearing this, Aurora interrupted with a gentle tone. "As long as you don't leave my healing range, I should be able to ensure your safety."

Many people immediately replied politely.

"I'm counting on you this time."

"Luckily, you're here."

"Sorry to trouble you."

Through the mechanisms of the World Tree, it was not difficult to guess that the other party was good at fighting. Everyone present knew very well that in such a fierce battle, the healer was the one who could increase their chances of survival. Many people gathered around Aurora as though they were her bodyguards.

Hila, on the other hand, was watching coldly from the side.

Manison ignored the noisy crowd and walked to Han Xiao's side. "Black Star, you seem a little nervous. Are you worried that your Indestructible Body won't be able to withstand such a fierce battle?"

Han Xiao turned around and sized him up. He then poked Manison Lord's Avatar's chest and said, "Come over with your true body if you dare. Let me see if you'll be nervous too."

"Heh, what a joke. I'm not an anomaly among Mechanics like you. I never do anything that puts myself in danger." Manison snorted.

"Come on, just say it. With just your small physique, you still dare to sashay in front of me?"

Han Xiao expressed his strong disdain.

Manison also laughed before continuing in a low voice after a brief pause. "You should know who the strongest person on the World Tree side is, right?"

"Hmm, the strongest should be the Ancestral Tree King, the leader of the five Great Tree Kings."

"Can you deal with him?" Manison was curious.

"This person is unfathomable. I can't say with any confidence."

Han Xiao shook his head.

Among the five Great Tree Kings, the Subduing Tree King as a Pugilist was the weakest, and the Ancestral Tree King was the strongest. Even in the heated battles of his previous life, the Ancestral Tree King was an elusive existence, and the number of times he had fought could be counted on one hand. However, the battle record of the Ancestral Tree King was extremely impressive, and those who died in his hands were all peak Beyond Grade As. None of them were weak, as if ordinary opponents were not worth his time.

At the same time, the Ancestral Tree King was the person who had the most connections with the World Tree. In a sense, he was the only 'master' of the World Tree, and Han Xiao was not sure if he could defeat him.

"Even you don't have confidence…" Manison was deep in thought.

Just as Han Xiao was about to say something, his communicator suddenly vibrated.

The room immediately fell silent, and everyone's eyes focused on Han Xiao. They all realized something, and their expressions turned solemn.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and took out his communicator. He paused and took a deep breath.

"They're here."

Chapter 1336: Battle

Ten minutes later, in the command room, the highest commanders like Simon and the commanding officers of the various armies gathered together to analyze the enemy. Many Beyond Grade As listened from the side, and only Han Xiao, the consultant, participated in the discussion.

"The enemy's location has been exposed. They have set up a temporary base in this distant area and have sent out many scouts. They have increased the teleportation coordinates and shortened the distance of the march. We estimate that when they encounter the intercepting troops, the main force will jump over…"

The tactical star map was displayed on the virtual screen, and there were many coordinates marked on it. Simon would enlarge or shrink areas of the map to match his explanation, and everyone listened attentively.

The main force of the World Tree Civilization had already gathered in their territory, but they did not set off immediately. Instead, they sent out scouts to build temporary strongholds and get closer to the interception circle, obtaining closer coordinates as jump points to shorten the distance.

This was because once the main force arrived at the war zone, they would not be able to hide and could only travel normally. There was a high chance that they would be attacked by the super-long-range attacks of the three Universal Civilizations. If the teleportation point was too far away from the intercepting circle, the damage would increase, so they had to reduce the distance as much as possible. Although the World Tree Civilization was not afraid of war damage, they did not want to bathe in cannon fire.

This was the intelligence that Han Xiao had obtained from Destiny's Child, and he had shared it with the three Universal Civilizations. Thus, this council of war was held.

"The enemy's troops mobilization ability is astonishing. They came very quickly and did not give us much time to gather. Although we have more troops, we do not have much of an advantage. This battle won't be easy," another commander said.

"Currently, our biggest advantage lies in our home-field advantage and depth of preparation. We have already set up many traps, ambush areas, and attack zones that exceed our visual range. If the enemy's main fleet is delayed for more than seven days from the jump point to the interception circle, we estimate that we can reduce the enemy's fleet by two billion to seven billion… However, the premise is that the information stolen is accurate enough. The enemy's battleship technology is not inferior to ours, so they won't bring out any more advanced technology," the senior officer in charge of managing the defense line construction muttered.

As they spoke, they all turned to look at Han Xiao. Most of the information about the World Tree was provided by Han Xiao, and they could only rely on Han Xiao for intelligence. A single person's contribution was countless times greater than all of them.

"There is no issue with the intelligence." Han Xiao nodded.

Although the World Tree Civilization was strong and had a lot of black technology, their battleship technology did not have much of an advantage. The technology of the main battleships was similar to that of the three Universal Civilizations', and there was no difference in their performance. It was shown during the battle in his previous life, so the three Universal Civilizations did not collapse even after being attacked suddenly.

Simon clapped his hands and said, "The situation is clear now. Now, the task for you…"

He quickly assigned the missions according to the plan, and it was soon the turn of the Beyond Grade As.

Simon looked at everyone and said in a deep voice, "You guys don't need to participate in the fire support and harassment battle in the early stages. Remain on standby at the base and wait for the battle to begin. Also, Mechanics, don't be idle. Provide technical support in the Virtual Networks."

"Okay."

Everyone nodded without any objections.

In a universe-level battle with billions of battleships, the amount of manpower they had was like a drop in the ocean for the enemy. The risk of fighting a fleet alone was far higher than the benefits. Such a mission did not require the participation of high-level combatants.

The battle conference was brief and concise, and the results were soon out. Not long after, the official announcement was sent, and the war machines were activated.

The commanders took action, and fleet after fleet left the dock, turning into streams of light and disappearing into the universe.

The players who were on standby in the various fleets received a few Main Storyline War Missions that they were waiting for, and the forums were once again filled with discussion.

Han Xiao had also triggered these missions, and after browsing through them carefully, he realized that the situation was similar to the main storyline missions of the World Tree War in his previous life. They were all about killing enemies for merit points, but there were slight differences in the description of the missions.

In his previous life, most of the terms used were 'resistance' and 'blocking'. Now, the mission description was more proactive, and the corresponding missions were adjusted according to the butterfly effect.

For example, this intercepting battle that did not exist in his previous life had formed a branch mission. If he could complete the strategic goal of blocking the enemy, not only would he receive a high reward, there was also a specific remark that it would have a positive impact on the overall battle. This was also the characteristic of the World Tree main storyline. Every part of the battle would form a branch mission, and the results would affect the overall strategy.

In his previous life, the players had quite a lot of combat power in the later versions. Sometimes, they would be able to command some of the battles. However, in a war of this scale, victory or defeat was not decided by them. They could only try their best to break through and create opportunities for the majority of the troops. This was also the role that the players often played in the battles in his previous life.

The reward for such main storyline missions was mainly experience. It was a drop in the ocean for Han Xiao, but it was extremely enticing for the players. If they could obtain the victory reward of the interception mission, their experience would increase by a large amount.

As a terminal of harvesting experience, the players were like a reservoir for Han Xiao. The players would do missions, work to create wealth, and then a portion of the wealth would flow into his hands through consumption and other methods to help him develop. If the leeks did not have a chance to shine, how could he maintain the rapid growth of his combat power over the years?

Therefore, Han Xiao had always loved such large-scale missions. Whether it was out of strategic consideration or for the goal of harvesting experience, he wanted to try his best to obtain victory in this battle and increase the accumulation of experience.

As Han Xiao and the other Beyond Grade As did not participate in the frontline harassment battle, they only watched the frontline battle report in the base every day and monitored the entire situation.

The three Universal Civilizations first intercepted and eliminated the scouts. Not long after, the World Tree finally chose the nearest jump point, and the expeditionary army officially arrived, heading toward the intercepting circle. The large fleet suffered from the attacks of the long-range firepower during the voyage, and they also suffered a certain amount of damage while passing through the areas with traps. However, even though they were frequently harassed by the three Universal Civilizations, the distance between the large fleet and the intercepting circle was still shrinking every day, getting closer and closer.

The situation developed step by step, and the World Tree expeditionary army finally came into contact with the interception circle. The armies of the three Universal Civilizations were on high alert, and the main forces of both sides finally started a direct battle. Many Beyond Grade As were summoned.

…

The light from the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device occupied his vision, and the next moment, Han Xiao and the Beyond Grade As were teleported to the main command ship at the rear of the battlefield.

"You're finally here."

Simon nodded as a greeting.

"How's the situation now?" Han Xiao asked while looking outside the window.

What appeared before his eyes was a magnificent battlefield that stretched as far as the eye could see. There were hundreds of billions of battleships on the battlefield, and they were all locked in battle. It was as if there was an endless net of light created by the cannons of the battleships. In such a large-scale battle, it was extremely difficult to coordinate all the battles together. The base commanders were divided into different battle zones, and the special technology and Universal Treasures of both sides were brought in the battle one after the other. All kinds of strange phenomena occurred in different areas, and more than a hundred thousand battleships exploded into fireworks every second.

The two sides naturally would not set battle arrays again. The war had begun the moment the harassment troops fired their first shot. The World Tree expeditionary army had been fighting the three Universal Civilizations all the way from the jump point to the intercepting circle, and they had not stopped fighting for a moment. Now, they were only going from harassment to a head-on battle, so there was no chance for them to temporarily stop to adjust.

Seeing this sight of the universe-level battle, many Beyond Grade As gasped in shock. The temperature in the room dropped a few degrees.

Looking at such an intense battle, the Beyond Grade As felt a headache coming on.

In this kind of intense battle, a Beyond Grade A individual would be negligible, and his life would be in danger at any time.

Only on a battlefield where two universe overlords clashed would one be able to understand that the internal conflicts of the past were mostly small skirmishes. This was the highest level of war.

Without caring about their thoughts, Simon replied with a deep voice, "Currently, we're still evenly matched. The direction of the situation is still unclear. The opponent's high-level combatants have yet to take action."

Han Xiao retracted his gaze and said, "Are the World Tree's experts still watching? We don't have to participate in the main battlefield, right?"

Simon shook his head. "No need. Other than the Mechanics providing Virtual Technology support, the mission for the rest of you is to deal with the high-level combatants of the World Tree. Don't worry about anything else for now."

Individual strengths were rarely responsible for direct combat in large-scale battles. Most of them used a series of tactics such as a sudden attack, assassinations, storm strongholds, and guarding the main ship. The commander would not allow the high-level combatants to waste their energy on the main battlefield. After all, a normal Beyond Grade A's strength and stamina were limited.

Only Mechanics with Virtual Technology would be able to play a huge role in the large galactic battlefield, constantly hacking into the enemy's network to seize control of the battleships. Their role was much more useful than other four Super classes.

"Sure." Han Xiao had no objections.

In a battlefield like this, they only had to take care of their own responsibilities. Controlling the entire situation was the responsibility of the commander, not the work of Beyond Grade As like them.

At this time, the real-time battlefield star map changed, and more than a hundred high-energy sources appeared in one of the war zones. The three Universal Civilizations' fleets in this area instantly suffered a large number of casualties, and many war flagships exploded. The situation quickly became one-sided.

"The World Tree has sent out high-level combatants?" Simon's eyes narrowed, and he turned around to look at the surveillance screen. He saw World Tree experts of all shapes and sizes charging forward, destroying the fleets of the three Universal Civilizations one after another with all kinds of abilities, opening up the situation for this war zone.

Han Xiao identified the enemies and locked his gaze on the Subduing Tree King.

He had thought that the Subduing Tree King would not participate in such a battle.

However, considering that the other party was a Pugilist who specialized in charging forward, it was reasonable for him to be in the suicide squad. After all, this was the only specialty a Pugilist had.

This time, Simon retracted his gaze, looked at everyone, and nodded.

"Everyone, I'll leave it to you."

The moment he said that, the direct Beyond Grade As of the three Universal Civilizations did not hesitate and headed toward the hatch. The expressions of the other Beyond Grade As turned serious, but they did not say anything. They shook their heads and followed.

Since they had chosen to come here, even if the battlefield was dangerous, it was impossible for them to escape.

Very soon, the Beyond Grade As left the spaceships one after another and flew at high speed on the battlefield. They moved along their own formation and quickly arrived at the battle zone.

Even though they were far away from each other, the auras of both parties that were unique to their individual strength resonated with each other and locked onto each other.

Han Xiao's gaze was locked on the Subduing Tree King from afar, and the Subduing Tree King also noticed it. He stared at Han Xiao, and his Pugilist flames continued to rise.

"Leave that Tree King to me. You guys deal with the rest," Han Xiao said in the channel.

"Understood."

The members of the association responded one after another. The direct Beyond Grade As distanced themselves a little and expressed the same attitude.

The Arcane Church did not allow Wuornos to participate in the battle. Black Star was currently the number one combatant in the three Universal Civilizations' army, so they naturally had no objections.

As Han Xiao charged forward, he activated all kinds of skills. His eyes never left the Subduing Tree King, and the two of them looked as though sparks were flying between them.

"In your territory, I could not touch you. I also have teammates now. What I didn't do last time will be resolved now!"

A cold light flashed past Han Xiao's eyes, and Mechanical Force suddenly shot out. The mechanical soldiers in his body were released and flew behind him, transforming and sticking to his body. The dense mechanical armor quickly covered his face that showed killing intent.

In the endless sea of fleets, the two groups of people approached each other rapidly with dazzling flames trailing behind them. Then, two streams of light suddenly collided, and a chaotic battle broke out!

Chapter 1337: Battle (2)

Multicolored lights spread out from the point of impact like a supernova.

The energy tsunami created by the combined forces of more than two hundred Beyond Grade As swallowed the large fleets around them. The high-energy reaction instantly alerted the countless battleship radars on the battlefield, and it instantly became the most eye-catching area in the entire battlefield.

The light cannons on the surface of the Mechanical Deity's body continuously bombarded a green meteor, but they were unable to penetrate the defense of the protective flames and were all reduced to light fragments.

Wrapped in green flames, the Subduing Tree King channeled his energy and punched out. His fist, which was flickering with dazzling light, hit the blade of the Celestial Punishment Edge heavily. At the point of contact, a violent shockwave exploded, and a loud ringing sound rang in the souls of living beings.

"Outsider, it really is you." The Subduing Tree King propped up Celestial Punishment Edge and released a cold mental wave.

Han Xiao could not be bothered to guess what the other party was thinking. Mechanical Force burst out from his body, and he activated the Getta Hadoken. The Celestial Punishment Edge maintained its momentum, and psionic energy gushed out along the edge of the blade. The powerful dark blue wave of energy sent the Subduing Tree King flying.

However, the next moment, the Subduing Tree King came to a halt, spun around, and charged again, continuing to face the Mechanical Deity's attacks head-on.

Fists and kicks brought about afterimages, and endless green shockwave blasts gushed out from his body, condensing to the point of almost solidifying. It was as if glowing spears were stabbing into the Mechanical Deity's psionic shield. With the support of the World Tree, the Subduing Tree King's protective flames were like an indestructible shield, constantly creating countless electric arcs and energy sparks in front of him. His fighting style had a strong suppression style.

The blade of the Celestial Punishment Edge swept up a wave of dark-blue psionic energy, each strike faster than the last. In the blink of an eye, Han Xiao had clashed thousands of times with the Tree King. The two of them were constantly moving forward and back at high speed, and the overlapping force fields caused the surrounding space to bend slightly.

If not for the fact that it's not suitable to use private messages, I would have said a few words…

Han Xiao pursed his lips and suppressed the urge to send a message to ask for the name of the move.

While fighting, he also observed the situation around him.

On a battlefield like this, there was no tacit understanding between armies to not attack high-level combatants. The countless battleships in the surroundings did not stop their attacks toward this side. Large numbers of troops were thrown into the war zone, forming a crisscross pattern.

However, the fleets on both sides wanted to kill the enemy's high-level combatants while protecting their own Supers. Thus, they formed a restraint, indirectly giving the Beyond Grade As on both sides room to maneuver.

It was also because of this reason that many Mechanics, including Han Xiao, did not summon too many mechanical troops. Otherwise, the target would be too large, and they would have no choice but to endure the concentrated fire of the surrounding fleets. This would result in significant additional losses, reducing their military strength. Limited resources needed to be used where they were needed the most, and this was not worth it.

Swoosh!

Just as Han Xiao was analyzing the situation, the Subduing Tree King's body suddenly glowed, and he utilized his Pugilist skills. His charging speed suddenly increased, and he charged straight at the Mechanical Deity's body. It was as if his entire body suddenly became invincible, and he actually crashed through the psionic shield. The green meteor smashed into the Mechanical Deity's abdomen, creating a huge pit, and large cracks spread on the armor.

Right after that, the Subduing Tree King's head suddenly started spinning as though it was going to turn into a drill and drill through the pit on the Mechanical Deity. Clearly, his head was not something ordinary.

However, right at this moment, large swaths of black nanoparticles suddenly seeped out from the pit in the Mechanical Deity's abdomen armor, quickly condensing and transforming into countless mechanical tentacles that lashed out at the Subduing Tree King. The tentacles suddenly tightened when the power reached the end, turning from a whip into a spear. A neat round of stabs landed on the Subduing Tree King's protective flames, pushing him out.

Following which, Han Xiao twisted the blade handle and used his other hand to slap the other party as if swatting a fly, sending the Tree King flying and knocking over three or four Beyond Grade As along the way.

"Want to enter my body? Dream on." Han Xiao patted the Mechanical Deity's abdomen, and the depression quickly recovered.

Against Mechanics, Pugilists would basically target the mechanic's main body or Lord's Avatar. This was the most efficient method, and the Subduing Tree King wanted to enter the Mechanical Deity's body to attack the main body.

Although he had caused a ruckus in the World Tree territory last time and lasted for about ten minutes under the siege of more than a hundred Beyond Grade As, this World Tree powerhouse still did not believe in his physical strength and tried to attack his main body.

After all, the three Universal Civilizations had accepted the title of 'Indestructible Body' because they had witnessed Han Xiao's achievements over the years. However, this information was not circulated in the World Tree Civilization. Han Xiao had only shown his strength once in the other party's territory before retreating with heavy injuries. Therefore, most of the World Tree experts did not know much about Han Xiao and would not easily give up on attacking his main body.

Han Xiao pondered. The strength of a Tree King is indeed extraordinary. I won't be able to take him down quickly.

Last time, they had fought in a hurry, so he did not experience the full strength of the Subduing Tree King. Now that he looked at it, the other party was indeed not weak. Before Karlot was fully matured, the Subduing Tree King was undoubtedly above all the Pugilists he had met so far. Be it 'Beast Ancestor' Gorutan or 'Star Shatterer' Sierron, they were all inferior compared to the Subduing Tree King. If they fought, they probably would not survive a day in the hands of the Tree King.

However, even if the Subduing Tree King was powerful, Han Xiao's raw strength was still above him.

At the same time, the Subduing Tree King also perfectly met the criteria of being a peak Beyond Grade A Super of the World Tree Faction. On the interface, the four talents of [World Tree Nemesis], [Civilization Leader Slayer], [Elderly Killer], and [Fearless Heart] all lit up.

"Let's fight steadily and defeat him." Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

He had the upper hand in terms of combat strength and class, but the Subduing Tree King was not someone to be trifled with. He could still exchange a few blows and would not be taken down in a short time.

The two of them fought intensely, and the other Beyond Grade As also engaged in a chaotic battle.

The energy from so many Beyond Grade As kept pushing the others away, causing everyone's battlefield to be further away from each other. Although most of them did not intend to fight one-on-one, they could support each other if they wanted to fight one after another. Thus, they formed small groups and fought fiercely.

…

Bang!

The Mechanical Emperor's Sacred Trident stabbed forward but was blocked by a broadsword. Psionic energy surrounded by Mechanical Force collided with each other on both sides of the trident, and the light blue energy ball exploded.

The two Mechanical Deities fought each other evenly, like two blurry afterimages that kept colliding. One of them was silver, and the other was gold and red with green energy surrounding its body. The color coordination was extremely bad.

"What a sharp fellow…"

Manison knocked his opponent away with his trident and narrowed his eyes.

He had already learned from Black Star that the individual strength of the World Tree was extremely powerful, but he only experienced the other side's powers after fighting them personally.

Although he had suffered a series of attacks from Black Star and was no longer at his peak, he was still firmly in the first tier. Ordinary peak Beyond Grade As were still no match for him. However, this enemy was now fighting him back and forth, even giving him quite a bit of pressure. Even though Manison realized that his strength slightly exceeded his opponent, it was not enough to give him an overwhelming advantage.

Furthermore, this person was not in the data of the World Tree experts that Han Xiao had provided. He was an unknown enemy.

Just as Manison was thinking, the other party suddenly sent out a mental wave.

"You're very powerful. What's your name?"

Hearing this, Manison did not respond.

Even after receiving no response, the other party did not stop and continued sending mental messages.

"It doesn't matter if you don't say it. I have my eyes on you. You have the right to be my trophy. The World Tree's Three Leaf Executive Officer, Lynn Karen. Remember this name. Your life is destined to be mine."

"You talk too much."

Manison was not affected at all.

After Black Star's training, he was no longer afraid of message bombardment.

However, he did remember the other party's name. According to Black Star, the ten Executive Officers were all at the top of the World Tree, and the higher they ranked, the more powerful they would be. Third Leaf was in the first tier of the World Tree experts, and she would definitely be in the top fifteen.

"Looks like a big fish…"

Manison's eyes flashed, and he silently increased his strength. His attacks became more and more vicious, and his killing intent overflowed.

…

In a certain part of the battlefield, a black and a white energy current collided with each other with a loud bang, causing countless sparks to fly like water.

Dark Lord Clotti controlled the surging dark energy and was fighting with a frail World Tree member.

The other party was also an Esper. He controlled dazzling white energy that was like flowing white gold. The texture was like a light muslin or like rolling fog, but it was extremely corrosive.

"What Esper Ability is this? It's on par with mine."

Clotti frowned slightly.

The strength of an Esper depended partly on their grade and partly on the effect of their Esper Ability. If their grade was the same, then the higher the grade of the Esper Ability, the more stable the advantage. For example, Gaud's energy control was one of the highest-grade Esper Abilities. If they grew to the same grade, Clotti basically had no chance of winning.

Clotti's dark energy control was already a Super High Risk Esper Ability, but the other party's Esper Ability was comparable to his.

Although the other party did not hit him, he realized that his cells had become weak, and his energy consumption was much higher than usual. It was as if the other party had used energy as a medium to attack him from afar.

This time, this person suddenly sent out a mental message and calmly said, "Your ability is not bad. If I present you to the mother tree, it will definitely be very happy."

"The World Tree also likes to collect Esper Abilities?" Clotti thought and tried to probe for information.

However, the other party did not reply.

Clotti thought that his opponent did not want to answer, so he gave up on the idea and continued to fight in silence.

However, after fighting for a while, the other party suddenly spoke.

"I'm the Four Leaf Executive Officer of the World Tree, Enrin Zarro."

Clotti was stunned. He thought that the other party was going to say something, so he immediately perked up.

However, after his opponent said this, he did not continue and fell silent.

Clotti frowned, feeling confused… Why did he suddenly introduce himself and stopped speaking?

After a while, Enrin spoke again.

"When you enter the embrace of the World Tree, we can become colleagues."

After saying this, he fell silent again, as though he was talking to himself and did not expect the other party to reply.

Clotti's eyelids twitched.

He confirmed that this was a weirdo who did whatever he wanted.

…

On the other side, Hila, who was wearing the Crimson Snake mechanical suit, was facing the attacks of four enemies. Crimson death energy gushed out like a tsunami, and the battle was extremely intense.

Compared to the other battlefields, there was a significant difference on Hila's side. When she was surrounded, there were no other Beyond Grade As supporting her. It was as though everyone was letting her face the attacks of multiple enemies alone.

Bang!

A Pugilist World Tree expert passed through the sea of death energy and beat Hila up. Just as she was about to break free from the chain attack, he kicked her in the abdomen.

While Hila was sent flying, another World Tree expert blocked her way. A series of spells rained down on Hila's back, sending her in another direction and inflicting another round of damage on her.

Hila tried her best to stabilize herself. Suddenly, she used Death Stealth and teleported to another location, gaining a short respite.

Her entire body was covered in blood. She looked like a ferocious evil spirit, heavily injured and weak.

Kasuyi, who was the closest, glanced over and quickly looked away. He had no intention of going over to help and even led his opponent further and further away.

Seeing this, one of the four attackers, a Holy Tree Emissary, said, "You've almost been beaten to death, but your companions are still ignoring you. No one is coming to help you… I didn't expect you guys to still be in the mood to have internal conflicts in the face of our invasion. Interesting."

Hila wiped the blood off her face, as though she did not feel any pain at all.

"No one came to help me… That's because I don't need help."

As soon as she finished speaking, a golden light suddenly erupted from her body, and all her injuries disappeared at a speed visible to the naked eye.

Hila straightened her back, and the chaotic energy waves returned to their peak. The refined death energy flowed out continuously, and her aura soared.

"It doesn't hurt at all. With this standard, it's a thousand years too early for you to try killing me!"

Chapter 1338: Battle (3)

Swoosh!

Kasuyi seemed to have turned into a phantom as he instantly dodged the magical energy beam from his opponent. He was not worried about Hila at all.

Hila's level was not at the peak Beyond Grade A realm, but in the eyes of the Beyond Grade As including Kasuyi, she was one of the most difficult to deal with. Not only could she reduce one's lifespan, but she also had a milkmaid bound to her. She was like an unkillable cockroach. Even if others were strong, no one was willing to provoke Hila.

Kasuyi turned his attention back to his opponent, and his eyes narrowed slightly. The invisible Psychic energy was like thousands of needles, giving his opponent a high-level Psychic Blast, but it was like hitting a solid wall. Most of its power was diverted by the opponent's Mental Defense Spell, turning into chaotic mental disturbances that spread to the surroundings, immediately triggering a large number of battleships' mental defense shields and even shattering the mental defense shields of the battleships at the front.

The other party was not willing to be outdone. Under the surge of energy, magic formations appeared one after another, gathering into a spherical shell. All kinds of exclusive spells poured out, dazzling and colorful. The dense wave of spells chased after Kasuyi, bombarding him with attacks.

"What a smooth magic connection. There are no flaws…"

Kasuyi's cells were all active, and his eyes emitted a strong light, observing his opponent while fighting.

Although he was not a Mage, he was knowledgeable. He could tell with one look that the other party had a lot of combat experience and was an extremely strong Mage. The coordination between spells was smooth and free, giving him the feeling that everything was integrated.

Furthermore, the World Tree was extremely powerful in terms of mental strength. If there was no overwhelming difference in strength, a Psychic would actually be at a disadvantage against a World Tree powerhouse. This was especially obvious in a battle of the same level. Kasuyi discovered that the opponent's mental barrier was extremely thick, and his mental attacks could not penetrate it as though it was indestructible.

"This guy seems to be a high-level Ancestral Spirit…"

Kasuyi adjusted his vision and saw the mark on the other party's forehead.

Black Star had once explained the composition of the World Tree powerhouses and helped them differentiate them. Ancestral Spirits had a special mark on their body that made them easy to recognize.

At this moment, he was fighting a member of the Thirteen Ancestral Spirits of the World Tree. He was ranked second, and his strength was among the top of the World Tree. He was not much weaker than the Three or Four Leaf Executive Officials.

While Kasuyi was making observations, the second Ancestral Spirit suddenly spoke.

"I recognize you. You're the one who killed Manny."

"Manny?"

Upon hearing this unfamiliar name, Kasuyi's eyes flashed. He immediately realized that this was the Holy Tree Emissary that he had killed some time ago.

The second Ancestral Spirit said indifferently, "I like strong enemies. You're a good opponent. I hope you can let me enjoy myself."

"…"

Kasuyi raised his brows.

We were just fighting to the death. Why did you suddenly start chatting?

He looked at the temporary chat channel of the Beyond Grade A team and realized that most of the people had been messaged by the World Tree powerhouses. It seemed like this was intentional.

On second thought, Kasuyi understood.

The mentality of the World Tree's experts is different from ours. They know that they won't really die in battle, so they are fearless and relaxed. We, on the other hand, have to fight with our all and are in a tense state. Therefore, they took the initiative to speak. It should be a psychological battle to affect our mentality… On the other hand, maybe they are trying to deepen the information connection and collect intelligence. Why not… Better not to answer.

Kasuyi changed his mind and gave up on responding. After leaving a 'don't answer' message in the chat channel, he focused on dealing with the second Ancestral Spirit. Psychic energy and magic flew all over the place.

…

A Starry Spiritual Dragon soared above the battlefield. Its eyes were like burning golden-red flames, and its enormous battleship-size body was extremely conspicuous. Every time its wings flapped, countless Dragon Spells would be cast, creating a storm of mana. Layers of defensive arrays covered its body. It was Dragon King Milizaus.

One of the army commanders was fighting with him. It looked like a tiny gray meteor was flying around the old dragon and attacking him continuously. He was wearing heavy armor and had all kinds of special firearms on his hands. He was a rare Cannon Master.

The World Tree Military Department was in charge of foreign battles, and a commander of the army meant the 'chief combatant of the military'. Only the top Beyond Grade As in the military could obtain such a title.

Every army commander had their own code name, which usually depended on their military unit. The army commander fighting the old dragon belonged to a World Tree Army called 'Dark Light', so he was known as Commander Dark Light.

The two of them were evenly matched, but because of his striking size, Milizaus became a target, attracting the firepower of most of the battleships around him.

In fact, when World Tree experts who were fighting with the other Beyond Grade As passed by, they would even throw a few skills at Old Dragon. After all, the target was so big, so the hit rate was extremely high.

Because of this, Milizaus suffered too much damage. The injuries on his body kept accumulating, and many dragon scales were torn off. His flesh and bones were deeply cut, and blood splattered everywhere. His situation was getting worse.

Only the old dragon was being beaten up.

Bam! A beam of light shot out from the muzzle of Commander Dark Light's cannon, piercing through the cracked defensive arrays and hitting the old dragon's back, shattering a large chunk of scales and flesh, adding a new injury to him.

"This is the first time I've seen a creature like you. I wonder what your meat tastes like," Commander Dark Light said as he fired his cannon.

Milizaus felt a sharp pain on his back. He swung his dragon head and let out an angry roar. The sound wave condensed from magic power surged out and hit Commander Dark Light, sending him flying.

However, Milizaus did not take the opportunity to chase after him. Instead, with a spiral movement, he flipped his body vertically, and a large number of magic patterns suddenly lit up on his body. The next moment, he disappeared from where he was and, with a flash, arrived elsewhere on the battlefield. There was a battle between more than ten people there, and he had his eyes on a Holy Tree Emissary who was heavily injured and was about to use his companions to cover his retreat.

Milizaus appeared instantly behind the Holy Tree Emissary. Before the other party could turn around and make a hasty defense, he opened his mouth and spat out a jade-like dragon breath that was enhanced by the Dragon Magic. It was like a golden-red flame that surged out and swallowed the target in an instant.

The Holy Tree Emissary's body melted and turned into a pile of dust that floated in the air before dissipating.

Not long after the battle started, the first casualty was born!

"Die!"

After claiming first blood, Milizaus felt that he had vented his anger. He was rejuvenated, fully displaying the essence of a kill steal.

However, his happiness did not last long. He was immediately beaten up. The World Tree experts around him turned around and focused their fire on Milizaus. They shattered a large number of dragon scales, and his life force flowed out rapidly.

At the same time, Commander Dark Light also rushed over. He switched to a Universal Treasure-level firearm and fired at Milizaus from afar. Powerful beams of light bombarded Milizaus' body, exploding into balls of flames and even shattering one dragon eye.

The surrounding battleships also turned their cannons around and focused their fire on Milizaus. He had gotten the first blood, but he was immediately targeted. He fell into danger, and his injuries were severe.

"Kill him!"

Commander Dark Light saw an opportunity and was prepared to kill the enemy in one go.

However, right at this moment, a change occurred.

Swoosh!

A dazzling pale golden light shot out from the back of the three Universal Civilizations' fleet and accurately landed on Milizaus.

An enormous amount of life energy poured in, and Milizaus' battered body immediately began to recover. In the blink of an eye, more than half of the heavily injured dragon's body had recovered, and he was full of energy again. The dragon tail swung excitedly and playfully shattered several World Tree battleships.

This scene attracted the attention of many World Tree experts, and their expressions changed slightly.

"Recovery-type Esper Ability‽"

After fighting in the universe for so many years, the World Tree experts had seen many things, and it was not rare to see Espers with recovery abilities. However, those who could reach the Beyond Grade A level were extremely rare. After all, recovery-type Esper Abilities were considered functional Esper Abilities and were not suitable for combat. Furthermore, most Esper Abilities did not have high potential, so training and sublimation were extremely difficult.

However, this time, not only did the enemy civilization have a recovery-type Esper, the recovery effect was unbelievably strong. It could heal a peak Beyond Grade A life form in just moments. It was no exaggeration to say that this was the strongest recovery-type Esper they had ever seen!

"I didn't expect this prey to have such a card."

The expressions of many World Tree experts changed, and they immediately realized that something was wrong.

If they did not get rid of this recovery-type Esper, their losses would be extremely huge, and this mutual destruction mission would be less effective!

"We have to kill the Esper first!"

A portion of the World Tree experts quickly completed their communication through the mental network. They immediately abandoned their current opponents, gathered together, and charged toward the source of the life force. Although the Esper was at the rear of the three Universal Civilizations' fleet, they had no choice but to charge head-on.

This was actually in-line with the players' strategy… After all, who would not cut the healer first in a team battle?

However, at this moment, a few streams of light suddenly shot out from the fleet, fearlessly facing this group of attackers who had the advantage in numbers. The two sides collided.

With a flash of light, violent explosions spread out, and the World Tree experts' advancement was immediately stopped.

The group of World Tree experts looked up and saw five Beyond Grade A life forms covered in light blocking their path.

"There's still a group hiding‽"

Seeing this, many World Tree experts were surprised. They thought that the high-level combatants of their opponents had all joined the battlefield.

The five of them looked at the large number of World Tree powerhouses. Not only were they not nervous, they even looked eager. They were the five Underworld Hero Spirit Kings.

The other three Heroic Spirit Kings, including Sorokin, did not appear. Aurora only sent five of them, and the leader was the second strongest Heroic Spirit King, Rega.

"Heh, I can finally exercise."

Rega stretched his shoulders, and without another word, he charged forward with the other four Hero Spirit Kings, starting a new brawl.

Even though the other Beyond Grade As knew about the Sanctum Revival, they did not want to sacrifice themselves so easily. In comparison, the Underworld Hero Spirits were the ones who were truly unafraid of death.

Meanwhile, in the three Universal Civilizations' command ship, Simon watched the battles of Han Xiao, Hila, and the Underworld Hero Spirits. He then turned to look at the calm Aurora and shook his head.

"Those from Planet Aquamarine… are all monsters."

…

Bang!

The Mechanical Deity and the Subduing Tree King clashed once again, and an intense shockwave erupted.

"This outsider seems to be even stronger than the last time we met…"

The Subduing Tree King stretched his aching fingers. Beneath his cold exterior was his racing heart.

Although the outcome of the battle could not be determined for the time being, he felt a long-forgotten pressure from Han Xiao. He had only experienced such an unparalleled sense of power from one person—the unfathomable Ancestral Tree King.

He did not expect that the civilization they had chosen this time would have such high-level combatants. They had met a tough opponent!

Although he did not want to admit it, he had to face reality. He might not be able to defeat this outsider who had such amazing abilities.

The Subduing Tree King quickly scanned the battlefield. In the mental network, there were already six or seven silent companions, which meant that they had died in battle.

With the help of the recovery-type Esper, not a single enemy was killed!

If this continued, would they not be completely wiped out?

How could this do?

"We can't wait any longer!"

The Subduing Tree King's eyes darkened. Seeing that the situation was not right, he immediately changed his mind.

Swoosh!

The Subduing Tree King suddenly retreated and covered his face with his palm. His mouth was wide open as if he was screaming in pain.

The next moment, a dazzling green light appeared all over his body, as if he had released the energy of the World Tree in his body. An endless green light overflowed from his body.

Then, with a bang, an irresistible pressure burst out from him, as if a higher being had descended!

The green light quickly condensed and turned into translucent light green roots of the World Tree. At first, they were just like many small snakes, floating beside the Subduing Tree King. However, the size of these roots quickly grew and expanded, whipping around the battlefield crazily!

The appearance of the Subduing Tree King had also changed. His entire body was different, and his body gained a texture like that of the World Tree roots. Green World Tree power flowed within his translucent body, as if he had undergone a transformation.

A powerful aura blew over like a suffocating gale!

Previously, the Subduing Tree King had mainly relied on his own strength to fight, but at this moment, he had started to borrow the World Tree's strength to a large extent. This was the World Tree's ability that could only be activated by the connection level of a Tree King, and it was also the reason why a Tree King was a Tree King.

All of this happened in an instant. During the transformation, Han Xiao did not stop his long-range attacks, but they were all blocked by the World Tree Roots.

"Oh? Using an ultimate move?"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

He was no stranger to this transformation. This was the unique power of the Tree King. It turned his body into a branch of the World Tree, like a temporary base station.

In his previous life, every time a Tree King activated this form, it would be a sign that they were going to start a massacre.

The most terrifying thing was not the increase in strength from this transformation but the branch of the World Tree that their body had turned into. It could bring about an exclusive faction buff halo that covered an extremely wide area, increasing the combat power of all the World Tree members on the battlefield!

This was the Tree King's war form!